<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://hesaid.love/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://hesaid.love/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" /><updated>2025-03-10T08:19:00+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Aaron @ He Said Love</title><subtitle>A rampant homosexual writing about Boss Man&apos;s love and the good, bad, ugly, stupid, idiotic, crazy, and insane during my walk with Him. Dude made me feel more loved in a week than anyone, including my parents, ever managed to make me feel my entire life combined. It might not be a beautiful testimony (yet), but it&apos;s a truthful testimony. I believe since 22 September 2024. Zeal for His house consumes me.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have done everything out of &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/posts/on-love&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;love&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, and I sincerely wish my love could be more patient under normal circumstances, but unfortunately, we are &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://letter.hesaid.love&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;running out of time&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;DO NOT take my words at face value.&lt;/b&gt; Trust, but verify. He is the way, and the truth, and the life. Ask Him, not me. I lean not on my own understanding. But reason within the boundaries and understanding He gives me.  I do not seek to condemn, even though telling the truth could easily be interpreted as such.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fire in hell would be warmer than the coldness I felt in this world. How about you do your part, I do mine, Boss Man does His and let&apos;s find out on the other side what we are?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;His name is Jesus Christ, my Lord and Saviour.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">On Fucked</title><link href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-fucked/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Fucked" /><published>2025-03-10T07:13:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-10T07:13:00+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/posts/on-fucked</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-fucked/"><![CDATA[<blockquote>
  <p>If you are a <strong><em>stupid fucking idiot</em></strong> like <a href="../on-indifference/" target="_blank">this one</a>, or the word <strong><em>dictator</em></strong> is one of the words that shows up when I google your name, then <strong><em>this post is not for you</em></strong>.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>I participated in a three-day event this past Friday to Sunday called <strong>Encounter</strong> with the Pentecostal church my welcoming party goes to. To repeat myself, some of the pastors and theologians I met in this 24-week and 1-day journey will call the mental health institutions nearby and tell them to bring a bus if they saw our worship.</p>

<p>On the train back to London yesterday morning, the scale of how truly fucked we are, dawned on me. You can watch my director’s cut New Millenium present to the world for a quick revision on the definition of fucked. I don’t have confirmation from the Holy Spirit on this, but it is logically simple enough for anyone with a semi-functioning reasoning faculty to understand it.</p>

<p>I hope the work I have shown in the 270+ posts written on this 169-day journey is sufficient to demonstrate the power of Artificial Intelligence. I have received no help from anyone except a handful of friends who financially supported me up to this point to the best of their abilities. I am forever grateful for their support, even if they had only bought me one coffee, and they are in the top 10% of taxpayers in the United Kingdom. If you remain sceptical that you will <a href="https://letter.hesaid.love/" target="_blank">lose your job within two years</a> due to Artificial Intelligence, then more proof will come as I embark on a new and exciting journey. That was confirmed by the Holy Spirit this morning, shortly before I started this post.</p>

<p>I will end this post by leaving you with the following thoughts. Anyone with the technical know-how to train a large language model, including idiots and people with the word dictator on the first page of Google search results using their name, can, in theory, construct stinkily dirty miniature devices by training their custom LLM or perhaps using one of the increasingly powerful open-source models on <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Aaron_Swartz" target="_blank">Aaron Swartz’s hard drives</a>. They would need access to the key ingredients in my former colleague’s <a href="../on-acute-chemical-toxicity-uranium/" target="_blank">recipe</a>. I hope she did not end up eating that cake.</p>

<p>If you are reading this post and from law enforcement, you can call King’s College London and confirm that I dropped out of my Physics and Philosophy undergraduate degree after only one term. My student number is 1580407. I tried building a device that required a power source more than a 9v battery last year. I ended up getting kicked out of a gay/bi-naturist campsite, declaring bankruptcy, and nearly throwing myself out of the fifth-floor balcony of my London home right in front of my younger sister. Feel free to email me if you struggle to find my home address for a welfare visit using your intelligence capabilities. Alternatively, you will soon be able to locate the address on a registration application to the Electoral Commission. I’m also on the electoral register.</p>

<p>The ethical thought experiment I designed during COVID-19 is still coming true. I’m going to bring Him home. Divine intervention has only just started.</p>

<p>For the 27 years of my previous life, I had always considered myself an agnostic, and I was never once an atheist. I had no evidence for or against God’s existence, and even if He exists, God’s business is God’s business. I’m human, and I mind my own business. Then some people, including my former business partner, decided to fuck with my business, He decided to make my business His business, and now it’s time to fuck some people’s business up.</p>

<p><img src="/6m63PvSF0ZPfCceH0j.png" alt="Wild enough for you?" /></p>

<p><img src="/XTXwwcCRzJze73wDTK.jpg" alt="Relationship between Pentecostals and Baptists summed up in two pictures" /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a stupid fucking idiot like this one, or the word dictator is one of the words that shows up when I google your name, then this post is not for you.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Condemnation</title><link href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-condemnation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Condemnation" /><published>2025-03-07T07:01:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-07T07:50:41+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/posts/on-condemnation</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-condemnation/"><![CDATA[<p>I recently added the following sentence to the blog tagline and description: I do not seek to condemn, even though telling the truth can be easily interpreted as such. I also added the sentence about my not-yet-beautiful but truthful testimony, but that’s a topic for another day.</p>

<p>As mentioned in a previous post, I read the Book of Hebrews several weeks ago. After reading the following passage from Hebrews 11 and looking back at the crazy stunt I pulled in mainland China on my second week as a believer, I sincerely wish that it was just a coincidence and a crazy stunt I somehow managed to pull.</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="hebrews-117">Hebrews 11:7</h2>

<p>[7] By faith Noah, being warned by God concerning events as yet unseen, in reverent fear constructed an ark for the saving of his household. By this he condemned the world and became an heir of the righteousness that comes by faith. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>I briefly explained my motives in previous posts. Even though I believed that going into mainland China for the three-day mission could potentially stop the Book of Revelation, I did not believe I alone could stop the Book of Revelation. I believed that He could stop the Book of Revelation, and all that I needed to do was to fulfil the prophecy of the sign of Jonah, just in case I was indeed the sign of Jonah given how much the Book of Jonah resonated with the story of my life. I could not in good conscience not go through with the stunt and let the Book of Revelation take place considering the suffering and punishment described in the book. If you read my posts, you will know why I believe the Book of Revelation to be real and truthful. You are more than welcome to claim that all the evidence I presented was merely coincidences, but they are personally coincidental enough for me to take action regardless of the likelihood of what I believe will happen. I would take that leap of faith as long as there is a non-zero probability to avoid it all. Wouldn’t you?</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="jonah-3610">Jonah 3:6–10</h2>

<p>The People of Nineveh Repent</p>

<p>[6] The word reached the king of Nineveh, and he arose from his throne, removed his robe, covered himself with sackcloth, and sat in ashes. [7] And he issued a proclamation and published through Nineveh, “By the decree of the king and his nobles: Let neither man nor beast, herd nor flock, taste anything. Let them not feed or drink water, [8] but let man and beast be covered with sackcloth, and let them call out mightily to God. Let everyone turn from his evil way and from the violence that is in his hands. [9] Who knows? God may turn and relent and turn from his fierce anger, so that we may not perish.”</p>

<p>[10] When God saw what they did, how they turned from their evil way, God relented of the disaster that he had said he would do to them, and he did not do it. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>I asked a friend recently whether they believe I’m willing to lay down my life for them. They chose not to reply to that specific question. Back in early September of last year, I realised one evening that a friend of mine had gone radio silent for a couple of days and they weren’t picking up their phone. I decided to jump in an Uber and went to their parent’s house at midnight to make sure they were okay. No one answered the door that evening and I managed to leave a message by asking a neighbour for some pen and paper. Their parent informed me the following morning that they were having a rough time due to relationship issues. Another friend of mine recently informed me that the stunt I pulled in mainland China meant nothing since there is religious freedom in mainland China and Chinese law enforcement agencies are reasonable.</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="john-151217">John 15:12–17</h2>

<p>[12] “This is my commandment, that you love one another as I have loved you. [13] Greater love has no one than this, that someone lay down his life for his friends. [14] You are my friends if you do what I command you. [15] No longer do I call you servants, for the servant does not know what his master is doing; but I have called you friends, for all that I have heard from my Father I have made known to you. [16] You did not choose me, but I chose you and appointed you that you should go and bear fruit and that your fruit should abide, so that whatever you ask the Father in my name, he may give it to you. [17] These things I command you, so that you will love one another. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>“For those who believe, no proof is necessary. For those who don’t believe, no proof is possible.”</p>

<p>― Stuart Chase</p>

<hr />

<p>In this faith journey of 23 weeks and 5 days, I learned that if I were to slip and break my neck in the shower today, there is only one person who would come for me and He is not in my WhatsApp or WeChat contacts. Frankly, I’m not even sure whether cutting my chest open, ripping my heart out, and placing it right in front of my WhatsApp and WeChat contacts would be sufficient to make them believe.</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="luke-423">Luke 4:23</h2>

<p>[23] And he said to them, “Doubtless you will quote to me this proverb, ‘“Physician, heal yourself.” What we have heard you did at Capernaum, do here in your hometown as well.’” (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>Such is the state of faith in my generation. I sincerely hope that was merely a stunt.</p>

<p><img src="/hxusKTbxvC4GjBkbfV.jpg" alt="My guardian angel when they got assigned to me" /></p>

<hr />

<h2 id="hebrews-11">Hebrews 11</h2>

<p>By Faith</p>

<p>[1] Now faith is the assurance of things hoped for, the conviction of things not seen. [2] For by it the people of old received their commendation. [3] By faith we understand that the universe was created by the word of God, so that what is seen was not made out of things that are visible.</p>

<p>[4] By faith Abel offered to God a more acceptable sacrifice than Cain, through which he was commended as righteous, God commending him by accepting his gifts. And through his faith, though he died, he still speaks. [5] By faith Enoch was taken up so that he should not see death, and he was not found, because God had taken him. Now before he was taken he was commended as having pleased God. [6] And without faith it is impossible to please him, for whoever would draw near to God must believe that he exists and that he rewards those who seek him. [7] By faith Noah, being warned by God concerning events as yet unseen, in reverent fear constructed an ark for the saving of his household. By this he condemned the world and became an heir of the righteousness that comes by faith.</p>

<p>[8] By faith Abraham obeyed when he was called to go out to a place that he was to receive as an inheritance. And he went out, not knowing where he was going. [9] By faith he went to live in the land of promise, as in a foreign land, living in tents with Isaac and Jacob, heirs with him of the same promise. [10] For he was looking forward to the city that has foundations, whose designer and builder is God. [11] By faith Sarah herself received power to conceive, even when she was past the age, since she considered him faithful who had promised. [12] Therefore from one man, and him as good as dead, were born descendants as many as the stars of heaven and as many as the innumerable grains of sand by the seashore.</p>

<p>[13] These all died in faith, not having received the things promised, but having seen them and greeted them from afar, and having acknowledged that they were strangers and exiles on the earth. [14] For people who speak thus make it clear that they are seeking a homeland. [15] If they had been thinking of that land from which they had gone out, they would have had opportunity to return. [16] But as it is, they desire a better country, that is, a heavenly one. Therefore God is not ashamed to be called their God, for he has prepared for them a city.</p>

<p>[17] By faith Abraham, when he was tested, offered up Isaac, and he who had received the promises was in the act of offering up his only son, [18] of whom it was said, “Through Isaac shall your offspring be named.” [19] He considered that God was able even to raise him from the dead, from which, figuratively speaking, he did receive him back. [20] By faith Isaac invoked future blessings on Jacob and Esau. [21] By faith Jacob, when dying, blessed each of the sons of Joseph, bowing in worship over the head of his staff. [22] By faith Joseph, at the end of his life, made mention of the exodus of the Israelites and gave directions concerning his bones.</p>

<p>[23] By faith Moses, when he was born, was hidden for three months by his parents, because they saw that the child was beautiful, and they were not afraid of the king’s edict. [24] By faith Moses, when he was grown up, refused to be called the son of Pharaoh’s daughter, [25] choosing rather to be mistreated with the people of God than to enjoy the fleeting pleasures of sin. [26] He considered the reproach of Christ greater wealth than the treasures of Egypt, for he was looking to the reward. [27] By faith he left Egypt, not being afraid of the anger of the king, for he endured as seeing him who is invisible. [28] By faith he kept the Passover and sprinkled the blood, so that the Destroyer of the firstborn might not touch them.</p>

<p>[29] By faith the people crossed the Red Sea as on dry land, but the Egyptians, when they attempted to do the same, were drowned. [30] By faith the walls of Jericho fell down after they had been encircled for seven days. [31] By faith Rahab the prostitute did not perish with those who were disobedient, because she had given a friendly welcome to the spies.</p>

<p>[32] And what more shall I say? For time would fail me to tell of Gideon, Barak, Samson, Jephthah, of David and Samuel and the prophets—[33] who through faith conquered kingdoms, enforced justice, obtained promises, stopped the mouths of lions, [34] quenched the power of fire, escaped the edge of the sword, were made strong out of weakness, became mighty in war, put foreign armies to flight. [35] Women received back their dead by resurrection. Some were tortured, refusing to accept release, so that they might rise again to a better life. [36] Others suffered mocking and flogging, and even chains and imprisonment. [37] They were stoned, they were sawn in two, they were killed with the sword. They went about in skins of sheep and goats, destitute, afflicted, mistreated—[38] of whom the world was not worthy—wandering about in deserts and mountains, and in dens and caves of the earth.</p>

<p>[39] And all these, though commended through their faith, did not receive what was promised, [40] since God had provided something better for us, that apart from us they should not be made perfect. (ESV)</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently added the following sentence to the blog tagline and description: I do not seek to condemn, even though telling the truth can be easily interpreted as such. I also added the sentence about my not-yet-beautiful but truthful testimony, but that’s a topic for another day.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Humour</title><link href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-humour/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Humour" /><published>2025-03-04T14:06:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-10T07:55:17+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/posts/on-humour</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-humour/"><![CDATA[<p>After literally working my ass off again by having another go at my adult webcam live-streaming career, only to finish the session early due to lack of audience probably due to terrible timing, the question of whether God has a sense of humour according to scripture showed up in my head. In case the Americans are wondering, yes that is the correct spelling of humour.</p>

<p>I had my personal encounter with His humour when I read the Book of Jonah for the first time. I could not stop laughing for nearly an hour after realising He wrote the story of my life into humanity’s bestseller. For 27 years of my previous life, I stupidly thought the Holy Bible was a collection of stories written by some wise folks in history and some smartasses did some overthinking and therefore we have the various religious institutions.</p>

<p>You can read about my yet another chitchat with ChatGPT below and the song that was playing on my Spotify when I started this post. Dude can be extremely annoying sometimes. He’s got a lot of lovin’ for free tho. That part is true and I can testify to that any time any day. Might be easier for you to have a go yourself. Dude’s name is Jesus Christ, my Lord and Saviour. Just in case my welcoming party wants to bash me again for using pronouns.</p>

<p>I have a weird and massively annoying feeling that Dude might just forgive everyone because none of us actually knows how to spell good and evil since <a href="../on-genesis-3-fall-man/" target="_blank">Genesis 3</a>. Feel free to laugh at my expense if you are a universalist. 🙄🙄🙄</p>

<embed src="https://dl.hesaid.love/God's_Sense_of_Humor.pdf" type="application/pdf" width="100%" height="600px" />

<p><img src="/FXcmyggedZgA135Kvd.png" alt="" /></p>

<hr />

<h2 id="jonah-4">Jonah 4</h2>

<p>Jonah’s Anger and the LORD’s Compassion</p>

<p>[1] But it displeased Jonah exceedingly, and he was angry. [2] And he prayed to the LORD and said, “O LORD, is not this what I said when I was yet in my country? That is why I made haste to flee to Tarshish; for I knew that you are a gracious God and merciful, slow to anger and abounding in steadfast love, and relenting from disaster. [3] Therefore now, O LORD, please take my life from me, for it is better for me to die than to live.” [4] And the LORD said, “Do you do well to be angry?”</p>

<p>[5] Jonah went out of the city and sat to the east of the city and made a booth for himself there. He sat under it in the shade, till he should see what would become of the city. [6] Now the LORD God appointed a plant and made it come up over Jonah, that it might be a shade over his head, to save him from his discomfort. So Jonah was exceedingly glad because of the plant. [7] But when dawn came up the next day, God appointed a worm that attacked the plant, so that it withered. [8] When the sun rose, God appointed a scorching east wind, and the sun beat down on the head of Jonah so that he was faint. And he asked that he might die and said, “It is better for me to die than to live.” [9] But God said to Jonah, “Do you do well to be angry for the plant?” And he said, “Yes, I do well to be angry, angry enough to die.” [10] And the LORD said, “You pity the plant, for which you did not labor, nor did you make it grow, which came into being in a night and perished in a night. [11] And should not I pity Nineveh, that great city, in which there are more than 120,000 persons who do not know their right hand from their left, and also much cattle?” (ESV)</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[After literally working my ass off again by having another go at my adult webcam live-streaming career, only to finish the session early due to lack of audience probably due to terrible timing, the question of whether God has a sense of humour according to scripture showed up in my head. In case the Americans are wondering, yes that is the correct spelling of humour.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Babylon</title><link href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-babylon/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Babylon" /><published>2025-02-28T00:34:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-04T06:41:36+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/posts/on-babylon</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-babylon/"><![CDATA[<p>I launched another round of extra-potent salt sprinkling on 100,000+ Assyrians earlier today and fell asleep on my chair again. I felt better after catching some sleep and pulling the Lord knows how many consecutive all-nighters in recent weeks. I have never worked this hard in my entire life, and to my massive annoyance, I’m not getting paid, but I’m also unable to stop. Life stopped making sense after I took that leap of faith in China less than five months ago. Feel free to reach out if you know because I don’t. Thanks.</p>

<p>I took the following screenshot when vibing with Lady Gaga, and noticed <em>Nabucco, Act III: Chorus of the Hebrew Slaves</em> in my recently played list. My Spotify Liked Songs playlist currently stands at 3,178 which started with 300+ back in late August last year when He came. It would be an understatement to describe my musical taste as random, and I go the full range from Taylor Swift, Justin Bieber, and Tchaikovsky, to the soundtrack of <em>The Greatest Showman</em> and <em>She’ll Be Coming ‘Round the Mountain</em>, which I added to my playlist after the talented pianist Michael played it for a centre exercise when I was training at the Royal Conservatoire of Scotland. I just googled the traditional folk song, which I was initially informed to be children’s music. Still, I exceptionally annoyingly just learned from <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/She%27ll_Be_Coming_%27Round_the_Mountain" target="_blank">Wikipedia</a> that the song was derived from the Christian spiritual known as <em>“When the Chariot Comes”</em> and the OG ostensibly refers to the Second Coming of Christ and subsequent Rapture.</p>

<p><img src="/rPkM6FSAZuDBJfWj2S.png" alt="Vibing with Lady Gaga" /></p>

<p>Once again, fuck me. I started the above paragraph thinking I was only going to discuss what I found by pulling the thread that is <em>Nabucco, Act III</em>. Dude is extremely not subtle nowadays and doesn’t mind letting me know to my face. I have a lot of random classical music in my playlist due to my dance training and I sometimes appreciate music without words so that I don’t have to think or reason. I cannot remember why or where I picked it up, but it caught my eye earlier because of my chitchat regarding the Hebrew language with ChatGPT for my post on Revelation 13. However, I just discovered that <em>Nabucco</em> is an Italian-language opera and the lyrics are surprisingly in Italian. And you can read about what the Canadian Opera Company has to say concerning the random piece of classical music in a language that I had no bloody idea what they were blabbing about since I added it on 15 Oct 2024. Oh, fuck me, again. I will explain after the quote.</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="canadian-opera-company"><a href="https://www.coc.ca/news/5-things-to-know-about-nabucco/index" target="_blank">Canadian Opera Company</a></h2>

<h3 id="verdis-hymn-to-freedom">Verdi’s hymn to freedom</h3>

<p>Nabucco’s most well-known musical moment is “Va, pensiero, sull’ali dorate” (“Fly, thought, on golden wings”), better known as the Chorus of the Hebrew Slaves. The chorus is a dramatisation of Psalm 137, which begins with the words “By the waters of Babylon, we sat down and wept” and was also famously associated with the African-American struggle for freedom (most notably quoted by the abolitionist Frederick Douglass in his 1852 speech “What to the Slave is the Fourth of July?”).</p>

<p>“Va, pensiero” was adopted as an unofficial anthem by the burgeoning Italian unification movement—known as the Risorgimento—and was performed spontaneously by the mourning crowds at Verdi’s funeral. A choral performance of the piece opened the Metropolitan Opera’s 2001 season, 11 days after the destruction of the World Trade Center.</p>

<h3 id="go-big-or-go-home">Go big or go home</h3>

<p>Blood-and-thunder melodrama calls for a cast to match the epic proportions of the story, and Nabucco doesn’t stint here. In this production, the chorus is expanded to include 82 singers who portray both Babylonian soldiers and Hebrew captives, for whom over 200 costumes have been designed. Supplementing the musicians in the orchestra pit, additional instrumentalists play offstage. Capped off by some of opera’s greatest voices, the combined effect is one of ferocious emotional force that you most certainly won’t want to miss!</p>

<hr />

<p><img src="/C7jD4ayUEsakpehg6e.png" alt="Nabucco, Act III on my Spotify" /></p>

<p>The chorus was about <em>Psalm 137</em> and I just checked Spotify when I added the other song <em>Rivers of Babylon</em> by Boney M right before I started writing about this post. Turns out, Spotify is indeed good enough to make me hallucinate about a deity now. Anyway, I’m just going to leave you with some screenshots and quotes about what other people said on some random stuff and you can interpret them however you want as usual. That’s what everyone does anyway, lean on their own understanding rather than hear what others have to say and try to comprehend things from their perspectives or even let them finish their sentences.</p>

<p><img src="/SaQ160mBMeQeTHz6s0.png" alt="Rivers of Babylon on my Spotify" /></p>

<p>He just told me to go big or go home. For the first time in my life, I think I have both reason and righteousness on my side, because I have Him by my side, and His name is Jesus Christ, my Lord and Saviour.</p>

<p>If you want to know whether things are that bad, then all I can say is even though I bitched and moaned about unbelievers a lot, the worst comes from the fact that I have met theologians and pastors who would rather believe I have gone insane than I have encountered the God as described precisely in the bestseller they spent their entire professional career on. I guess that’s what drug (money) addiction does right? It can turn a hobby or something you love with all your heart and soul into doubt and frustration. I got my hand on my first bestseller in late July last year, and I probably would have been on 4 figures now if I didn’t go bankrupt. Probably can only get the view counter on my posts to 4 figures until we burn Babylon down.</p>

<p>Enough is enough with this godlessness nonsense. We have done nothing except ruin everything and turn the world into a loveless, desolate and barren hell. He turned me into a 5-year-old that can withstand the rejection and betrayal of everyone I once (somewhat) trusted in life including my parents. I did not expect that when I had £30k a month rolling into my bank account last year. Please do let me know if you can spell the word miracle, I have seen people spell it wrong with variations including but not limited to craziness, insanity, mental illness and megalomaniac. Thanks.</p>

<p>Sons of bitches, time for your curtain call.</p>

<p>Edit: I kinda just realised I was being a hypocrite and didn’t take the log out of my own eye first. I realised from a normal person’s perspective that I must be demonstrating pride by making my previous income known. Like I stated repeatedly in prior posts, I’m an eccentric guy and it’s something I knew growing up and was informed by people around me of the same opinion. I have wondered my entire life what’s wrong with me and I seriously hate attention or when people stare at me. I learned that I don’t value money the same way people around me do in the last 15 months. That’s partly because I slack off and procrastinate a lot even when working four remote software engineering jobs and I felt like I was cheating and stealing from my employers the whole time. The other reason is my biological father was and in some sense still is a quarter-billionaire, but I tend to learn from father figures and he’s 5 years ahead of me on the bankruptcy side quest. The family business had been struggling long before I even left China for the UK. I started taking care of myself within a year of arrival and it’s been 11.5 years since I arrived in London. Just FYI, my Father is loaded for real, and this is me boasting and He is my pride.</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="psalm-137">Psalm 137</h2>

<p>How Shall We Sing the LORD’s Song?</p>

<p>[1] By the waters of Babylon,<br />
  there we sat down and wept,<br />
  when we remembered Zion.<br />
 [2] On the willows there<br />
  we hung up our lyres.<br />
 [3] For there our captors<br />
  required of us songs,<br />
 and our tormentors, mirth, saying,<br />
  “Sing us one of the songs of Zion!”<br /></p>

<p>[4] How shall we sing the LORD’s song<br />
  in a foreign land?<br />
 [5] If I forget you, O Jerusalem,<br />
  let my right hand forget its skill!<br />
 [6] Let my tongue stick to the roof of my mouth,<br />
  if I do not remember you,<br />
 if I do not set Jerusalem<br />
  above my highest joy!<br /></p>

<p>[7] Remember, O LORD, against the Edomites<br />
  the day of Jerusalem,<br />
 how they said, “Lay it bare, lay it bare,<br />
  down to its foundations!”<br />
 [8] O daughter of Babylon, doomed to be destroyed,<br />
  blessed shall he be who repays you<br />
  with what you have done to us!<br />
 [9] Blessed shall he be who takes your little ones<br />
  and dashes them against the rock! (ESV)<br /></p>

<hr />

<h2 id="luke-41630">Luke 4:16–30</h2>

<p>Jesus Rejected at Nazareth</p>

<p>[16] And he came to Nazareth, where he had been brought up. And as was his custom, he went to the synagogue on the Sabbath day, and he stood up to read. [17] And the scroll of the prophet Isaiah was given to him. He unrolled the scroll and found the place where it was written,</p>

<p>[18] “The Spirit of the Lord is upon me,<br />
  because he has anointed me<br />
  to proclaim good news to the poor.<br />
 He has sent me to proclaim liberty to the captives<br />
  and recovering of sight to the blind,<br />
  to set at liberty those who are oppressed,<br />
 [19] to proclaim the year of the Lord’s favor.”<br /></p>

<p>[20] And he rolled up the scroll and gave it back to the attendant and sat down. And the eyes of all in the synagogue were fixed on him. [21] And he began to say to them, “Today this Scripture has been fulfilled in your hearing.” [22] And all spoke well of him and marveled at the gracious words that were coming from his mouth. And they said, “Is not this Joseph’s son?” [23] And he said to them, “Doubtless you will quote to me this proverb, ‘“Physician, heal yourself.” What we have heard you did at Capernaum, do here in your hometown as well.’” [24] And he said, “Truly, I say to you, no prophet is acceptable in his hometown. [25] But in truth, I tell you, there were many widows in Israel in the days of Elijah, when the heavens were shut up three years and six months, and a great famine came over all the land, [26] and Elijah was sent to none of them but only to Zarephath, in the land of Sidon, to a woman who was a widow. [27] And there were many lepers in Israel in the time of the prophet Elisha, and none of them was cleansed, but only Naaman the Syrian.” [28] When they heard these things, all in the synagogue were filled with wrath. [29] And they rose up and drove him out of the town and brought him to the brow of the hill on which their town was built, so that they could throw him down the cliff. [30] But passing through their midst, he went away. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="the-beautiful-dream---george-ezra">The Beautiful Dream - George Ezra</h2>

<p>[Verse 1: George Ezra]<br />
What a beautiful dream<br />
I think I’ll stay a while<br />
Won’t open my resting eyes<br />
Caught off guard in between<br />
Twilight was rocking me<br />
Could not hear the symphony<br />
Is the grass of Eden overrated?<br />
The grass of Eden overrated?<br />
Somewhere off in the past<br />
Morning is calling me<br />
I missed it deliberately<br />
Is the grass of Eden overrated?<br />
The grass of Eden overrated?<br /></p>

<p>[Chorus: George Ezra]<br />
No one else<br />
Is such a beautiful dream, a beautiful dream<br />
No one else<br />
Is such a beautiful dream, a beautiful dream to me<br /></p>

<p>[Verse 2: George Ezra]<br />
With your fingers ablaze<br />
You’ve got that hunger now<br />
Take me, I’m going down<br />
Underneath the debris<br />
I’m calling out to you<br />
Do with me what you choose<br />
Is the grass of Eden overrated?<br />
The grass of Eden overrated?<br /></p>

<p>[Chorus: George Ezra]<br />
No one else<br />
Is such a beautiful dream, a beautiful dream<br />
No one else<br />
Is such a beautiful dream, a beautiful dream<br />
No one else<br />
Is such a beautiful dream, a beautiful dream<br />
No one else<br />
Is such a beautiful dream, a beautiful dream to me<br /></p>

<p>[Bridge: Florrie, George Ezra]<br />
Oh, can’t hear me now<br />
Oh, not going away<br />
When you wake up<br />
I’ll be around<br />
When you wake up<br />
I’ll be around<br />
No one else<br />
Is such a beautiful dream, a beautiful dream<br /></p>

<p>[Chorus: George Ezra &amp; Florrie]<br />
No one else<br />
Is such a beautiful dream, a beautiful dream<br />
No one else<br />
Is such a beautiful dream, a beautiful dream<br />
No one else<br />
Is such a beautiful dream, a beautiful dream to me<br />
Such a beautiful dream, a beautiful dream<br />
Such a beautiful dream, a beautiful dream to me<br /></p>

<hr />

<h2 id="we-are-the-champions---queen">We Are the Champions - Queen</h2>

<p>[Verse 1]<br />
I’ve paid my dues<br />
Time after time<br />
I’ve done my sentence<br />
But committed no crime<br />
And bad mistakes<br />
I’ve made a few<br /></p>

<p>[Pre-Chorus]<br />
I’ve had my share of sand kicked in my face<br />
But I’ve come through (And I mean to go on and on, and on, and on)<br /></p>

<p>[Chorus]<br />
We are the champions, my friends<br />
And we’ll keep on fighting till the end<br />
We are the champions<br />
We are the champions<br />
No time for losers<br />
‘Cause we are the champions<br />
Of the world<br /></p>

<p>[Verse 2]<br />
I’ve taken my bows<br />
And my curtain calls<br />
You brought me fame and fortune and everything that goes with it<br />
I thank you all<br />
But it’s been no bed of roses<br />
No pleasure cruise<br /></p>

<p>[Pre-Chorus]<br />
I consider it a challenge before the whole human race<br />
And I ain’t gonna lose (And I mean to go on and on, and on, and on)<br /></p>

<p>[Chorus]<br />
We are the champions, my friends<br />
And we’ll keep on fighting till the end<br />
We are the champions<br />
We are the champions<br />
No time for losers<br />
‘Cause we are the champions<br />
Of the world<br /></p>

<p>[Outro]<br />
We are the champions, my friends<br />
And we’ll keep on fighting till the end, oh<br />
We are the champions<br />
We are the champions<br />
No time for losers<br />
‘Cause we are the champions<br /></p>

<hr />

<h2 id="hunter---galantis">Hunter - Galantis</h2>

<p>[Intro: Hannah Wilson]<br />
Mm-mm-mm<br /></p>

<p>[Chorus: Hannah Wilson]<br />
I am the hunter, I am the great unknown<br />
Only my love can conquer<br />
I am the, I am the hunter (I am the hunter)<br />
I am the hunter, into the wild, we go<br />
Give up your heart, surrender<br />
‘Cause I am the, I am the hunter (I am the—hey)<br /></p>

<p>[Verse 1: Hannah Wilson]<br />
We’ve been on this road<br />
To a place that, one day, we’ll know<br />
Adventure to the other side (I am the, I am the)<br />
Searching high and low for the treasure deep in your soul<br />
The fortune teller’s always right<br /></p>

<p>[Pre-Chorus: Hannah Wilson]<br />
Got them red eyes in the night<br />
Like a panther, outta sight<br />
Gonna sing my battle cry<br />
‘Cause I am the, I am the, I am the<br /></p>

<p>[Chorus: Hannah Wilson]<br />
I am the hunter, I am the great unknown<br />
Only my love can conquer<br />
I am the, I am the hunter (I am the hunter)<br />
I am the hunter, into the wild, we go<br />
Give up your heart, surrender<br />
‘Cause I am the, I am the hunter (I am the—hey)<br /></p>

<p>[Post-Chorus: Hannah Wilson]<br />
I am the (Mm-mm-mm)<br />
I am the (Mm-mm-mm, hey)<br />
I am the, I am the (Mm-mm-mm)<br />
I am the (Mm-mm-mm)<br />
I am the, I am the, I am the—<br /></p>

<p>[Verse 2: Hannah Wilson]<br />
Strangers wild and free<br />
Through the flames, you’re all that I see<br />
A force you, that you can’t deny (I am the, I am the)<br />
Hear my calling<br />
Lock and load, come running to me<br />
Dancing through the midnight (I am the, I am the)<br /></p>

<p>[Pre-Chorus: Hannah Wilson]<br />
Got them red eyes in the night<br />
Like a panther, outta sight<br />
Gonna sing my battle cry<br />
‘Cause I am the, I am the, I am the<br /></p>

<p>[Chorus: Hannah Wilson]<br />
I am the hunter, I am the great unknown<br />
Only my love can conquer<br />
I am the, I am the hunter (I am the hunter)<br />
I am the hunter, into the wild, we go<br />
Give up your heart, surrender<br />
‘Cause I am the, I am the hunter (I am the—hey)<br /></p>

<p>[Post-Chorus: Hannah Wilson]<br />
I am the (Mm-mm-mm)<br />
I am the (Mm-mm-mm, hey)<br />
I am the, I am the (Mm-mm-mm)<br />
I am the (Mm-mm-mm)<br /></p>

<p>[Outro: Hannah Wilson]<br />
I am the, I am the, I am the<br />
I am the, I am the, I am the hunt-<br />
I am the, I am the, I am the<br />
I am-I am, I am-I am, I am-I am<br />
Hunter<br /></p>

<hr />

<p><img src="/HFzAW3TKrW8DnZERUC.jpg" alt="Daddy Cool" /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I launched another round of extra-potent salt sprinkling on 100,000+ Assyrians earlier today and fell asleep on my chair again. I felt better after catching some sleep and pulling the Lord knows how many consecutive all-nighters in recent weeks. I have never worked this hard in my entire life, and to my massive annoyance, I’m not getting paid, but I’m also unable to stop. Life stopped making sense after I took that leap of faith in China less than five months ago. Feel free to reach out if you know because I don’t. Thanks.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Revelation 13</title><link href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-revelation-13/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Revelation 13" /><published>2025-02-26T16:16:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-04T14:51:05+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/posts/on-revelation-13</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-revelation-13/"><![CDATA[<p style="font-size: 27px;"><b>Firstly, I just want to say what a King of Kings and King of Drama.</b></p>

<p>Halfway through my bitching in a recent post, I found myself reading the interpretation of Revelation 13 on BibleRef and I got struck by lightning once again when I read the following.</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="revelation-1318">Revelation 13:18</h2>

<p>[18] This calls for wisdom: let the one who has understanding calculate the number of the beast, for it is the number of a man, and his number is 666. (ESV)</p>

<h2 id="what-does-revelation-1318-mean"><a href="https://www.bibleref.com/Revelation/13/Revelation-13-18.html" target="_blank">What does Revelation 13:18 mean?</a></h2>

<p>Other possibilities abound. Some are more obscure, and unlikely, than others. Ezra 2:13 gives the number of descendants of Adonikam as 666. Because “Adonikam” means “the lord who rises up” or “lord of the enemy,” a few interpreters suggest the beast who rises from the earth will bear the name Adonikam. The mathematical value of 6x6x6 is 216, leading some to believe that this number, not “six hundred and sixty six” will be the “number of the name” of the beast.</p>

<p>In reality, no one knows exactly what 666 means. We can only draw on basic concepts to understand some of its implications. For example, 6 is one short of 7, which is the biblical number of perfection. The number 6 represents imperfection and is therefore man’s number. God is perfectly holy—thrice holy—as the seraphim of Isaiah’s vision proclaim. They called to one another, “Holy, holy, holy is the LORD of hosts” (Isaiah 6:3). Repeating this three times emphasizes its absolute nature. By contrast, imperfect man is unholy, unholy, unholy: 6-6-6.</p>

<h2 id="ezra-213">Ezra 2:13</h2>

<p>[13] The sons of Adonikam, 666. (ESV)</p>

<h2 id="adonikam---wikipedia"><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_minor_Hebrew_Bible_figures,_A%E2%80%93K#Adonikam" target="_blank">Adonikam - Wikipedia</a></h2>

<p>Adonikam (Hebrew אֲדֹנִיקָם, meaning, “My Lord is risen up.”[57]) is a Biblical figure, one of those “which came with Zerubbabel” (Ezra 2:13). His “children,” or retainers, numbering 666, came to Jerusalem (Ezra 8:13). In the Septuagint, depending on the manuscript and location, the name is given as Adon[e]ikam, Adonikan, Adeikam, Adenikam, Adaneikam or Adoniakaim.[57] In Nehemiah 7:18, his descendants were 667 instead of the previous number 666.[58]</p>

<embed src="https://dl.hesaid.love/Meaning_of_Onik_in_Adonikam.pdf" type="application/pdf" width="100%" height="600px" />

<h2 id="1-corinthians-13813">1 Corinthians 13:8–13</h2>

<p>[8] Love never ends. As for prophecies, they will pass away; as for tongues, they will cease; as for knowledge, it will pass away. [9] For we know in part and we prophesy in part, [10] but when the perfect comes, the partial will pass away. [11] When I was a child, I spoke like a child, I thought like a child, I reasoned like a child. When I became a man, I gave up childish ways. [12] For now we see in a mirror dimly, but then face to face. Now I know in part; then I shall know fully, even as I have been fully known.</p>

<p>[13] So now faith, hope, and love abide, these three; but the greatest of these is love. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>This is how I read the sentence.</p>

<p>Ezra 2:13 gives the number of <strong>descendants of Adonikam</strong> as 666.</p>

<p>Hence, 666 could be the number of humanity, the unholy, unholy, unholy imperfect man, who could also be the abomination of desolation standing in the holy place proclaiming there is no God, which is essentially proclaiming himself to be God.</p>

<p>I caught some false teachers smuggling stinky <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Humanism" target="_blank">humanism</a> by only focusing on the soft stuff in the New Testament, which breaks the third commandment and blasphemies against God.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>Starting in the 20th century, some humanist movements are non-religious and aligned with secularism. Most frequently in contemporary usage, humanism refers to a non-theistic view centered on human agency, and a reliance only on science and reason rather than revelation from a divine source to understand the world. A non-theistic humanist worldview asserts that religion is not a precondition of morality, and objects to excessive religious entanglement with education and the state.</p>

  <p>Humanism - Wikipedia</p>
</blockquote>

<p>I discussed in <a href="../on-genesis-3-fall-man/" target="_blank">a previous post</a> something the crafty serpent gave the woman that she did not have before, which led to the fall of man in Genesis 3. That thing was <strong>doubt</strong> and I read Revelation 13 again substituting the dragon with <strong>doubt</strong>.</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="revelation-13110">Revelation 13:1–10</h2>

<p>The First Beast</p>

<p>[1] And I saw a beast rising out of the sea, with ten horns and seven heads, with ten diadems on its horns and blasphemous names on its heads. [2] And the beast that I saw was like a leopard; its feet were like a bear’s, and its mouth was like a lion’s mouth. And to it the dragon gave his power and his throne and great authority. [3] One of its heads seemed to have a mortal wound, but its mortal wound was healed, and the whole earth marveled as they followed the beast. [4] And they worshiped the dragon, for he had given his authority to the beast, and they worshiped the beast, saying, “Who is like the beast, and who can fight against it?”</p>

<p>[5] And the beast was given a mouth uttering haughty and blasphemous words, and it was allowed to exercise authority for forty-two months. [6] It opened its mouth to utter blasphemies against God, blaspheming his name and his dwelling, that is, those who dwell in heaven. [7] Also it was allowed to make war on the saints and to conquer them. And authority was given it over every tribe and people and language and nation, [8] and all who dwell on earth will worship it, everyone whose name has not been written from the foundation of the world in the book of life of the Lamb who was slain. [9] If anyone has an ear, let him hear:</p>

<p>[10] If anyone is to be taken captive,<br />
  to captivity he goes;<br />
 if anyone is to be slain with the sword,<br />
  with the sword must he be slain.<br /></p>

<p>Here is a call for the endurance and faith of the saints. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>I’m way too lazy to work out everything myself and my to-do list is barely going down at the moment. Feel free to have a go at it yourself, but here is where the 27 years of my previous life come in. The <a href="../on-sheep-and-goats/" target="_blank">ethical thought experiment</a> I designed during COVID-19 came true last year, which involved an Austrian artist, a time machine, nuclear weapons, humanity and divine intervention. I asked ChatGPT about the symbolism of the sea in the Holy Bible, and put down humanity and/or reason/science for the first beast. The mortal wound was World War II and/or physics.</p>

<embed src="https://dl.hesaid.love/symbolism_of_the_sea.pdf" type="application/pdf" width="100%" height="600px" />

<p><img src="/vDxArBCrKmpZmHt4y0.jpg" alt="Now I am become Death, the destroyer of worlds" /></p>

<h2 id="recommended-reading-list">Recommended Reading List</h2>

<p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Liberal_arts_education" target="_blank">Seven liberal arts</a> and <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Liberal_arts_education#Modern_usage" target="_blank">ten mathematical and natural sciences</a>, legacy of <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Classical_antiquity" target="_blank">classical antiquity</a>.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>The seven subjects in the ancient and medieval meaning came to be divided into the trivium of rhetoric, grammar, and logic, and the quadrivium of astronomy, arithmetic, geometry, and music.</p>

  <p>Life science (biology, neuroscience)<br />
Physical science (physics, astronomy, physical geography, chemistry, earth science)<br />
Formal science (logic, mathematics, statistics)<br /></p>

  <p>Liberal arts education - Wikipedia</p>
</blockquote>

<h3 id="second-half-of-the-tribulation---setting-up-the-abomination-of-desolation">Second half of the tribulation - Setting up the abomination of desolation</h3>

<p><a href="https://unesdoc.unesco.org/ark:/48223/pf0000122938" target="_blank">Science for the twenty-first century: a new commitment</a>
📥 <a href="https://dl.hesaid.love/122938engo.pdf" target="_blank">Download (Backup)</a></p>

<p><a href="https://unesdoc.unesco.org/ark:/48223/pf0000141952" target="_blank">World Declaration on Higher Education for the Twenty-first Century: Vision and Action and Framework for Priority Action for Change and Development in Higher Education, adopted by the World Conference on Higher Education: Higher Education in the Twenty-first Century, Vision and Action, 9 October 1998</a>
📥 <a href="https://dl.hesaid.love/141952eng.pdf" target="_blank">Download (Backup)</a></p>

<h3 id="first-half-of-the-tribulation-maybe">First half of the tribulation (maybe)</h3>

<p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_International_Economic_Order" target="_blank">New International Economic Order (NIEO)</a></p>

<p><a href="https://digitallibrary.un.org/record/218450?v=pdf" target="_blank">Declaration on the Establishment of a New International Economic Order.</a>
📥 <a href="https://dl.hesaid.love/A_RES_3201(S-VI)-EN.pdf" target="_blank">Download (Backup)</a></p>

<p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Helsinki_Accords" target="_blank">Helsinki Accords</a></p>

<h2 id="apology">Apology</h2>

<p>My sincere apologies to <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Prince_Hassan_bin_Talal" target="_blank">Prince Hassan bin Talal of Jordan</a>, a fellow pretentious Oxford alumnus who studied Oriental Studies at Christ Church College, Oxford. I must pay tribute to his dedication to advancing the global scientific agenda given his humble educational background in humanities and as a descendant of a well-known historical figure whose name I was unable to locate in my favourite bestseller. I did not expect the royal family of Jordan to be that actively involved in various international scientific organisations and UNESCO.</p>

<p>I learned something rather interesting when doing my due diligence which turned out to be rather embarrassingly insufficient. The Jordanian royal family has been the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hashemite_custodianship_of_Jerusalem_holy_sites" target="_blank">custodian of the Christian holy sites</a> in the city of Jerusalem since 1924. I visited the Church of the Holy Sepulchre last month.</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="1-john-218">1 John 2:18</h2>

<p>Warning Concerning Antichrists</p>

<p>[18] Children, it is the last hour, and as you have heard that antichrist is coming, so now many antichrists have come. Therefore we know that it is the last hour. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="revelation-131118">Revelation 13:11–18</h2>

<p>The Second Beast</p>

<p>[11] Then I saw another beast rising out of the earth. It had two horns like a lamb and it spoke like a dragon. [12] It exercises all the authority of the first beast in its presence, and makes the earth and its inhabitants worship the first beast, whose mortal wound was healed. [13] It performs great signs, even making fire come down from heaven to earth in front of people, [14] and by the signs that it is allowed to work in the presence of the beast it deceives those who dwell on earth, telling them to make an image for the beast that was wounded by the sword and yet lived. [15] And it was allowed to give breath to the image of the beast, so that the image of the beast might even speak and might cause those who would not worship the image of the beast to be slain. [16] Also it causes all, both small and great, both rich and poor, both free and slave, to be marked on the right hand or the forehead, [17] so that no one can buy or sell unless he has the mark, that is, the name of the beast or the number of its name. [18] This calls for wisdom: let the one who has understanding calculate the number of the beast, for it is the number of a man, and his number is 666. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>I put down technology/internet as the second beast. The beast spoke like a dragon (doubt) indeed. I was <a href="../on-going-home/" target="_blank">informed by an Israeli border officer last month</a> that the second beast performed great signs just the night before and made fire come down from heaven to earth in front of people. I was quite willing to walk into a special delivery from the second beast during my trip due to how faithful my “friends” had been.</p>

<p>I put down humanity/humanism/self and/or <a href="../on-drug-money-addiction/" target="_blank">drugs (money)</a> for the image of the beast. People kept telling me to think about myself first during my recent rollercoaster ride of six months, and less than a dozen people bought me coffee. It seems like most only think about me, myself and I all day and are extremely occupied with taking and posting selfies on Instagram or whatever trendy Web3 social media bullshit the crypto/tech bros are up to nowadays. I also learned that I’m one of those extremely rare idiots who do not worship themselves, consider themselves to be of the utmost importance in the head, nor consider themselves righteous all the time. No wonder I’m bankrupt and rent is 4.5 months overdue right now despite making mid-six-figures less than a year ago. I certainly cannot buy or sell right now. I have started my adult live-stream webcam career for a couple of weeks now. I’m still below the withdrawal minimum on Chaturbate and Stripchat due to my unwillingness to do private shows and my insistence on goodwill-only income, despite literally working my ass off and giving my best every single stream. It’s honestly extremely difficult to earn an honest living nowadays, probably not a path you want to go down if you consider yourself “wise”.</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="2-timothy-319">2 Timothy 3:1–9</h2>

<p>Godlessness in the Last Days</p>

<p>[1] But understand this, that in the last days there will come times of difficulty. [2] For people will be lovers of self, lovers of money, proud, arrogant, abusive, disobedient to their parents, ungrateful, unholy, [3] heartless, unappeasable, slanderous, without self-control, brutal, not loving good, [4] treacherous, reckless, swollen with conceit, lovers of pleasure rather than lovers of God, [5] having the appearance of godliness, but denying its power. Avoid such people. [6] For among them are those who creep into households and capture weak women, burdened with sins and led astray by various passions, [7] always learning and never able to arrive at a knowledge of the truth. [8] Just as Jannes and Jambres opposed Moses, so these men also oppose the truth, men corrupted in mind and disqualified regarding the faith. [9] But they will not get very far, for their folly will be plain to all, as was that of those two men. (ESV)</p>

<h2 id="2-thessalonians-2112">2 Thessalonians 2:1–12</h2>

<p>The Man of Lawlessness</p>

<p>[1] Now concerning the coming of our Lord Jesus Christ and our being gathered together to him, we ask you, brothers, [2] not to be quickly shaken in mind or alarmed, either by a spirit or a spoken word, or a letter seeming to be from us, to the effect that the day of the Lord has come. [3] Let no one deceive you in any way. For that day will not come, unless the rebellion comes first, and the man of lawlessness is revealed, the son of destruction, [4] who opposes and exalts himself against every so-called god or object of worship, so that he takes his seat in the temple of God, proclaiming himself to be God. [5] Do you not remember that when I was still with you I told you these things? [6] And you know what is restraining him now so that he may be revealed in his time. [7] For the mystery of lawlessness is already at work. Only he who now restrains it will do so until he is out of the way. [8] And then the lawless one will be revealed, whom the Lord Jesus will kill with the breath of his mouth and bring to nothing by the appearance of his coming. [9] The coming of the lawless one is by the activity of Satan with all power and false signs and wonders, [10] and with all wicked deception for those who are perishing, because they refused to love the truth and so be saved. [11] Therefore God sends them a strong delusion, so that they may believe what is false, [12] in order that all may be condemned who did not believe the truth but had pleasure in unrighteousness. (ESV)</p>

<h2 id="jude-1723">Jude 17–23</h2>

<p>A Call to Persevere</p>

<p>[17] But you must remember, beloved, the predictions of the apostles of our Lord Jesus Christ. [18] They said to you, “In the last time there will be scoffers, following their own ungodly passions.” [19] It is these who cause divisions, worldly people, devoid of the Spirit. [20] But you, beloved, building yourselves up in your most holy faith and praying in the Holy Spirit, [21] keep yourselves in the love of God, waiting for the mercy of our Lord Jesus Christ that leads to eternal life. [22] And have mercy on those who doubt; [23] save others by snatching them out of the fire; to others show mercy with fear, hating even the garment stained by the flesh. (ESV)</p>

<h2 id="psalm-4810">Psalm 48:10</h2>

<p>[10] As your name, O God,
  so your praise reaches to the ends of the earth.
 Your right hand is filled with righteousness. (ESV)</p>

<h2 id="matthew-2533">Matthew 25:33</h2>

<p>[33] And he will place the sheep on his right, but the goats on the left. (ESV)</p>

<h2 id="matthew-71214">Matthew 7:12–14</h2>

<p>The Golden Rule</p>

<p>[12] “So whatever you wish that others would do to you, do also to them, for this is the Law and the Prophets.</p>

<p>[13] “Enter by the narrow gate. For the gate is wide and the way is easy that leads to destruction, and those who enter by it are many. [14] For the gate is narrow and the way is hard that leads to life, and those who find it are few. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>The descendants of Adonikam are 667 as counted in Nehemiah 7:18 instead of 666 in Ezra 2:13. You can read about my little chitchat with ChatGPT below. I noticed at least one error where ChatGPT confused the counts as 667 in Ezra 2:13 and 666 in Nehemiah 7:18.</p>

<embed src="https://dl.hesaid.love/chitchat_666_667_chatgpt.pdf" type="application/pdf" width="100%" height="600px" />

<p>Given we are in an intellectual, spiritual, moral and ethical decay where a Christian informed me yesterday that trying to save other people is a sign of pride, I have decided to follow Boss Man regardless of what the antichrists pretending to be Christians say. Although, I kinda realised I had been following Him all my life even in the 27 years of my previous life. The only thing is I did not know His name, but I did know His other glorious name - Truth. I learned 157 days ago that His name is Jesus Christ, my Lord and Saviour.</p>

<p>Boss Man gave me a list containing 113,119 Assyrian camps yesterday. I have got some nations to sprinkle and startle, as well as proclaiming the gospel of the kingdom throughout the whole world as a testimony to all nations.</p>

<p>I have been telling the devil and Satan to piss off and leave me alone in the name of my Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ since my welcoming party taught me at the beginning of this journey less than 6 months ago. I think he might have finally fucked off now. 🤞</p>

<p>I don’t doubt. I believe.</p>

<p>See ya.</p>

<p>Edit: surprise, surprise, totally did not expect the first jobs <a href="https://letter.hesaid.love" target="_blank">AI would take away</a> are pastors and theologians. 😅</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="matthew-1230">Matthew 12:30</h2>

<p>[30] Whoever is not with me is against me, and whoever does not gather with me scatters. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<embed src="https://dl.hesaid.love/Man_of_Lawlessness_Bible_Summary.pdf" type="application/pdf" width="100%" height="600px" />

<p><img src="/E5sHTxyHTXDA43nCHZ.gif" alt="Fuck off, Satan" /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Firstly, I just want to say what a King of Kings and King of Drama.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://hesaid.love/E5sHTxyHTXDA43nCHZ.gif" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://hesaid.love/E5sHTxyHTXDA43nCHZ.gif" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">On Messiah(s)</title><link href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-messiahs/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Messiah(s)" /><published>2025-02-26T06:52:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-02-26T12:39:31+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/posts/on-messiahs</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-messiahs/"><![CDATA[<p>Yesterday was the second time someone told me that trying to save other people is a sign of pride. They also kindly informed me that I’m an egomaniac who believes that I might be a chosen one. Unlike the first time, it was slightly better this time since it came from a Christian. Although, does that make it worse? I don’t know. I’m not sure I know how to spell good and evil anymore. Let me know if you know how to spell good and evil. Thanks.</p>

<p>Allegedly Christians like to ask the question what would Jesus do when facing ethical and moral choices, evidently it’s called discipleship otherwise known as following Jesus. I would like to reiterate my position once again and make another apology in advance for the language I’m about to use since I noticed that no mother fucker tries to learn what happened first before opening their mouths and informing me of their fucking opinions. I had zero mother fucking desire to be the fucking messiah and I still have zero mother fucking desire to be the messiah. I don’t know if I’m the fucking messiah, and you are more than fucking welcome to inform me about your fucking opinion after you learned what happened. I wrote them all down.</p>

<p>It’s been 157 days since I believed, and throughout this journey, I realised the m-word is a big no-no to mention to believers. And you would automatically receive the labels including but not limited to egomaniac, megalomaniac and narcissist. I couldn’t help but find it both ironic and sarcastic that Christians have been hoping for the second coming for over 2,000 years now and the immediate reaction they have when some random dude wants to show them evidence is to refer them to mental health services without bothering with glancing the evidence served up on a platter, despite the dude’s only wish is to find out why life became magic and why people lost reasoning capabilities overnight. Frankly, speaking from the perspective of a rampant homosexual who has more sexual partners in an hour every other day than the average heterosexual will have in their entire life, I kinda feel bad for Boss Man given the stigma and discrimination attached to His job title. He did have a pretty rough time and went on a sabbatical not long after a pretty bad workplace injury. I will check with Him next time we speak to see how’s that lawsuit preparation going and when He will be done with His career break. I’m pretty sure Dude’s a worse procrastinator than me.</p>

<p>I kinda asked Him for some stupid stuff when I first learned how to pray including but not limited to letting me suffer and save some random people including but not limited to rampant homosexuals. Whether or not He will allow me to, I don’t know. I trust Him and I did not trust myself even once in my entire life. He does tell me to stop working and go chill the fuck out somewhat regularly. The health insurance is pretty good with this Boss, and I heard a Colleague got injured three years into the job and Dude is still chilling on paid leave after 2,000 years. My former life ambition was to build an interesting tech startup and ideally work up to a net worth of 10-50 mil so that I could study and explore any extremely random interest that I somehow magically come up with every 3 to 6 months, and could still be in t-shirt and jeans without anyone bothering me. I was definitely on track with that with a mid-six-figure income at 27, then I tried to take my first holiday and you are reading about the ongoing nuclear fallout. I’m gonna work my ass off, both literally and figuratively, and see if I can also go on a sabbatical for something like forever and ever.</p>

<p>Feel free to get in touch after you find out about the m-word thing. To be honest, given how successfully we managed to fuck this up, I think the singular m-word might not be enough, and we might be able to unfuck this quicker if we start using the plural form. But it took decades for my community, some of whom are rampant homosexuals like me who enjoy getting fucked in the ass by talented Germans in FickstutenMarkt for 4hrs+ non-stop whilst listening to sick Berlin techno, to fight for our rights to be equal citizens of society, and we still face discrimination today. Statistically speaking, I think the m-word community will have a significantly harder time, but speaking from first-hand personal experience, statistics is a synonym for null in their dictionary. Big Man does not play dice with His creation.</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="matthew-2422">Matthew 24:22</h2>

<p>[22] And if those days had not been cut short, no human being would be saved. But for the sake of the elect those days will be cut short. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="matthew-241522">Matthew 24:15–22</h2>

<p>The Abomination of Desolation</p>

<p>[15] “So when you see the abomination of desolation spoken of by the prophet Daniel, standing in the holy place (let the reader understand), [16] then let those who are in Judea flee to the mountains. [17] Let the one who is on the housetop not go down to take what is in his house, [18] and let the one who is in the field not turn back to take his cloak. [19] And alas for women who are pregnant and for those who are nursing infants in those days! [20] Pray that your flight may not be in winter or on a Sabbath. [21] For then there will be great tribulation, such as has not been from the beginning of the world until now, no, and never will be. [22] And if those days had not been cut short, no human being would be saved. But for the sake of the elect those days will be cut short. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="matthew-127">Matthew 12:7</h2>

<p>[7] And if you had known what this means, ‘I desire mercy, and not sacrifice,’ you would not have condemned the guiltless. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="matthew-9913">Matthew 9:9–13</h2>

<p>Jesus Calls Matthew</p>

<p>[9] As Jesus passed on from there, he saw a man called Matthew sitting at the tax booth, and he said to him, “Follow me.” And he rose and followed him.</p>

<p>[10] And as Jesus reclined at table in the house, behold, many tax collectors and sinners came and were reclining with Jesus and his disciples. [11] And when the Pharisees saw this, they said to his disciples, “Why does your teacher eat with tax collectors and sinners?” [12] But when he heard it, he said, “Those who are well have no need of a physician, but those who are sick. [13] Go and learn what this means: ‘I desire mercy, and not sacrifice.’ For I came not to call the righteous, but sinners.” (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="matthew-715">Matthew 7:1–5</h2>

<p>Judging Others</p>

<p>[1] “Judge not, that you be not judged. [2] For with the judgment you pronounce you will be judged, and with the measure you use it will be measured to you. [3] Why do you see the speck that is in your brother’s eye, but do not notice the log that is in your own eye? [4] Or how can you say to your brother, ‘Let me take the speck out of your eye,’ when there is the log in your own eye? [5] You hypocrite, first take the log out of your own eye, and then you will see clearly to take the speck out of your brother’s eye. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="luke-121314">Luke 12:13–14</h2>

<p>The Parable of the Rich Fool</p>

<p>[13] Someone in the crowd said to him, “Teacher, tell my brother to divide the inheritance with me.” [14] But he said to him, “Man, who made me a judge or arbitrator over you?” (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="hosea-6">Hosea 6</h2>

<p>Israel and Judah Are Unrepentant</p>

<p>[1] “Come, let us return to the LORD;<br />
  for he has torn us, that he may heal us;<br />
  he has struck us down, and he will bind us up.<br />
 [2] After two days he will revive us;<br />
  on the third day he will raise us up,<br />
  that we may live before him.<br />
 [3] Let us know; let us press on to know the LORD;<br />
  his going out is sure as the dawn;<br />
 he will come to us as the showers,<br />
  as the spring rains that water the earth.”<br /></p>

<p>[4] What shall I do with you, O Ephraim?<br />
  What shall I do with you, O Judah?<br />
 Your love is like a morning cloud,<br />
  like the dew that goes early away.<br />
 [5] Therefore I have hewn them by the prophets;<br />
  I have slain them by the words of my mouth,<br />
  and my judgment goes forth as the light.<br />
 [6] For I desire steadfast love and not sacrifice,<br />
  the knowledge of God rather than burnt offerings.<br /></p>

<p>[7] But like Adam they transgressed the covenant;<br />
  there they dealt faithlessly with me.<br />
 [8] Gilead is a city of evildoers,<br />
  tracked with blood.<br />
 [9] As robbers lie in wait for a man,<br />
  so the priests band together;<br />
 they murder on the way to Shechem;<br />
  they commit villainy.<br />
 [10] In the house of Israel I have seen a horrible thing;<br />
  Ephraim’s whoredom is there; Israel is defiled.<br /></p>

<p>[11] For you also, O Judah, a harvest is appointed.<br /></p>

<p>When I restore the fortunes of my people, (ESV)<br /></p>

<hr />

<h2 id="genesis-182233">Genesis 18:22–33</h2>

<p>Abraham Intercedes for Sodom</p>

<p>[22] So the men turned from there and went toward Sodom, but Abraham still stood before the LORD. [23] Then Abraham drew near and said, “Will you indeed sweep away the righteous with the wicked? [24] Suppose there are fifty righteous within the city. Will you then sweep away the place and not spare it for the fifty righteous who are in it? [25] Far be it from you to do such a thing, to put the righteous to death with the wicked, so that the righteous fare as the wicked! Far be that from you! Shall not the Judge of all the earth do what is just?” [26] And the LORD said, “If I find at Sodom fifty righteous in the city, I will spare the whole place for their sake.”</p>

<p>[27] Abraham answered and said, “Behold, I have undertaken to speak to the Lord, I who am but dust and ashes. [28] Suppose five of the fifty righteous are lacking. Will you destroy the whole city for lack of five?” And he said, “I will not destroy it if I find forty-five there.” [29] Again he spoke to him and said, “Suppose forty are found there.” He answered, “For the sake of forty I will not do it.” [30] Then he said, “Oh let not the Lord be angry, and I will speak. Suppose thirty are found there.” He answered, “I will not do it, if I find thirty there.” [31] He said, “Behold, I have undertaken to speak to the Lord. Suppose twenty are found there.” He answered, “For the sake of twenty I will not destroy it.” [32] Then he said, “Oh let not the Lord be angry, and I will speak again but this once. Suppose ten are found there.” He answered, “For the sake of ten I will not destroy it.” [33] And the LORD went his way, when he had finished speaking to Abraham, and Abraham returned to his place. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="ezekiel-222931">Ezekiel 22:29–31</h2>

<p>[29] The people of the land have practiced extortion and committed robbery. They have oppressed the poor and needy, and have extorted from the sojourner without justice. [30] And I sought for a man among them who should build up the wall and stand in the breach before me for the land, that I should not destroy it, but I found none. [31] Therefore I have poured out my indignation upon them. I have consumed them with the fire of my wrath. I have returned their way upon their heads, declares the Lord GOD.” (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="jeremiah-515">Jeremiah 5:1–5</h2>

<p>Jerusalem Refused to Repent</p>

<p>[1] Run to and fro through the streets of Jerusalem,<br />
  look and take note!<br />
 Search her squares to see<br />
  if you can find a man,<br />
 one who does justice<br />
  and seeks truth,<br />
 that I may pardon her.<br />
 [2] Though they say, “As the LORD lives,”<br />
  yet they swear falsely.<br />
 [3] O LORD, do not your eyes look for truth?<br />
 You have struck them down,<br />
  but they felt no anguish;<br />
 you have consumed them,<br />
  but they refused to take correction.<br />
 They have made their faces harder than rock;<br />
  they have refused to repent.<br /></p>

<p>[4] Then I said, “These are only the poor;<br />
  they have no sense;<br />
 for they do not know the way of the LORD,<br />
  the justice of their God.<br />
 [5] I will go to the great<br />
  and will speak to them,<br />
 for they know the way of the LORD,<br />
  the justice of their God.”<br />
 But they all alike had broken the yoke;<br />
  they had burst the bonds. (ESV)<br /></p>

<hr />

<h2 id="isaiah-591417">Isaiah 59:14–17</h2>

<p>Judgment and Redemption</p>

<p>[14] Justice is turned back,<br />
  and righteousness stands far away;<br />
 for truth has stumbled in the public squares,<br />
  and uprightness cannot enter.<br />
 [15] Truth is lacking,<br />
  and he who departs from evil makes himself a prey.<br /></p>

<p>The LORD saw it, and it displeased him<br />
  that there was no justice.<br />
 [16] He saw that there was no man,<br />
  and wondered that there was no one to intercede;<br />
 then his own arm brought him salvation,<br />
  and his righteousness upheld him.<br />
 [17] He put on righteousness as a breastplate,<br />
  and a helmet of salvation on his head;<br />
 he put on garments of vengeance for clothing,<br />
  and wrapped himself in zeal as a cloak. (ESV)<br /></p>

<hr />

<p><img src="/rC2HGNNWR3JzrY4ngY.jpg" alt="Father forgive them, for I literally can't even" /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday was the second time someone told me that trying to save other people is a sign of pride. They also kindly informed me that I’m an egomaniac who believes that I might be a chosen one. Unlike the first time, it was slightly better this time since it came from a Christian. Although, does that make it worse? I don’t know. I’m not sure I know how to spell good and evil anymore. Let me know if you know how to spell good and evil. Thanks.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Love</title><link href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-love/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Love" /><published>2025-02-24T23:26:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-02-24T23:26:00+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/posts/on-love</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-love/"><![CDATA[<p>In the last couple of days, my Chinese missionary guide has stopped responding to my messages. Based on the sentiment of our latest messages, I can tell my welcoming party, which the Lord prepared for me in the UK 11.5 years ago, is starting to withdraw. I read the following passages from 2 Thessalonians yesterday.</p>

<hr />

<p>2 Thessalonians 2:1–12</p>

<p>The Man of Lawlessness</p>

<p>[1] Now concerning the coming of our Lord Jesus Christ and our being gathered together to him, we ask you, brothers, [2] not to be quickly shaken in mind or alarmed, either by a spirit or a spoken word, or a letter seeming to be from us, to the effect that the day of the Lord has come. [3] Let no one deceive you in any way. For that day will not come, unless the rebellion comes first, and the man of lawlessness is revealed, the son of destruction, [4] who opposes and exalts himself against every so-called god or object of worship, so that he takes his seat in the temple of God, proclaiming himself to be God. [5] Do you not remember that when I was still with you I told you these things? [6] And you know what is restraining him now so that he may be revealed in his time. [7] For the mystery of lawlessness is already at work. Only he who now restrains it will do so until he is out of the way. [8] And then the lawless one will be revealed, whom the Lord Jesus will kill with the breath of his mouth and bring to nothing by the appearance of his coming. [9] The coming of the lawless one is by the activity of Satan with all power and false signs and wonders, [10] and with all wicked deception for those who are perishing, because they refused to love the truth and so be saved. [11] Therefore God sends them a strong delusion, so that they may believe what is false, [12] in order that all may be condemned who did not believe the truth but had pleasure in unrighteousness. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>As alluded to multiple times in my previous posts, epistemologically there are only three things that I know. He exists, He loves me, and I exist, in that precise order of precedence. And before my welcoming party bashes me again for using pronouns, He is my Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ, whose last known appearance on earth was around 2,000 years ago. Besides that, everything else is a belief that can be subject to doubt and reasoning. I picture my knowledge system as a tree, and each new branch is rooted in one or more branches. Each branch has a variable belief probability that indicates my confidence when understanding the world through the fruits of that branch. My root branch was drifting in the sea of knowledge after reading Descartes’ <em>Meditations on First Philosophy</em> during COVID-19 and nearly got burnt in the fire that is existentialism, nihilism and antinatalism. Six months ago, He came and firmly attached my root to the vine that is my Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ.</p>

<p>After getting kicked out of the gay/bi-sexual naturist campsite Rosebay in late July last year, I felt His love for the first time when standing on Oxford Street in central London one evening. I checked my WhatsApp messages and Amazon order history. I placed the order for my first Holy Bible after that evening. I realised the reason why it hurt that much was because I loved everyone at the campsite and getting kicked out smashed my heart into pieces. And after picking a fight with nature for three months, I also loved nature and all the new interests and possibilities I started to explore. I asked myself how much I love and using the equation of love I derived at age 16, I realised I was willing to take a bullet for any stranger that was walking past me that evening. That was the precise moment I felt His love for the first time.</p>

<p>My welcoming party taught me quite early on that regardless of what I do with the Holy Spirit and spiritual gifts, I should do it with love, faith and hope, and love always comes first. In case there is any doubt, the equation of love is the greatest amount of sacrifice one is willing to make.</p>

<p>I have been searching my heart and soul ever since getting kicked out of Rosebay. Despite my entire world turning on me in my early teenage years, Rosebay and now, I believe I gave more than I took in this life. The only other possibility that I can think of is I have successfully deceived myself, in which case I deserve burning in hell for eternity and I will accept any judgment He has for me regardless. I will leave judgement to Him, it’s too heavy a task for a mere servant like me and I’m just gonna get the homecoming party ready.</p>

<p>I will see you at sunrise.</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="hebrews-1113">Hebrews 11:1–3</h2>

<p>By Faith</p>

<p>[1] Now faith is the assurance of things hoped for, the conviction of things not seen. [2] For by it the people of old received their commendation. [3] By faith we understand that the universe was created by the word of God, so that what is seen was not made out of things that are visible. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="romans-11617">Romans 1:16–17</h2>

<p>The Righteous Shall Live by Faith</p>

<p>[16] For I am not ashamed of the gospel, for it is the power of God for salvation to everyone who believes, to the Jew first and also to the Greek. [17] For in it the righteousness of God is revealed from faith for faith, as it is written, “The righteous shall live by faith.” (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="galatians-216">Galatians 2:16</h2>

<p>[16] yet we know that a person is not justified by works of the law but through faith in Jesus Christ, so we also have believed in Christ Jesus, in order to be justified by faith in Christ and not by works of the law, because by works of the law no one will be justified. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="mark-112025">Mark 11:20–25</h2>

<p>The Lesson from the Withered Fig Tree</p>

<p>[20] As they passed by in the morning, they saw the fig tree withered away to its roots. [21] And Peter remembered and said to him, “Rabbi, look! The fig tree that you cursed has withered.” [22] And Jesus answered them, “Have faith in God. [23] Truly, I say to you, whoever says to this mountain, ‘Be taken up and thrown into the sea,’ and does not doubt in his heart, but believes that what he says will come to pass, it will be done for him. [24] Therefore I tell you, whatever you ask in prayer, believe that you have received it, and it will be yours. [25] And whenever you stand praying, forgive, if you have anything against anyone, so that your Father also who is in heaven may forgive you your trespasses.” (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="matthew-171920">Matthew 17:19–20</h2>

<p>[19] Then the disciples came to Jesus privately and said, “Why could we not cast it out?” [20] He said to them, “Because of your little faith. For truly, I say to you, if you have faith like a grain of mustard seed, you will say to this mountain, ‘Move from here to there,’ and it will move, and nothing will be impossible for you.” (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="2-corinthians-5610">2 Corinthians 5:6–10</h2>

<p>[6] So we are always of good courage. We know that while we are at home in the body we are away from the Lord, [7] for we walk by faith, not by sight. [8] Yes, we are of good courage, and we would rather be away from the body and at home with the Lord. [9] So whether we are at home or away, we make it our aim to please him. [10] For we must all appear before the judgment seat of Christ, so that each one may receive what is due for what he has done in the body, whether good or evil. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="glorious---song-by-macklemore"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7OrLroFa0AI" target="_blank">Glorious - Song by Macklemore</a></h2>

<p>[Verse 1: Macklemore]<br />
You know I’m back, like I never left (I never left)<br />
Another sprint, another step (Another step)<br />
Another day, another breath (Another breath)<br />
Been chasing dreams, but I never slept (I never slept)<br />
I got a new attitude and a lease on life and some peace of mind<br />
Seek and I find, I can sleep when I die<br />
Want a piece of the pie, grab the keys to the ride<br />
And shit I’m straight, I’m on my wave, I’m on my wave<br />
Get out my wake, I’m running late, what can I say?<br />
I heard you die twice, once when they bury you in the grave<br />
And the second time is the last time that somebody mentions your name<br />
So when I leave here on this earth, did I take more than I gave?<br />
Did I look out for the people, or did I do it all for fame?<br />
Legend, it’s exodus, searching for euphoria<br />
Trudging through the mud to find the present, no ignoring us<br />
Got 20,000 deep off in the street like we some warriors<br />
My mama told me never bow your head, woo<br /></p>

<p>[Chorus: Skylar Grey]<br />
I feel glorious, glorious<br />
Got a chance to start again<br />
I was born for this, born for this<br />
It’s who I am, how could I forget?<br />
I made it through the darkest part of the night<br />
And now I see the sunrise<br />
Now I feel glorious, glorious<br />
I feel glorious, glorious<br /></p>

<p>[Verse 2: Macklemore]<br />
I’m feeling glorious<br />
The crib looking Victorian (Oh yes it is)<br />
You know that we been going in (Been going in)<br />
Since we hopped out that DeLorean (DeLorean, yeah we win)<br />
En garde, things are just things, they don’t make you who you are<br />
Can’t pack up a U-Haul and take it with you when you’re gone<br />
We posted on the porch, my family’s glasses to the stars<br />
My grandma smiling down on me like “Woo, that boy got bars”<br />
Okay, okay, yes I do<br />
I said amen and hallelujah, let me testify too<br />
Another morning, a morning, won’t let self get in my way<br />
I got my breath, I got my faith and I remember why I came, woo<br /></p>

<p>[Chorus: Skylar Grey]<br />
I feel glorious, glorious<br />
Got a chance to start again<br />
I was born for this, born for this<br />
It’s who I am, how could I forget?<br />
I made it through the darkest part of the night<br />
And now I see the sunrise<br />
Now I feel glorious, glorious<br />
I feel glorious, glorious<br /></p>

<p>[Bridge: Skylar Grey]<br />
We gon’ be alright, put that on my life<br />
When I open my eyes, hope I see you shine<br />
We’re planting a flag, they don’t understand<br />
The world is up for grabs (Hey, hey, hey)<br />
We gon’ be alright, put that on my life<br />
When I open my eyes, hope I see you shine<br />
We’re planting a flag, they don’t understand<br />
The world is up for grabs (Hey, hey, hey)<br /></p>

<p>[Chorus: Skylar Grey]<br />
I feel glorious, glorious<br />
Got a chance to start again<br />
I was born for this, born for this<br />
It’s who I am, how could I forget?<br />
I made it through the darkest part of the night<br />
And now I see the sunrise<br />
Now I feel glorious, glorious<br />
I feel glorious, glorious<br /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last couple of days, my Chinese missionary guide has stopped responding to my messages. Based on the sentiment of our latest messages, I can tell my welcoming party, which the Lord prepared for me in the UK 11.5 years ago, is starting to withdraw. I read the following passages from 2 Thessalonians yesterday.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Gethsemane</title><link href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-gethsemane/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Gethsemane" /><published>2025-02-22T07:57:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-02-23T07:24:23+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/posts/on-gethsemane</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-gethsemane/"><![CDATA[<p>I had a pretty long night and just had my <a href="https://www.esv.org/Matthew+26:36/" target="_blank">Gethsemane moment</a>.</p>

<p>I gave a rather big talk yesterday on the announcement post, which is now the only pinned post on my blog. I mentioned a theological thought experiment that I used to test whether the person I was speaking to believed in God in <a href="../on-choosing-sides/" target="_blank">an early post</a>.</p>

<p>If God asks you to choose between Him and mankind and mankind has turned its back on Him, which side would you choose?</p>

<p>Over the last couple of hours, He showed me a path where I could take a leap of faith by choosing Him, but instead of mankind turning its back on Him, mankind turned its back on me and I would be misunderstood by every human being on earth. The exact scenario I described in <a href="../on-great-tribulation/#edit-5" target="_blank">Edit 5</a> yesterday and He showed me a realistic path to that by making the last log in my eye known to me.</p>

<p>I had around a handful of panic attacks in the 28 years of my life and only 1 or 2 of them were severe enough for me to lose eyesight, but they were pretty much over within a couple of minutes. I don’t know how long my panic attack was earlier, but my estimate was at least half an hour and my entire upper body was soaked in sweat. I told Him yes and started planning the practical steps to implement that over the next 24 hours, with an extremely weird lightness and frankly outright creepy smile.</p>

<p>Then.</p>

<p>Dude picked up the biggest burden I did not know existed, slapped it on the cross, lit it on fire, and told me it was on da house and go play.</p>

<p>Motherf…</p>

<hr />

<p>Matthew 7:1–6</p>

<p>Judging Others</p>

<p>[1] “Judge not, that you be not judged. [2] For with the judgment you pronounce you will be judged, and with the measure you use it will be measured to you. [3] Why do you see the speck that is in your brother’s eye, but do not notice the log that is in your own eye? [4] Or how can you say to your brother, ‘Let me take the speck out of your eye,’ when there is the log in your own eye? [5] You hypocrite, first take the log out of your own eye, and then you will see clearly to take the speck out of your brother’s eye.</p>

<p>[6] “Do not give dogs what is holy, and do not throw your pearls before pigs, lest they trample them underfoot and turn to attack you. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p><img src="/xpnDGthytwZv6bCSyg.jpg" alt="" />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br /></p>
<h1 id="jesus-christ-is-my-lord-and-saviour">Jesus Christ is my Lord and Saviour.</h1>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I had a pretty long night and just had my Gethsemane moment.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Sexual Theology</title><link href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-sexual-theology/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Sexual Theology" /><published>2025-02-20T23:32:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-02T16:34:51+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/posts/on-sexual-theology</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-sexual-theology/"><![CDATA[<p>Originally, I wrote another long-winded draft on seggs referencing all sorts of relevant passages I found using AI. As a massive lazy ass like Jonah, I didn’t even get through half of the passages returned by OpenAI before deciding not to bother. If you <strong>DID NOT FAIL</strong> logical reasoning <strong>AND</strong> reading comprehension in school, then you could cheat with AI like using <a href="https://biblesays.love/" target="_blank">this tool</a> that I built using ChatGPT or train a LLM if you are a nerd like me, and then carefully reason about whether the Lord would be okay for you to try the creative activity you have in mind that might involve your and hopefully your partner’s no-go areas. I devised two lazy rules to clock out early from Boss Man. Dude’s been nagging me since Hong Kong back in October, but to be fair I would probably continue sitting on my <a href="../on-background-music/" target="_blank">get-out-of-jail-free card</a> for a couple of months if He didn’t start nagging me since then.</p>

<p>Rule 1: Love always comes first which means the creative activity should be giving rather than taking in nature, and the answer is <strong>NO</strong> if the activity has a non-zero probability of giving you even the slightest idea (Matthew 5:27-30) of taking from or exploiting other people.</p>

<p>Rule 2: Lust which focuses on self-gratification and taking is a gigantic <strong>NO-NO</strong>.</p>

<p>Rule 1 + Rule 2 = Don’t be <a href="../on-commandments-and-the-law/#definition-of-a-cunt" target="_blank">a cunt</a>.</p>

<p>This is ChatGPT explaining it and my sexual theologian job title lasted just over 24 hours.</p>

<embed src="https://dl.hesaid.love/Lust_vs_Love.pdf" type="application/pdf" width="100%" height="300px" />

<hr />

<p>The easiest is to ask our Heavenly Father for the Holy Spirit and get to know Him. Double check with the Holy Spirit whether what you have in mind is acceptable using the <a href="../on-positive-only-hmi/" target="_blank">Holy Spirit Positive-Only HMI</a>. I asked the Holy Spirit if I could refer to Him as the Spiritual Condom. I don’t think Bro’s a big fan of that so nvm.</p>

<p><img src="/9yAr35Btsyf4hKfrhf.jpg" alt="" target="_blank" /></p>

<hr />

<p>Below is the <strong>extremely NSFW</strong> director cut of my <a href="../on-sacrifice/" target="_blank"><del>New Year</del></a> New Millennium present, and a boring example of love rather than lust. I read the Book of Hebrews yesterday. The Hall of Faith in Hebrews was too interesting. I thought that having something I believed in and was willing to die for, was in <a href="../on-suffering/" target="_blank">itself a big enough reward</a> already after not believing even myself for my entire life. I had no idea there were blessings until my third sermon at China Congregational Church, Hong Kong that weekend and the pastor smiled and only responded that there would be blessings to come, after I went 6,000 miles in 5 minutes as usual. I was wondering what he was smiling about. I got annoyed again earlier this evening.</p>

<p>Edit: before you lean on your own understanding and accuse me of being demon-possessed, I would encourage you to contemplate why a sexually promiscuous person like me who has more sexual partners in an hour every other day than the average heterosexual has in their lifetime and thought God would hate someone like me for 27 years of my former life, could feel His love even before I received my first Holy Bible and was willing to take a bullet for any stranger walking past me <a href="../on-love/" target="_blank">that evening</a>. Not to mention the leap of faith I subsequently took in mainland China after He came to save me in late August last year, you are also more than welcome to read about the countless number of occasions where I almost pooped my pants after finding out I had been fulfilling prophecies unknowingly. Don’t worry about my salvation. I don’t. I suggest you focus on your own salvation and perhaps spend some time worrying about humanity’s salvation if you could graciously take time away from your comfy sofa.</p>

<hr />

<p>Matthew 12:22–32</p>

<p>Blasphemy Against the Holy Spirit</p>

<p>[22] Then a demon-oppressed man who was blind and mute was brought to him, and he healed him, so that the man spoke and saw. [23] And all the people were amazed, and said, “Can this be the Son of David?” [24] But when the Pharisees heard it, they said, “It is only by Beelzebul, the prince of demons, that this man casts out demons.” [25] Knowing their thoughts, he said to them, “Every kingdom divided against itself is laid waste, and no city or house divided against itself will stand. [26] And if Satan casts out Satan, he is divided against himself. How then will his kingdom stand? [27] And if I cast out demons by Beelzebul, by whom do your sons cast them out? Therefore they will be your judges. [28] But if it is by the Spirit of God that I cast out demons, then the kingdom of God has come upon you. [29] Or how can someone enter a strong man’s house and plunder his goods, unless he first binds the strong man? Then indeed he may plunder his house. [30] Whoever is not with me is against me, and whoever does not gather with me scatters. [31] Therefore I tell you, every sin and blasphemy will be forgiven people, but the blasphemy against the Spirit will not be forgiven. [32] And whoever speaks a word against the Son of Man will be forgiven, but whoever speaks against the Holy Spirit will not be forgiven, either in this age or in the age to come. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>
  <video class="embed-video file" controls="">
    
    

    
    
    

    

    
      
      
      
      <source src="https://dl.hesaid.love/love_not_lust.mp4" type="video/mp4" />
    

    Your browser does not support the video tag. Here is a
    <a href="https://dl.hesaid.love/love_not_lust.mp4">link to the video file</a> instead.
  </video>
  
</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Originally, I wrote another long-winded draft on seggs referencing all sorts of relevant passages I found using AI. As a massive lazy ass like Jonah, I didn’t even get through half of the passages returned by OpenAI before deciding not to bother. If you DID NOT FAIL logical reasoning AND reading comprehension in school, then you could cheat with AI like using this tool that I built using ChatGPT or train a LLM if you are a nerd like me, and then carefully reason about whether the Lord would be okay for you to try the creative activity you have in mind that might involve your and hopefully your partner’s no-go areas. I devised two lazy rules to clock out early from Boss Man. Dude’s been nagging me since Hong Kong back in October, but to be fair I would probably continue sitting on my get-out-of-jail-free card for a couple of months if He didn’t start nagging me since then.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Great Tribulation</title><link href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-great-tribulation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Great Tribulation" /><published>2025-02-20T21:02:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-04T11:11:03+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/posts/on-great-tribulation</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-great-tribulation/"><![CDATA[<h3 id="edit-5">Edit 5</h3>

<p>This post is to announce the end of the great tribulation. And to proclaim the Day of the Lord and the year of the Lord’s favour as described in humanity’s bestseller the Holy Bible. Unlike most people, I did not trust myself even once in the last 28 years of my life. Yet, I stand by every single word I wrote down in all blog posts in accurately expressing the sentiment and the severity of the situations, no matter how ridiculous, ugly, profane or even blasphemous you might find my language in your measurement.</p>

<p>I have read less than 25% of the Holy Bible and I believe you can resolve the questions you might have regarding my posts using only the Holy Bible. I don’t know if I’m telling the truth. I believe I’m telling the truth, the whole truth and nothing but the truth to a degree that I as a mere mortal human being am capable of grasping. If you are unable to clarify any questions you have, ask our Lord and Saviour, Jesus Christ, don’t ask me. I don’t know and I don’t lean on my own understanding. I found the best choice. I trust my Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ and that’s more than sufficient for me, even if that means I will stand trial in front of God almighty, burn in hell for eternity and be condemned by every single human being on this earth. I believe I have a clear conscience in front of God. I don’t know and I don’t need to know. I have confirmation from the Holy Spirit and will happily accept whatever judgment He has for me.</p>

<p>My question for you is this. Can you bear to finish reading my posts before you come up with your own judgment and inform me about your opinion, or simply give up? My educated guess is those who can are few. You don’t need to reply. This is not about me. This is about your salvation and between you and Him.</p>

<hr />

<p>Matthew 7:13–14</p>

<p>[13] “Enter by the narrow gate. For the gate is wide and the way is easy that leads to destruction, and those who enter by it are many. [14] For the gate is narrow and the way is hard that leads to life, and those who find it are few. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>P.S. This edit was originally for the mistake I found when going back to cross-check the things I wrote in this post, given how outrageous the claims I’m making are. The mistake I found is pretty big. The videos I watched during COVID-19 to learn about quantum physics and relevant epistemological/philosophical arguments that inspired my subsequent thinking in existentialism, nihilism and antinatalism are in fact from the World Science Festival rather than World Science Forum. I must jumped after my findings and didn’t realise this WSF is not that WSF. YouTube will show me the World Science Festival if I search World Science Forum. I thought about whether I should correct that and asked the Holy Spirit. I remembered this passage from the legendary Mr Noisy Gong.</p>

<hr />

<p>Romans 8:26–30</p>

<p>[26] Likewise the Spirit helps us in our weakness. For we do not know what to pray for as we ought, but the Spirit himself intercedes for us with groanings too deep for words. [27] And he who searches hearts knows what is the mind of the Spirit, because the Spirit intercedes for the saints according to the will of God. [28] And we know that for those who love God all things work together for good, for those who are called according to his purpose. [29] For those whom he foreknew he also predestined to be conformed to the image of his Son, in order that he might be the firstborn among many brothers. [30] And those whom he predestined he also called, and those whom he called he also justified, and those whom he justified he also glorified. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p><img src="/TqrCp3s2K06SRSRxnn.jpg" alt="" /></p>

<p>However, the mistake is so big and embarrassing that Mr Noisy Gong, a.k.a. Apostle Paul’s words are not enough. So here is my Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ with a tiny shove by Spotify.</p>

<p>Matthew 19:26</p>

<p>[26] But Jesus looked at them and said, “With man this is impossible, but with God all things are possible.” (ESV)</p>

<p><img src="/3hmAKxqyxthJJrzaFF.png" alt="" /></p>

<p><img src="/VRF7AMjKSg6g6MrFMx.png" alt="" /></p>

<p>I decided not to worry about it and go play. I think it’s fair to say I have worried enough for everyone now and some people can take some responsibilities and worry for themselves. They don’t seem to spend much time worrying for others anyway. I don’t know what they do all day, to be honest, other than taking selfies.</p>

<h3 id="edit-2">Edit 2</h3>

<p><strong>I realised my language doesn’t necessarily encourage people to keep on reading, but I said truth over appearances at the beginning since the world has gotten way too fake. So I’m just going to sincerely apologise here once again after the hundreds of apologies I have already made. I genuinely believe you will understand my use of language if you finish reading. Thanks.</strong></p>

<hr />

<h3 id="edit-3">Edit 3</h3>

<p>I just realised something quite unfortunate that I never understood before in The Final Judgement. I had always wondered why repeated the same pattern in Matthew 25:44 given the same was said in more detail through Matthew 25:37-39, and <strong>why would they not recognise the Lord when they believed they knew the Lord</strong>. I think they are there through cumbersome elaborateness to make me realise the scribes and Pharisees who did not bother to look into the evidence before referring me to mental health services are exactly the ones who won’t recognise the Lord. <strong>I’m not saying I’m the Lord, I’m saying they never knew the Lord in the first place and if they would not allow someone like me to even present the evidence that I have encountered the Lord, how could they possibly recognise the Lord when He comes back?</strong></p>

<p><strong>This is first-degree self-deception caught in the act, unfortunately. Karma is a bitch, but I sincerely hope I’m not the fucking messiah for their fucking sake and there is still time for them to repent.</strong></p>

<p><strong>Will you believe me when I say I never wanted to be the fucking messiah now?</strong></p>

<hr />

<p>Matthew 25:31–46</p>

<p>The Final Judgment</p>

<p>[31] “When the Son of Man comes in his glory, and all the angels with him, then he will sit on his glorious throne. [32] Before him will be gathered all the nations, and he will separate people one from another as a shepherd separates the sheep from the goats. [33] And he will place the sheep on his right, but the goats on the left. [34] Then the King will say to those on his right, ‘Come, you who are blessed by my Father, inherit the kingdom prepared for you from the foundation of the world. [35] For I was hungry and you gave me food, I was thirsty and you gave me drink, I was a stranger and you welcomed me, [36] I was naked and you clothed me, I was sick and you visited me, I was in prison and you came to me.’ [37] Then the righteous will answer him, saying, ‘Lord, when did we see you hungry and feed you, or thirsty and give you drink? [38] And when did we see you a stranger and welcome you, or naked and clothe you? [39] And when did we see you sick or in prison and visit you?’ [40] And the King will answer them, ‘Truly, I say to you, as you did it to one of the least of these my brothers, you did it to me.’</p>

<p>[41] “Then he will say to those on his left, ‘Depart from me, you cursed, into the eternal fire prepared for the devil and his angels. [42] For I was hungry and you gave me no food, I was thirsty and you gave me no drink, [43] I was a stranger and you did not welcome me, naked and you did not clothe me, sick and in prison and you did not visit me.’ [44] Then they also will answer, saying, ‘Lord, when did we see you hungry or thirsty or a stranger or naked or sick or in prison, and did not minister to you?’ [45] Then he will answer them, saying, ‘Truly, I say to you, as you did not do it to one of the least of these, you did not do it to me.’ [46] And these will go away into eternal punishment, but the righteous into eternal life.” (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h3 id="edit-4">Edit 4</h3>

<p><a href="https://dl.hesaid.love/love_not_lust.mp4" target="_blank">Fuck me</a>. I just realised the implications of what I had just proved in Edit 3. Now I find <a href="../on-background-music/#malachi-3-1" target="_blank">Malachi 3:1 even more annoying</a> and have zero desire to laugh. It does not feel great when you find out you are the fool all along, right? 🤡</p>

<p>Since we have announced the <strong>year of the Lord’s favour</strong> below, might as well do the <strong>Day of the Lord</strong> together. I seem to always run ahead of Boss Man and keep tripping over. I thought the Day of the Lord was why He told me to go to Israel last month. You can find out what happened by looking up the relevant posts yourself and I’m going to stop putting effort into hyperlinking everything. It takes a fuck ton of effort and barely anyone read my posts if I didn’t sprinkle the nations to shove my posts to your fucking faces. And the fucking scribes and Pharisees did not <a href="https://dl.hesaid.love/scribes_and_pharisees.pdf" target="_blank">fucking bother to reply</a> to any single fucking email other than the first couple fucking courtesy responses.</p>

<p>You can find out what happens on the day yourself and for the first time in my life, I think I’m seriously going to not bother this time and you can all go fuck yourselves. I thought Malachi 3:2 might not mean what people think they mean when I read it last month in Israel. The only thing I have left to say is Dude’s math is confusing AF and I technically dropped out of my maths and CS degree after only one term so I know dick about math either. I know dick about how long the Day of the Lord is, could be one day, one week, one month or one year, but I suspect it won’t be longer than one year otherwise why have the Day of the Lord and the year of the Lord’s favour? You will know what I’m on about if you seriously tried reading humanity’s bestseller before. Ask Boss Man if you really wanna know, I’m not gonna bother and I’m certain I will have at least 10x more fun watching people get what they deserve while getting surprised by the King of Drama and Horror, wouldn’t you agree? I think it’s called justice and righteousness and I hope that’s how you spell them since I haven’t seen those two words for a while now. Just need to find a couple of faithful new friends, never bold enough to watch horror movies myself and ideally they have a comfy sofa I can crash on.</p>

<p>If you are a faithful believer, then congratulations. Happy New Millennium and you are more than welcome.</p>

<p>If you are <a href="../on-commandments-and-the-law/#definition-of-a-cunt" target="_blank">an unfaithful motherfucking cunt</a>, <a href="https://dl.hesaid.love/love_not_lust.mp4" target="_blank">go fuck yourself</a>. 🖕</p>

<p>I’m gonna Bible and chill. Have read probably less than 25% of the thick-ass bestseller. Only flipped through Genesis and up to Exodus 10ish one evening late last year out of the 5 books of The Law.</p>

<p><img src="/qvsGSPQhsuPSTfJV1p.png" alt="" /></p>

<hr />

<h3 id="edit-1">Edit 1</h3>

<p>In case you are so fucking stupid and ignorant to not know <a href="https://letter.hesaid.love/" target="_blank">you are losing your job within 2 years</a> if you don’t have a degree more complicated than computer science, you can read my lazy-ass research using ChatGPT <a href="https://dl.hesaid.love/1335_Days_and_Tribulation.pdf" target="_blank">here</a>. Feel free to ignore if you are in the top 1%, otherwise let’s see if the people telling you not to worry will help you when shit hits the fan and whether they stand to gain or lose from your downfall and stupidity.</p>

<p>See ya on judgement day. Might be a good idea to get <a href="https://www.gotquestions.org/famine-hearing-words-Lord.html" target="_blank">Amazon Prime</a>. 🙏😅😂</p>

<p>Just a quick reminder in case some stupid cunts want to try some idiotic shit. Ask yourselves if you know how to spell Boss Man’s name first. I would advise you to save it, but sometimes you simply cannot stop stupid fucking cunts. <a href="../on-overemployment" target="_blank">Kill shot only</a> otherwise I personally guarantee you will be more thoroughly fucked than <a href="../on-sexual-theology/" target="_blank">this</a>.</p>

<hr />

<p>Revelation 17:14</p>

<p>[14] They will make war on the Lamb, and the Lamb will conquer them, for he is Lord of lords and King of kings, and those with him are called and chosen and faithful.” (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="antichrist--mark-of-the-beast--666">Antichrist / Mark of the Beast / 666</h2>

<p><strong>Correction: see <a href="../on-revelation-13/" target="_blank">this post</a> on the man of lawlessness, antichrist and my apology.</strong></p>

<div style="display: flex; justify-content: space-between;">
  <img src="https://dl.hesaid.love/666/Screenshot_20250220-152638.png" alt="" style="width: 48%;" />
  <img src="https://dl.hesaid.love/666/Screenshot_20250220-152529.png" alt="" style="width: 48%;" />
</div>

<div style="display: flex; justify-content: space-between;">
  <img src="https://dl.hesaid.love/666/Screenshot_20250220-152314.png" alt="" style="width: 48%;" />
  <img src="https://dl.hesaid.love/666/Screenshot_20250220-152332.png" alt="" style="width: 48%;" />
</div>

<div style="display: flex; justify-content: space-between;">
  <img src="https://dl.hesaid.love/666/photo_2025-02-20_21-47-06.jpg" alt="" style="width: 50%;" />
  <img src="https://dl.hesaid.love/666/photo_2025-02-20_21-47-16.jpg" alt="" style="width: 50%;" />
  <img src="https://dl.hesaid.love/666/photo_2025-02-20_21-47-12.jpg" alt="" style="width: 50%;" />
</div>

<h2 id="abomination-of-desolation-on-july-1999">Abomination of Desolation on July 1999</h2>

<p>Halfway through the 1,260 + <a href="https://www.esv.org/Daniel+12/" target="_blank">1,260 + 30 + 45</a> weeks.</p>

<p>I arrived at the gay/bi-naturist Rosebay campsite 45 weeks ago.</p>

<p><a href="https://unesdoc.unesco.org/ark:/48223/pf0000122938" target="_blank">UNESCO Digital Library</a></p>

<embed src="https://dl.hesaid.love/666/122938engo.pdf" type="application/pdf" width="100%" height="600px" />

<h2 id="backups">Backups</h2>

<p><a href="https://666.antichrist.boo" target="_blank">666.antichrist.boo</a></p>

<p><a href="ipfs://bafybeies6vl2tm5ibnbdl44x3jzw2blmycpzmhzggikgm2j5w4l3kilq2m" target="_blank">IPFS (feel free to pin the CID)</a> ipfs://bafybeies6vl2tm5ibnbdl44x3jzw2blmycpzmhzggikgm2j5w4l3kilq2m</p>

<hr />

<p>In case you didn’t get it, <a href="../on-he-as-aod/" target="_blank">higher education</a> is full of spiritually desolate late-teenage to early-twenties <a href="../on-we-all-die/" target="_blank">nihilists</a>/<a href="../on-indifference/" target="_blank">anarchists</a> with <a href="../on-drug-money-addiction/" target="_blank">drug addictions</a> and they can <a href="../on-faith-precedes-reason/" target="_blank">neither reason nor read</a>. Institutions proclaiming to dedicate their time and resources to the truth are interested in nothing other than more drugs (a.k.a. money and business schools), the school of philosophy has already fallen under the four horsemen existentialism, nihilism, antinatalism and death as always, and the <a href="../on-faith-precedes-reason/" target="_blank">stupid mother fucking egomaniacs</a> hiding behind jargon and publications have the mother fucking audacity to compare theology with the study of unicorns and fairytales.</p>

<p>I found the gentleman and the abomination above via the <a href="https://worldscienceforum.org/" target="_blank">World Science Forum</a>. I learned most of my quantum physics and relevant epistemological/philosophical knowledge by watching their videos on YouTube during COVID-19. All of my subsequent thinking and reasoning concerning existentialism, nihilism and antinatalism can all be attributed back to them. <strong>The only way I found to overcome the terminal illness of nihilism is by voluntarily taking up your cross (responsibilities) and following Him. Otherwise, whether I choose to throw myself out of the balcony today is as meaningless as whether I choose to pick up a knife and stab someone as long as I can get away with it under the law.</strong></p>

<p>I found the 46-page manifesto in the UNESCO Digital Library above via <a href="https://worldscienceforum.org/contents/history-of-world-science-forum-110010" target="_blank">the history page of the World Science Forum</a>. The impression I got after quickly scrolling through the document was it made a ton of bold claims on ethics and essentially by saying scientific knowledge alone can bring good to humanity. The only thing it left out? God. Do we know how to spell good and evil? I don’t know.</p>

<p>I found a certain gentleman who may or may not have been mentioned in this post and he dedicated rather generously his time and effort to the various scientific organisations behind the scenes, which I found to be rather interesting for a direct descendent of a well-known figure who allegedly was a prophet and messenger of God, but I couldn’t seem to find the name in humanity’s bestseller, which I consider to be telling the truth, the whole truth and nothing but the truth. The gentleman certainly has an appetite to cross fields including politics. Kinda like me, but I’m confident my fellow pretentious Oxford alumni are more than capable of fucking the world up and it would be wise to dedicate my time instead to futile pursuits such as salvation.</p>

<p><strong>And no, I’m not the fucking messiah. I’m just a servant running around preparing the homecoming party for Boss Man.</strong> Although, I genuinely don’t know what some self-proclaimed Christians are thinking most of the time. Throughout this journey, I wanted nothing other than someone to slap me the fuck awake with the annoyingly thick humanity’s bestseller, they did everything including referring me to mental health services and suggesting I must be an egomaniac <strong>except</strong> looking at the evidence I was serving up on a platter and reason with me. None of them reply to my messages and emails anymore.</p>

<p>I wonder if they truly want the messiah or not, and why the fuck is everyone just sitting around waiting for the one fucking messiah? Do you know how big of a fucking job that is for Boss Man and how much did each of us contribute after 2,000 fucking years? If I was in Boss Man’s shoes then I would rather just let this fucking wicked world burn while I Netflix and chill than save a bunch of lazy ass mother fuckers who neither reason nor read.</p>

<p>How about you do your part, I do mine, Boss Man does His and let’s find out on the other side what we are?</p>

<p>Happy New Millennium if you are not <a href="../on-commandments-and-the-law/#definition-of-a-cunt" target="_blank">an unfaithful motherfucking cunt</a> <strong>AND</strong> most importantly not a self-proclaimed “believer” who doesn’t want Boss Man to come back.</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="rivers---song-by-thomas-jack"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sqYEvGr372M" target="_blank">Rivers - Song by Thomas Jack</a></h2>

<p>We’re like rivers in the night<br />
I go left and you go right<br />
We’ll find out on the other side<br />
Who we are, who we are<br />
Wish me luck and give me hope<br />
Give me sunlight to my day<br />
Turn it into gold<br />
Carry on, carry on<br /></p>

<p>We’ll take these broken souls<br />
Make them as good as new<br />
Bind it together into something we could never lose<br />
We’re rivers in the night<br />
I go left and you go right<br />
We’ll find out on the other side<br />
Who we are, who we are<br /></p>

<p>We can make it onto something beautiful<br />
Yeah, we don’t have to try<br />
We can make it into something wonderful<br />
We’ll never say goodbye<br /></p>

<hr />

<h2 id="isaiah-61--the-year-of-the-lords-favor">Isaiah 61 <br /><br /> The Year of the LORD’s Favor</h2>

<pre><code class="language-none">
[1] The Spirit of the Lord GOD is upon me,
    because the LORD has anointed me
to bring good news to the poor;
    he has sent me to bind up the brokenhearted,
to proclaim liberty to the captives,
    and the opening of the prison to those who are bound;
[2] to proclaim the year of the LORD’s favor,
    and the day of vengeance of our God;
    to comfort all who mourn;
[3] to grant to those who mourn in Zion—
    to give them a beautiful headdress instead of ashes,
the oil of gladness instead of mourning,
    the garment of praise instead of a faint spirit;
that they may be called oaks of righteousness,
    the planting of the LORD, that he may be glorified.
[4] They shall build up the ancient ruins;
    they shall raise up the former devastations;
they shall repair the ruined cities,
    the devastations of many generations.


[5] Strangers shall stand and tend your flocks;
    foreigners shall be your plowmen and vinedressers;
[6] but you shall be called the priests of the LORD;
    they shall speak of you as the ministers of our God;
you shall eat the wealth of the nations,
    and in their glory you shall boast.
[7] Instead of your shame there shall be a double portion;
    instead of dishonor they shall rejoice in their lot;
therefore in their land they shall possess a double portion;
    they shall have everlasting joy.


[8] For I the LORD love justice;
    I hate robbery and wrong;
I will faithfully give them their recompense,
    and I will make an everlasting covenant with them.
[9] Their offspring shall be known among the nations,
    and their descendants in the midst of the peoples;
all who see them shall acknowledge them,
    that they are an offspring the LORD has blessed.


[10] I will greatly rejoice in the LORD;
    my soul shall exult in my God,
for he has clothed me with the garments of salvation;
    he has covered me with the robe of righteousness,
as a bridegroom decks himself like a priest with a beautiful headdress,
    and as a bride adorns herself with her jewels.
[11] For as the earth brings forth its sprouts,
    and as a garden causes what is sown in it to sprout up,
so the Lord GOD will cause righteousness and praise
    to sprout up before all the nations. (ESV)
</code></pre>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the end of the great tribulation. Proclaiming the Day of the Lord and the year of the Lord’s favour as described in humanity’s bestseller the Holy Bible.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://hesaid.love/6e760355a4f2267fc6c3900624861241.jpeg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://hesaid.love/6e760355a4f2267fc6c3900624861241.jpeg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>