<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://hesaid.love/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://hesaid.love/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" /><updated>2025-02-26T11:59:22+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Aaron @ He Said Love</title><subtitle>A rampant homosexual writing about Boss Man&apos;s love and the good, bad, ugly, stupid, idiotic, crazy, and insane during my walk with Him. Dude made me feel more loved in a week than anyone, including my parents, ever managed to make me feel my entire life combined. Believed since 22 September 2024. Zeal for His house consumes me. DO NOT take my words at face value. Trust, but verify. The Lord is the only source of truth, ask the Holy Spirit to confirm, not me. The fire in hell would be warmer than the coldness I felt in this world. How about you do your part, I do mine, Boss Man does His and let&apos;s find out on the other side what we are?</subtitle><entry><title type="html">On Messiah(s)</title><link href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-messiahs/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Messiah(s)" /><published>2025-02-26T06:52:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-02-26T06:52:00+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/posts/on-messiahs</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-messiahs/"><![CDATA[<p>Yesterday was the second time someone told me that trying to save other people is a sign of pride. They also kindly informed me that I’m an egomaniac who believes that I might be a chosen one. Unlike the first time, it was slightly better this time since it came from a Christian. Although, does that make it worse? I don’t know. I’m not sure I know how to spell good and evil anymore. Let me know if you know how to spell good and evil. Thanks.</p>

<p>Allegedly Christians like to ask the question what would Jesus do when facing ethical and moral choices, evidently it’s called discipleship otherwise known as following Jesus. I would like to reiterate my position once again and make another apology in advance for the language I’m about to use since I noticed that no mother fucker tries to learn what happened first before opening their mouths and informing me of their fucking opinions. I had zero mother fucking desire to be the fucking messiah and I still have zero mother fucking desire to be the messiah. I don’t know if I’m the fucking messiah, and you are more than fucking welcome to inform me about your fucking opinion after you learned what happened. I wrote them all down.</p>

<p>It’s been 157 days since I believed, and throughout this journey, I realised the m-word is a big no-no to mention to believers. And you would automatically receive the labels including but not limited to egomaniac, megalomaniac and narcissist. I couldn’t help but find it both ironic and sarcastic that Christians have been hoping for the second coming for over 2,000 years now and the immediate reaction they have when some random dude wants to show them evidence is to refer them to mental health services without bothering with glancing the evidence served up on a platter, despite the dude’s only wish is to find out why life became magic and why people lost reasoning capabilities overnight. Frankly, speaking from the perspective of a rampant homosexual who has more sexual partners in an hour every other day than the average heterosexual will have in their entire life, I kinda feel bad for Boss Man given the stigma and discrimination attached to His job title. He did have a pretty rough time and went on a sabbatical not long after a pretty bad workplace injury. I will check with Him next time we speak to see how’s that lawsuit preparation going and when He will be done with His career break. I’m pretty sure Dude’s a worse procrastinator than me.</p>

<p>I kinda asked Him for some stupid stuff when I first learned how to pray including but not limited to letting me suffer and save some random people including but not limited to rampant homosexuals. Whether or not He will allow me to, I don’t know. I trust Him and I did not trust myself even once in my entire life. He does tell me to stop working and go chill the fuck out somewhat regularly. The health insurance is pretty good with this Boss, and I heard a Colleague got injured three years into the job and Dude is still chilling on paid leave after 2,000 years. My former life ambition was to build an interesting tech startup and ideally work up to a net worth of 10-50 mil so that I could study and explore any extremely random interest that I somehow magically come up with every 3 to 6 months, and could still be in t-shirt and jeans without anyone bothering me. I was definitely on track with that with a mid-six-figure income at 27, then I tried to take my first holiday and you are reading about the ongoing nuclear fallout. I’m gonna work my ass off, both literally and figuratively, and see if I can also go on a sabbatical for something like forever and ever.</p>

<p>Feel free to get in touch after you find out about the m-word thing. To be honest, given how successfully we managed to fuck this up, I think the singular m-word might not be enough, and we might be able to unfuck this quicker if we start using the plural form. But it took decades for my community, some of whom are rampant homosexuals like me who enjoy getting fucked in the ass by talented Germans in FickstutenMarkt for 4hrs+ non-stop whilst listening to sick Berlin techno, to fight for our rights to be equal citizens of society, and we still face discrimination today. Statistically speaking, I think the m-word community will have a significantly harder time, but speaking from first-hand personal experience, statistics is a synonym for null in their dictionary.</p>

<hr />

<p>Matthew 24:22</p>

<p>[22] And if those days had not been cut short, no human being would be saved. But for the sake of the elect those days will be cut short. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>Matthew 24:15–22</p>

<p>The Abomination of Desolation</p>

<p>[15] “So when you see the abomination of desolation spoken of by the prophet Daniel, standing in the holy place (let the reader understand), [16] then let those who are in Judea flee to the mountains. [17] Let the one who is on the housetop not go down to take what is in his house, [18] and let the one who is in the field not turn back to take his cloak. [19] And alas for women who are pregnant and for those who are nursing infants in those days! [20] Pray that your flight may not be in winter or on a Sabbath. [21] For then there will be great tribulation, such as has not been from the beginning of the world until now, no, and never will be. [22] And if those days had not been cut short, no human being would be saved. But for the sake of the elect those days will be cut short. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>Matthew 12:7</p>

<p>[7] And if you had known what this means, ‘I desire mercy, and not sacrifice,’ you would not have condemned the guiltless. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>Matthew 9:9–13</p>

<p>Jesus Calls Matthew</p>

<p>[9] As Jesus passed on from there, he saw a man called Matthew sitting at the tax booth, and he said to him, “Follow me.” And he rose and followed him.</p>

<p>[10] And as Jesus reclined at table in the house, behold, many tax collectors and sinners came and were reclining with Jesus and his disciples. [11] And when the Pharisees saw this, they said to his disciples, “Why does your teacher eat with tax collectors and sinners?” [12] But when he heard it, he said, “Those who are well have no need of a physician, but those who are sick. [13] Go and learn what this means: ‘I desire mercy, and not sacrifice.’ For I came not to call the righteous, but sinners.” (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>Matthew 7:1–5</p>

<p>Judging Others</p>

<p>[1] “Judge not, that you be not judged. [2] For with the judgment you pronounce you will be judged, and with the measure you use it will be measured to you. [3] Why do you see the speck that is in your brother’s eye, but do not notice the log that is in your own eye? [4] Or how can you say to your brother, ‘Let me take the speck out of your eye,’ when there is the log in your own eye? [5] You hypocrite, first take the log out of your own eye, and then you will see clearly to take the speck out of your brother’s eye. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>Luke 12:13–14</p>

<p>The Parable of the Rich Fool</p>

<p>[13] Someone in the crowd said to him, “Teacher, tell my brother to divide the inheritance with me.” [14] But he said to him, “Man, who made me a judge or arbitrator over you?” (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>Hosea 6</p>

<p>Israel and Judah Are Unrepentant</p>

<p>[1] “Come, let us return to the LORD;<br />
  for he has torn us, that he may heal us;<br />
  he has struck us down, and he will bind us up.<br />
 [2] After two days he will revive us;<br />
  on the third day he will raise us up,<br />
  that we may live before him.<br />
 [3] Let us know; let us press on to know the LORD;<br />
  his going out is sure as the dawn;<br />
 he will come to us as the showers,<br />
  as the spring rains that water the earth.”<br /></p>

<p>[4] What shall I do with you, O Ephraim?<br />
  What shall I do with you, O Judah?<br />
 Your love is like a morning cloud,<br />
  like the dew that goes early away.<br />
 [5] Therefore I have hewn them by the prophets;<br />
  I have slain them by the words of my mouth,<br />
  and my judgment goes forth as the light.<br />
 [6] For I desire steadfast love and not sacrifice,<br />
  the knowledge of God rather than burnt offerings.<br /></p>

<p>[7] But like Adam they transgressed the covenant;<br />
  there they dealt faithlessly with me.<br />
 [8] Gilead is a city of evildoers,<br />
  tracked with blood.<br />
 [9] As robbers lie in wait for a man,<br />
  so the priests band together;<br />
 they murder on the way to Shechem;<br />
  they commit villainy.<br />
 [10] In the house of Israel I have seen a horrible thing;<br />
  Ephraim’s whoredom is there; Israel is defiled.<br /></p>

<p>[11] For you also, O Judah, a harvest is appointed.<br /></p>

<p>When I restore the fortunes of my people, (ESV)<br /></p>

<hr />

<p>Genesis 18:22–33</p>

<p>Abraham Intercedes for Sodom</p>

<p>[22] So the men turned from there and went toward Sodom, but Abraham still stood before the LORD. [23] Then Abraham drew near and said, “Will you indeed sweep away the righteous with the wicked? [24] Suppose there are fifty righteous within the city. Will you then sweep away the place and not spare it for the fifty righteous who are in it? [25] Far be it from you to do such a thing, to put the righteous to death with the wicked, so that the righteous fare as the wicked! Far be that from you! Shall not the Judge of all the earth do what is just?” [26] And the LORD said, “If I find at Sodom fifty righteous in the city, I will spare the whole place for their sake.”</p>

<p>[27] Abraham answered and said, “Behold, I have undertaken to speak to the Lord, I who am but dust and ashes. [28] Suppose five of the fifty righteous are lacking. Will you destroy the whole city for lack of five?” And he said, “I will not destroy it if I find forty-five there.” [29] Again he spoke to him and said, “Suppose forty are found there.” He answered, “For the sake of forty I will not do it.” [30] Then he said, “Oh let not the Lord be angry, and I will speak. Suppose thirty are found there.” He answered, “I will not do it, if I find thirty there.” [31] He said, “Behold, I have undertaken to speak to the Lord. Suppose twenty are found there.” He answered, “For the sake of twenty I will not destroy it.” [32] Then he said, “Oh let not the Lord be angry, and I will speak again but this once. Suppose ten are found there.” He answered, “For the sake of ten I will not destroy it.” [33] And the LORD went his way, when he had finished speaking to Abraham, and Abraham returned to his place. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>Ezekiel 22:29–31</p>

<p>[29] The people of the land have practiced extortion and committed robbery. They have oppressed the poor and needy, and have extorted from the sojourner without justice. [30] And I sought for a man among them who should build up the wall and stand in the breach before me for the land, that I should not destroy it, but I found none. [31] Therefore I have poured out my indignation upon them. I have consumed them with the fire of my wrath. I have returned their way upon their heads, declares the Lord GOD.” (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>Jeremiah 5:1–5</p>

<p>Jerusalem Refused to Repent</p>

<p>[1] Run to and fro through the streets of Jerusalem,<br />
  look and take note!<br />
 Search her squares to see<br />
  if you can find a man,<br />
 one who does justice<br />
  and seeks truth,<br />
 that I may pardon her.<br />
 [2] Though they say, “As the LORD lives,”<br />
  yet they swear falsely.<br />
 [3] O LORD, do not your eyes look for truth?<br />
 You have struck them down,<br />
  but they felt no anguish;<br />
 you have consumed them,<br />
  but they refused to take correction.<br />
 They have made their faces harder than rock;<br />
  they have refused to repent.<br /></p>

<p>[4] Then I said, “These are only the poor;<br />
  they have no sense;<br />
 for they do not know the way of the LORD,<br />
  the justice of their God.<br />
 [5] I will go to the great<br />
  and will speak to them,<br />
 for they know the way of the LORD,<br />
  the justice of their God.”<br />
 But they all alike had broken the yoke;<br />
  they had burst the bonds. (ESV)<br /></p>

<hr />

<p>Isaiah 59:14–17</p>

<p>Judgment and Redemption</p>

<p>[14] Justice is turned back,<br />
  and righteousness stands far away;<br />
 for truth has stumbled in the public squares,<br />
  and uprightness cannot enter.<br />
 [15] Truth is lacking,<br />
  and he who departs from evil makes himself a prey.<br /></p>

<p>The LORD saw it, and it displeased him<br />
  that there was no justice.<br />
 [16] He saw that there was no man,<br />
  and wondered that there was no one to intercede;<br />
 then his own arm brought him salvation,<br />
  and his righteousness upheld him.<br />
 [17] He put on righteousness as a breastplate,<br />
  and a helmet of salvation on his head;<br />
 he put on garments of vengeance for clothing,<br />
  and wrapped himself in zeal as a cloak. (ESV)<br /></p>

<hr />

<p><img src="/rC2HGNNWR3JzrY4ngY.jpg" alt="Father forgive them, for I literally can't even" /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday was the second time someone told me that trying to save other people is a sign of pride. They also kindly informed me that I’m an egomaniac who believes that I might be a chosen one. Unlike the first time, it was slightly better this time since it came from a Christian. Although, does that make it worse? I don’t know. I’m not sure I know how to spell good and evil anymore. Let me know if you know how to spell good and evil. Thanks.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Love</title><link href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-love/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Love" /><published>2025-02-24T23:26:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-02-24T23:26:00+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/posts/on-love</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-love/"><![CDATA[<p>In the last couple of days, my Chinese missionary guide has stopped responding to my messages. Based on the sentiment of our latest messages, I can tell my welcoming party, which the Lord prepared for me in the UK 11.5 years ago, is starting to withdraw. I read the following passages from 2 Thessalonians yesterday.</p>

<hr />

<p>2 Thessalonians 2:1–12</p>

<p>The Man of Lawlessness</p>

<p>[1] Now concerning the coming of our Lord Jesus Christ and our being gathered together to him, we ask you, brothers, [2] not to be quickly shaken in mind or alarmed, either by a spirit or a spoken word, or a letter seeming to be from us, to the effect that the day of the Lord has come. [3] Let no one deceive you in any way. For that day will not come, unless the rebellion comes first, and the man of lawlessness is revealed, the son of destruction, [4] who opposes and exalts himself against every so-called god or object of worship, so that he takes his seat in the temple of God, proclaiming himself to be God. [5] Do you not remember that when I was still with you I told you these things? [6] And you know what is restraining him now so that he may be revealed in his time. [7] For the mystery of lawlessness is already at work. Only he who now restrains it will do so until he is out of the way. [8] And then the lawless one will be revealed, whom the Lord Jesus will kill with the breath of his mouth and bring to nothing by the appearance of his coming. [9] The coming of the lawless one is by the activity of Satan with all power and false signs and wonders, [10] and with all wicked deception for those who are perishing, because they refused to love the truth and so be saved. [11] Therefore God sends them a strong delusion, so that they may believe what is false, [12] in order that all may be condemned who did not believe the truth but had pleasure in unrighteousness. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>As alluded to multiple times in my previous posts, epistemologically there are only three things that I know. He exists, He loves me, and I exist, in that precise order of precedence. And before my welcoming party bashes me again for using pronouns, He is my Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ, whose last known appearance on earth was around 2,000 years ago. Besides that, everything else is a belief that can be subject to doubt and reasoning. I picture my knowledge system as a tree, and each new branch is rooted in one or more branches. Each branch has a variable belief probability that indicates my confidence when understanding the world through the fruits of that branch. My root branch was drifting in the sea of knowledge after reading Descartes’ <em>Meditations on First Philosophy</em> during COVID-19 and nearly got burnt in the fire that is existentialism, nihilism and antinatalism. Six months ago, He came and firmly attached my root to the vine that is my Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ.</p>

<p>After getting kicked out of the gay/bi-sexual naturist campsite Rosebay in late July last year, I felt His love for the first time when standing on Oxford Street in central London one evening. I checked my WhatsApp messages and Amazon order history. I placed the order for my first Holy Bible after that evening. I realised the reason why it hurt that much was because I loved everyone at the campsite and getting kicked out smashed my heart into pieces. And after picking a fight with nature for three months, I also loved nature and all the new interests and possibilities I started to explore. I asked myself how much I love and using the equation of love I derived at age 16, I realised I was willing to take a bullet for any stranger that was walking past me that evening. That was the precise moment I felt His love for the first time.</p>

<p>My welcoming party taught me quite early on that regardless of what I do with the Holy Spirit and spiritual gifts, I should do it with love, faith and hope, and love always comes first. In case there is any doubt, the equation of love is the greatest amount of sacrifice one is willing to make.</p>

<p>I have been searching my heart and soul ever since getting kicked out of Rosebay. Despite my entire world turning on me in my early teenage years, Rosebay and now, I believe I gave more than I took in this life. The only other possibility that I can think of is I have successfully deceived myself, in which case I deserve burning in hell for eternity and I will accept any judgment He has for me regardless. I will leave judgement to Him, it’s too heavy a task for a mere servant like me and I’m just gonna get the homecoming party ready.</p>

<p>I will see you at sunrise.</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="hebrews-1113">Hebrews 11:1–3</h2>

<p>By Faith</p>

<p>[1] Now faith is the assurance of things hoped for, the conviction of things not seen. [2] For by it the people of old received their commendation. [3] By faith we understand that the universe was created by the word of God, so that what is seen was not made out of things that are visible. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="romans-11617">Romans 1:16–17</h2>

<p>The Righteous Shall Live by Faith</p>

<p>[16] For I am not ashamed of the gospel, for it is the power of God for salvation to everyone who believes, to the Jew first and also to the Greek. [17] For in it the righteousness of God is revealed from faith for faith, as it is written, “The righteous shall live by faith.” (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="galatians-216">Galatians 2:16</h2>

<p>[16] yet we know that a person is not justified by works of the law but through faith in Jesus Christ, so we also have believed in Christ Jesus, in order to be justified by faith in Christ and not by works of the law, because by works of the law no one will be justified. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="mark-112025">Mark 11:20–25</h2>

<p>The Lesson from the Withered Fig Tree</p>

<p>[20] As they passed by in the morning, they saw the fig tree withered away to its roots. [21] And Peter remembered and said to him, “Rabbi, look! The fig tree that you cursed has withered.” [22] And Jesus answered them, “Have faith in God. [23] Truly, I say to you, whoever says to this mountain, ‘Be taken up and thrown into the sea,’ and does not doubt in his heart, but believes that what he says will come to pass, it will be done for him. [24] Therefore I tell you, whatever you ask in prayer, believe that you have received it, and it will be yours. [25] And whenever you stand praying, forgive, if you have anything against anyone, so that your Father also who is in heaven may forgive you your trespasses.” (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="matthew-171920">Matthew 17:19–20</h2>

<p>[19] Then the disciples came to Jesus privately and said, “Why could we not cast it out?” [20] He said to them, “Because of your little faith. For truly, I say to you, if you have faith like a grain of mustard seed, you will say to this mountain, ‘Move from here to there,’ and it will move, and nothing will be impossible for you.” (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="2-corinthians-5610">2 Corinthians 5:6–10</h2>

<p>[6] So we are always of good courage. We know that while we are at home in the body we are away from the Lord, [7] for we walk by faith, not by sight. [8] Yes, we are of good courage, and we would rather be away from the body and at home with the Lord. [9] So whether we are at home or away, we make it our aim to please him. [10] For we must all appear before the judgment seat of Christ, so that each one may receive what is due for what he has done in the body, whether good or evil. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="glorious---song-by-macklemore"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7OrLroFa0AI" target="_blank">Glorious - Song by Macklemore</a></h2>

<p>[Verse 1: Macklemore]<br />
You know I’m back, like I never left (I never left)<br />
Another sprint, another step (Another step)<br />
Another day, another breath (Another breath)<br />
Been chasing dreams, but I never slept (I never slept)<br />
I got a new attitude and a lease on life and some peace of mind<br />
Seek and I find, I can sleep when I die<br />
Want a piece of the pie, grab the keys to the ride<br />
And shit I’m straight, I’m on my wave, I’m on my wave<br />
Get out my wake, I’m running late, what can I say?<br />
I heard you die twice, once when they bury you in the grave<br />
And the second time is the last time that somebody mentions your name<br />
So when I leave here on this earth, did I take more than I gave?<br />
Did I look out for the people, or did I do it all for fame?<br />
Legend, it’s exodus, searching for euphoria<br />
Trudging through the mud to find the present, no ignoring us<br />
Got 20,000 deep off in the street like we some warriors<br />
My mama told me never bow your head, woo<br /></p>

<p>[Chorus: Skylar Grey]<br />
I feel glorious, glorious<br />
Got a chance to start again<br />
I was born for this, born for this<br />
It’s who I am, how could I forget?<br />
I made it through the darkest part of the night<br />
And now I see the sunrise<br />
Now I feel glorious, glorious<br />
I feel glorious, glorious<br /></p>

<p>[Verse 2: Macklemore]<br />
I’m feeling glorious<br />
The crib looking Victorian (Oh yes it is)<br />
You know that we been going in (Been going in)<br />
Since we hopped out that DeLorean (DeLorean, yeah we win)<br />
En garde, things are just things, they don’t make you who you are<br />
Can’t pack up a U-Haul and take it with you when you’re gone<br />
We posted on the porch, my family’s glasses to the stars<br />
My grandma smiling down on me like “Woo, that boy got bars”<br />
Okay, okay, yes I do<br />
I said amen and hallelujah, let me testify too<br />
Another morning, a morning, won’t let self get in my way<br />
I got my breath, I got my faith and I remember why I came, woo<br /></p>

<p>[Chorus: Skylar Grey]<br />
I feel glorious, glorious<br />
Got a chance to start again<br />
I was born for this, born for this<br />
It’s who I am, how could I forget?<br />
I made it through the darkest part of the night<br />
And now I see the sunrise<br />
Now I feel glorious, glorious<br />
I feel glorious, glorious<br /></p>

<p>[Bridge: Skylar Grey]<br />
We gon’ be alright, put that on my life<br />
When I open my eyes, hope I see you shine<br />
We’re planting a flag, they don’t understand<br />
The world is up for grabs (Hey, hey, hey)<br />
We gon’ be alright, put that on my life<br />
When I open my eyes, hope I see you shine<br />
We’re planting a flag, they don’t understand<br />
The world is up for grabs (Hey, hey, hey)<br /></p>

<p>[Chorus: Skylar Grey]<br />
I feel glorious, glorious<br />
Got a chance to start again<br />
I was born for this, born for this<br />
It’s who I am, how could I forget?<br />
I made it through the darkest part of the night<br />
And now I see the sunrise<br />
Now I feel glorious, glorious<br />
I feel glorious, glorious<br /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last couple of days, my Chinese missionary guide has stopped responding to my messages. Based on the sentiment of our latest messages, I can tell my welcoming party, which the Lord prepared for me in the UK 11.5 years ago, is starting to withdraw. I read the following passages from 2 Thessalonians yesterday.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Gethsemane</title><link href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-gethsemane/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Gethsemane" /><published>2025-02-22T07:57:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-02-23T07:24:23+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/posts/on-gethsemane</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-gethsemane/"><![CDATA[<p>I had a pretty long night and just had my <a href="https://www.esv.org/Matthew+26:36/" target="_blank">Gethsemane moment</a>.</p>

<p>I gave a rather big talk yesterday on the announcement post, which is now the only pinned post on my blog. I mentioned a theological thought experiment that I used to test whether the person I was speaking to believed in God in <a href="../on-choosing-sides/" target="_blank">an early post</a>.</p>

<p>If God asks you to choose between Him and mankind and mankind has turned its back on Him, which side would you choose?</p>

<p>Over the last couple of hours, He showed me a path where I could take a leap of faith by choosing Him, but instead of mankind turning its back on Him, mankind turned its back on me and I would be misunderstood by every human being on earth. The exact scenario I described in <a href="../on-great-tribulation/#edit-5" target="_blank">Edit 5</a> yesterday and He showed me a realistic path to that by making the last log in my eye known to me.</p>

<p>I had around a handful of panic attacks in the 28 years of my life and only 1 or 2 of them were severe enough for me to lose eyesight, but they were pretty much over within a couple of minutes. I don’t know how long my panic attack was earlier, but my estimate was at least half an hour and my entire upper body was soaked in sweat. I told Him yes and started planning the practical steps to implement that over the next 24 hours, with an extremely weird lightness and frankly outright creepy smile.</p>

<p>Then.</p>

<p>Dude picked up the biggest burden I did not know existed, slapped it on the cross, lit it on fire, and told me it was on da house and go play.</p>

<p>Motherf…</p>

<hr />

<p>Matthew 7:1–6</p>

<p>Judging Others</p>

<p>[1] “Judge not, that you be not judged. [2] For with the judgment you pronounce you will be judged, and with the measure you use it will be measured to you. [3] Why do you see the speck that is in your brother’s eye, but do not notice the log that is in your own eye? [4] Or how can you say to your brother, ‘Let me take the speck out of your eye,’ when there is the log in your own eye? [5] You hypocrite, first take the log out of your own eye, and then you will see clearly to take the speck out of your brother’s eye.</p>

<p>[6] “Do not give dogs what is holy, and do not throw your pearls before pigs, lest they trample them underfoot and turn to attack you. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p><img src="/xpnDGthytwZv6bCSyg.jpg" alt="" />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br /></p>
<h1 id="jesus-christ-is-my-lord-and-saviour">Jesus Christ is my Lord and Saviour.</h1>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I had a pretty long night and just had my Gethsemane moment.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Sexual Theology</title><link href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-sexual-theology/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Sexual Theology" /><published>2025-02-20T23:32:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-02-21T23:12:40+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/posts/on-sexual-theology</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-sexual-theology/"><![CDATA[<p>Originally, I wrote another long-winded draft on seggs referencing all sorts of relevant passages I found using AI. As a massive lazy ass like Jonah, I didn’t even get through half of the passages returned by OpenAI before deciding not to bother. If you <strong>DID NOT FAIL</strong> logical reasoning <strong>AND</strong> reading comprehension in school, then you could cheat with AI like using <a href="https://biblesays.love/" target="_blank">this tool</a> that I built using ChatGPT or train a LLM if you are a nerd like me, and then carefully reason about whether the Lord would be okay for you to try the creative activity you have in mind that might involve your and hopefully your partner’s no-go areas. I devised two lazy rules to clock out early from Boss Man. Dude’s been nagging me since Hong Kong back in October, but to be fair I would probably continue sitting on my <a href="../on-background-music/" target="_blank">get-out-of-jail-free card</a> for a couple of months if He didn’t start nagging me since then.</p>

<p>Rule 1: Love always comes first which means the creative activity should be giving rather than taking in nature, and the answer is <strong>NO</strong> if the activity has a non-zero probability of giving you even the slightest idea (Matthew 5:27-30) of taking from or exploiting other people.</p>

<p>Rule 2: Lust which focuses on self-gratification and taking is a gigantic <strong>NO-NO</strong>.</p>

<p>Rule 1 + Rule 2 = Don’t be <a href="../on-commandments-and-the-law/#definition-of-a-cunt" target="_blank">a cunt</a>.</p>

<p>This is ChatGPT explaining it and my sexual theologian job title lasted just over 24 hours.</p>

<embed src="https://dl.hesaid.love/Lust_vs_Love.pdf" type="application/pdf" width="100%" height="300px" />

<hr />

<p>The easiest is to ask our Heavenly Father for the Holy Spirit and get to know Him. Double check with the Holy Spirit whether what you have in mind is acceptable using the <a href="../on-positive-only-hmi/" target="_blank">Holy Spirit Positive-Only HMI</a>. I asked the Holy Spirit if I could refer to Him as the Spiritual Condom. I don’t think Bro’s a big fan of that so nvm.</p>

<p><img src="/9yAr35Btsyf4hKfrhf.jpg" alt="" target="_blank" /></p>

<hr />

<p>Below is the <strong>extremely NSFW</strong> director cut of my <a href="../on-sacrifice/" target="_blank"><del>New Year</del></a> New Millennium present, and a boring example of love rather than lust. I read the Book of Hebrews yesterday. The Hall of Faith in Hebrews was too interesting. I thought that having something I believed in and was willing to die for, was in <a href="../on-suffering/" target="_blank">itself a big enough reward</a> already after not believing even myself for my entire life. I had no idea there were blessings until my third sermon at China Congregational Church, Hong Kong that weekend and the pastor smiled and only responded that there would be blessings to come, after I went 6,000 miles in 5 minutes as usual. I was wondering what he was smiling about. I got annoyed again earlier this evening.</p>

<p>
  <video class="embed-video file" controls="">
    
    

    
    
    

    

    
      
      
      
      <source src="https://dl.hesaid.love/love_not_lust.mp4" type="video/mp4" />
    

    Your browser does not support the video tag. Here is a
    <a href="https://dl.hesaid.love/love_not_lust.mp4">link to the video file</a> instead.
  </video>
  
</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Originally, I wrote another long-winded draft on seggs referencing all sorts of relevant passages I found using AI. As a massive lazy ass like Jonah, I didn’t even get through half of the passages returned by OpenAI before deciding not to bother. If you DID NOT FAIL logical reasoning AND reading comprehension in school, then you could cheat with AI like using this tool that I built using ChatGPT or train a LLM if you are a nerd like me, and then carefully reason about whether the Lord would be okay for you to try the creative activity you have in mind that might involve your and hopefully your partner’s no-go areas. I devised two lazy rules to clock out early from Boss Man. Dude’s been nagging me since Hong Kong back in October, but to be fair I would probably continue sitting on my get-out-of-jail-free card for a couple of months if He didn’t start nagging me since then.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Great Tribulation</title><link href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-great-tribulation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Great Tribulation" /><published>2025-02-20T21:02:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-02-22T02:47:48+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/posts/on-great-tribulation</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-great-tribulation/"><![CDATA[<h3 id="edit-5">Edit 5</h3>

<p>This post is to announce the end of the great tribulation. And to proclaim the Day of the Lord and the year of the Lord’s favour as described in humanity’s bestseller the Holy Bible. Unlike most people, I did not trust myself even once in the last 28 years of my life. Yet, I stand by every single word I wrote down in all blog posts in accurately expressing the sentiment and the severity of the situations, no matter how ridiculous, ugly, profane or even blasphemous you might find my language in your measurement.</p>

<p>I have read less than 25% of the Holy Bible and I believe you can resolve the questions you might have regarding my posts using only the Holy Bible. I don’t know if I’m telling the truth. I believe I’m telling the truth, the whole truth and nothing but the truth to a degree that I as a mere mortal human being am capable of grasping. If you are unable to clarify any questions you have, ask our Lord and Saviour, Jesus Christ, don’t ask me. I don’t know and I don’t lean on my own understanding. I found the best choice. I trust my Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ and that’s more than sufficient for me, even if that means I will stand trial in front of God almighty, burn in hell for eternity and be condemned by every single human being on this earth. I believe I have a clear conscience in front of God. I don’t know and I don’t need to know. I have confirmation from the Holy Spirit and will happily accept whatever judgment He has for me.</p>

<p>My question for you is this. Can you bear to finish reading my posts before you come up with your own judgment and inform me about your opinion, or simply give up? My educated guess is those who can are few. You don’t need to reply. This is not about me. This is about your salvation and between you and Him.</p>

<hr />

<p>Matthew 7:13–14</p>

<p>[13] “Enter by the narrow gate. For the gate is wide and the way is easy that leads to destruction, and those who enter by it are many. [14] For the gate is narrow and the way is hard that leads to life, and those who find it are few. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>P.S. This edit was originally for the mistake I found when going back to cross-check the things I wrote in this post, given how outrageous the claims I’m making are. The mistake I found is pretty big. The videos I watched during COVID-19 to learn about quantum physics and relevant epistemological/philosophical arguments that inspired my subsequent thinking in existentialism, nihilism and antinatalism are in fact from the World Science Festival rather than World Science Forum. I must jumped after my findings and didn’t realise this WSF is not that WSF. YouTube will show me the World Science Festival if I search World Science Forum. I thought about whether I should correct that and asked the Holy Spirit. I remembered this passage from the legendary Mr Noisy Gong.</p>

<hr />

<p>Romans 8:26–30</p>

<p>[26] Likewise the Spirit helps us in our weakness. For we do not know what to pray for as we ought, but the Spirit himself intercedes for us with groanings too deep for words. [27] And he who searches hearts knows what is the mind of the Spirit, because the Spirit intercedes for the saints according to the will of God. [28] And we know that for those who love God all things work together for good, for those who are called according to his purpose. [29] For those whom he foreknew he also predestined to be conformed to the image of his Son, in order that he might be the firstborn among many brothers. [30] And those whom he predestined he also called, and those whom he called he also justified, and those whom he justified he also glorified. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p><img src="/TqrCp3s2K06SRSRxnn.jpg" alt="" /></p>

<p>However, the mistake is so big and embarrassing that Mr Noisy Gong, a.k.a. Apostle Paul’s words are not enough. So here is my Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ with a tiny shove by Spotify.</p>

<p>Matthew 19:26</p>

<p>[26] But Jesus looked at them and said, “With man this is impossible, but with God all things are possible.” (ESV)</p>

<p><img src="/3hmAKxqyxthJJrzaFF.png" alt="" /></p>

<p><img src="/VRF7AMjKSg6g6MrFMx.png" alt="" /></p>

<p>I decided not to worry about it and go play. I think it’s fair to say I have worried enough for everyone now and some people can take some responsibilities and worry for themselves. They don’t seem to spend much time worrying for others anyway. I don’t know what they do all day, to be honest, other than taking selfies.</p>

<h3 id="edit-2">Edit 2</h3>

<p><strong>I realised my language doesn’t necessarily encourage people to keep on reading, but I said truth over appearances at the beginning since the world has gotten way too fake. So I’m just going to sincerely apologise here once again after the hundreds of apologies I have already made. I genuinely believe you will understand my use of language if you finish reading. Thanks.</strong></p>

<hr />

<h3 id="edit-3">Edit 3</h3>

<p>I just realised something quite unfortunate that I never understood before in The Final Judgement. I had always wondered why repeated the same pattern in Matthew 25:44 given the same was said in more detail through Matthew 25:37-39, and <strong>why would they not recognise the Lord when they believed they knew the Lord</strong>. I think they are there through cumbersome elaborateness to make me realise the scribes and Pharisees who did not bother to look into the evidence before referring me to mental health services are exactly the ones who won’t recognise the Lord. <strong>I’m not saying I’m the Lord, I’m saying they never knew the Lord in the first place and if they would not allow someone like me to even present the evidence that I have encountered the Lord, how could they possibly recognise the Lord when He comes back?</strong></p>

<p><strong>This is first-degree self-deception caught in the act, unfortunately. Karma is a bitch, but I sincerely hope I’m not the fucking messiah for their fucking sake and there is still time for them to repent.</strong></p>

<p><strong>Will you believe me when I say I never wanted to be the fucking messiah now?</strong></p>

<hr />

<p>Matthew 25:31–46</p>

<p>The Final Judgment</p>

<p>[31] “When the Son of Man comes in his glory, and all the angels with him, then he will sit on his glorious throne. [32] Before him will be gathered all the nations, and he will separate people one from another as a shepherd separates the sheep from the goats. [33] And he will place the sheep on his right, but the goats on the left. [34] Then the King will say to those on his right, ‘Come, you who are blessed by my Father, inherit the kingdom prepared for you from the foundation of the world. [35] For I was hungry and you gave me food, I was thirsty and you gave me drink, I was a stranger and you welcomed me, [36] I was naked and you clothed me, I was sick and you visited me, I was in prison and you came to me.’ [37] Then the righteous will answer him, saying, ‘Lord, when did we see you hungry and feed you, or thirsty and give you drink? [38] And when did we see you a stranger and welcome you, or naked and clothe you? [39] And when did we see you sick or in prison and visit you?’ [40] And the King will answer them, ‘Truly, I say to you, as you did it to one of the least of these my brothers, you did it to me.’</p>

<p>[41] “Then he will say to those on his left, ‘Depart from me, you cursed, into the eternal fire prepared for the devil and his angels. [42] For I was hungry and you gave me no food, I was thirsty and you gave me no drink, [43] I was a stranger and you did not welcome me, naked and you did not clothe me, sick and in prison and you did not visit me.’ [44] Then they also will answer, saying, ‘Lord, when did we see you hungry or thirsty or a stranger or naked or sick or in prison, and did not minister to you?’ [45] Then he will answer them, saying, ‘Truly, I say to you, as you did not do it to one of the least of these, you did not do it to me.’ [46] And these will go away into eternal punishment, but the righteous into eternal life.” (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h3 id="edit-4">Edit 4</h3>

<p><a href="https://dl.hesaid.love/love_not_lust.mp4" target="_blank">Fuck me</a>. I just realised the implications of what I had just proved in Edit 3. Now I find <a href="../on-background-music/#malachi-3-1" target="_blank">Malachi 3:1 even more annoying</a> and have zero desire to laugh. It does not feel great when you find out you are the fool all along, right? 🤡</p>

<p>Since we have announced the <strong>year of the Lord’s favour</strong> below, might as well do the <strong>Day of the Lord</strong> together. I seem to always run ahead of Boss Man and keep tripping over. I thought the Day of the Lord was why He told me to go to Israel last month. You can find out what happened by looking up the relevant posts yourself and I’m going to stop putting effort into hyperlinking everything. It takes a fuck ton of effort and barely anyone read my posts if I didn’t sprinkle the nations to shove my posts to your fucking faces. And the fucking scribes and Pharisees did not <a href="https://dl.hesaid.love/scribes_and_pharisees.pdf" target="_blank">fucking bother to reply</a> to any single fucking email other than the first couple fucking courtesy responses.</p>

<p>You can find out what happens on the day yourself and for the first time in my life, I think I’m seriously going to not bother this time and you can all go fuck yourselves. I thought Malachi 3:2 might not mean what people think they mean when I read it last month in Israel. The only thing I have left to say is Dude’s math is confusing AF and I technically dropped out of my maths and CS degree after only one term so I know dick about math either. I know dick about how long the Day of the Lord is, could be one day, one week, one month or one year, but I suspect it won’t be longer than one year otherwise why have the Day of the Lord and the year of the Lord’s favour? You will know what I’m on about if you seriously tried reading humanity’s bestseller before. Ask Boss Man if you really wanna know, I’m not gonna bother and I’m certain I will have at least 10x more fun watching people get what they deserve while getting surprised by the King of Drama and Horror, wouldn’t you agree? I think it’s called justice and righteousness and I hope that’s how you spell them since I haven’t seen those two words for a while now. Just need to find a couple of faithful new friends, never bold enough to watch horror movies myself and ideally they have a comfy sofa I can crash on.</p>

<p>If you are a faithful believer, then congratulations. Happy New Millennium and you are more than welcome.</p>

<p>If you are <a href="../on-commandments-and-the-law/#definition-of-a-cunt" target="_blank">an unfaithful motherfucking cunt</a>, <a href="https://dl.hesaid.love/love_not_lust.mp4" target="_blank">go fuck yourself</a>. 🖕</p>

<p>I’m gonna Bible and chill. Have read probably less than 25% of the thick-ass bestseller. Only flipped through Genesis and up to Exodus 10ish one evening late last year out of the 5 books of The Law.</p>

<p><img src="/qvsGSPQhsuPSTfJV1p.png" alt="" /></p>

<hr />

<h3 id="edit-1">Edit 1</h3>

<p>In case you are so fucking stupid and ignorant to not know <a href="https://letter.hesaid.love/" target="_blank">you are losing your job within 2 years</a> if you don’t have a degree more complicated than computer science, you can read my lazy-ass research using ChatGPT <a href="https://dl.hesaid.love/1335_Days_and_Tribulation.pdf" target="_blank">here</a>. Feel free to ignore if you are in the top 1%, otherwise let’s see if the people telling you not to worry will help you when shit hits the fan and whether they stand to gain or lose from your downfall and stupidity.</p>

<p>See ya on judgement day. Might be a good idea to get <a href="https://www.gotquestions.org/famine-hearing-words-Lord.html" target="_blank">Amazon Prime</a>. 🙏😅😂</p>

<p>Just a quick reminder in case some stupid cunts want to try some idiotic shit. Ask yourselves if you know how to spell Boss Man’s name first. I would advise you to save it, but sometimes you simply cannot stop stupid fucking cunts. <a href="../on-overemployment" target="_blank">Kill shot only</a> otherwise I personally guarantee you will be more thoroughly fucked than <a href="../on-sexual-theology/" target="_blank">this</a>.</p>

<hr />

<p>Revelation 17:14</p>

<p>[14] They will make war on the Lamb, and the Lamb will conquer them, for he is Lord of lords and King of kings, and those with him are called and chosen and faithful.” (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="antichrist--mark-of-the-beast--666">Antichrist / Mark of the Beast / 666</h2>

<div style="display: flex; justify-content: space-between;">
  <img src="https://dl.hesaid.love/666/Screenshot_20250220-152638.png" alt="" style="width: 48%;" />
  <img src="https://dl.hesaid.love/666/Screenshot_20250220-152529.png" alt="" style="width: 48%;" />
</div>

<div style="display: flex; justify-content: space-between;">
  <img src="https://dl.hesaid.love/666/Screenshot_20250220-152314.png" alt="" style="width: 48%;" />
  <img src="https://dl.hesaid.love/666/Screenshot_20250220-152332.png" alt="" style="width: 48%;" />
</div>

<div style="display: flex; justify-content: space-between;">
  <img src="https://dl.hesaid.love/666/photo_2025-02-20_21-47-06.jpg" alt="" style="width: 50%;" />
  <img src="https://dl.hesaid.love/666/photo_2025-02-20_21-47-16.jpg" alt="" style="width: 50%;" />
  <img src="https://dl.hesaid.love/666/photo_2025-02-20_21-47-12.jpg" alt="" style="width: 50%;" />
</div>

<h2 id="abomination-of-desolation-on-july-1999">Abomination of Desolation on July 1999</h2>

<p>Halfway through the 1,260 + <a href="https://www.esv.org/Daniel+12/" target="_blank">1,260 + 30 + 45</a> weeks.</p>

<p>I arrived at the gay/bi-naturist Rosebay campsite 45 weeks ago.</p>

<p><a href="https://unesdoc.unesco.org/ark:/48223/pf0000122938" target="_blank">UNESCO Digital Library</a></p>

<embed src="https://dl.hesaid.love/666/122938engo.pdf" type="application/pdf" width="100%" height="600px" />

<h2 id="backups">Backups</h2>

<p><a href="https://666.antichrist.boo" target="_blank">666.antichrist.boo</a></p>

<p><a href="ipfs://bafybeies6vl2tm5ibnbdl44x3jzw2blmycpzmhzggikgm2j5w4l3kilq2m" target="_blank">IPFS (feel free to pin the CID)</a> ipfs://bafybeies6vl2tm5ibnbdl44x3jzw2blmycpzmhzggikgm2j5w4l3kilq2m</p>

<hr />

<p>In case you didn’t get it, <a href="../on-he-as-aod/" target="_blank">higher education</a> is full of spiritually desolate late-teenage to early-twenties <a href="../on-we-all-die/" target="_blank">nihilists</a>/<a href="../on-indifference/" target="_blank">anarchists</a> with <a href="../on-drug-money-addiction/" target="_blank">drug addictions</a> and they can <a href="../on-faith-precedes-reason/" target="_blank">neither reason nor read</a>. Institutions proclaiming to dedicate their time and resources to the truth are interested in nothing other than more drugs (a.k.a. money and business schools), the school of philosophy has already fallen under the four horsemen existentialism, nihilism, antinatalism and death as always, and the <a href="../on-faith-precedes-reason/" target="_blank">stupid mother fucking egomaniacs</a> hiding behind jargon and publications have the mother fucking audacity to compare theology with the study of unicorns and fairytales.</p>

<p>I found the gentleman and the abomination above via the <a href="https://worldscienceforum.org/" target="_blank">World Science Forum</a>. I learned most of my quantum physics and relevant epistemological/philosophical knowledge by watching their videos on YouTube during COVID-19. All of my subsequent thinking and reasoning concerning existentialism, nihilism and antinatalism can all be attributed back to them. <strong>The only way I found to overcome the terminal illness of nihilism is by voluntarily taking up your cross (responsibilities) and following Him. Otherwise, whether I choose to throw myself out of the balcony today is as meaningless as whether I choose to pick up a knife and stab someone as long as I can get away with it under the law.</strong></p>

<p>I found the 46-page manifesto in the UNESCO Digital Library above via <a href="https://worldscienceforum.org/contents/history-of-world-science-forum-110010" target="_blank">the history page of the World Science Forum</a>. The impression I got after quickly scrolling through the document was it made a ton of bold claims on ethics and essentially by saying scientific knowledge alone can bring good to humanity. The only thing it left out? God. Do we know how to spell good and evil? I don’t know.</p>

<p>I found a certain gentleman who may or may not have been mentioned in this post and he dedicated rather generously his time and effort to the various scientific organisations behind the scenes, which I found to be rather interesting for a direct descendent of a well-known figure who allegedly was a prophet and messenger of God, but I couldn’t seem to find the name in humanity’s bestseller, which I consider to be telling the truth, the whole truth and nothing but the truth. The gentleman certainly has an appetite to cross fields including politics. Kinda like me, but I’m confident my fellow pretentious Oxford alumni are more than capable of fucking the world up and it would be wise to dedicate my time instead to futile pursuits such as salvation.</p>

<p><strong>And no, I’m not the fucking messiah. I’m just a servant running around preparing the homecoming party for Boss Man.</strong> Although, I genuinely don’t know what some self-proclaimed Christians are thinking most of the time. Throughout this journey, I wanted nothing other than someone to slap me the fuck awake with the annoyingly thick humanity’s bestseller, they did everything including referring me to mental health services and suggesting I must be an egomaniac <strong>except</strong> looking at the evidence I was serving up on a platter and reason with me. None of them reply to my messages and emails anymore.</p>

<p>I wonder if they truly want the messiah or not, and why the fuck is everyone just sitting around waiting for the one fucking messiah? Do you know how big of a fucking job that is for Boss Man and how much did each of us contribute after 2,000 fucking years? If I was in Boss Man’s shoes then I would rather just let this fucking wicked world burn while I Netflix and chill than save a bunch of lazy ass mother fuckers who neither reason nor read.</p>

<p>How about you do your part, I do mine, Boss Man does His and let’s find out on the other side what we are?</p>

<p>Happy New Millennium if you are not <a href="../on-commandments-and-the-law/#definition-of-a-cunt" target="_blank">an unfaithful motherfucking cunt</a> <strong>AND</strong> most importantly not a self-proclaimed “believer” who doesn’t want Boss Man to come back.</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="rivers---song-by-thomas-jack"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sqYEvGr372M" target="_blank">Rivers - Song by Thomas Jack</a></h2>

<p>We’re like rivers in the night<br />
I go left and you go right<br />
We’ll find out on the other side<br />
Who we are, who we are<br />
Wish me luck and give me hope<br />
Give me sunlight to my day<br />
Turn it into gold<br />
Carry on, carry on<br /></p>

<p>We’ll take these broken souls<br />
Make them as good as new<br />
Bind it together into something we could never lose<br />
We’re rivers in the night<br />
I go left and you go right<br />
We’ll find out on the other side<br />
Who we are, who we are<br /></p>

<p>We can make it onto something beautiful<br />
Yeah, we don’t have to try<br />
We can make it into something wonderful<br />
We’ll never say goodbye<br /></p>

<hr />

<h2 id="isaiah-61--the-year-of-the-lords-favor">Isaiah 61 <br /><br /> The Year of the LORD’s Favor</h2>

<pre><code class="language-none">
[1] The Spirit of the Lord GOD is upon me,
    because the LORD has anointed me
to bring good news to the poor;
    he has sent me to bind up the brokenhearted,
to proclaim liberty to the captives,
    and the opening of the prison to those who are bound;
[2] to proclaim the year of the LORD’s favor,
    and the day of vengeance of our God;
    to comfort all who mourn;
[3] to grant to those who mourn in Zion—
    to give them a beautiful headdress instead of ashes,
the oil of gladness instead of mourning,
    the garment of praise instead of a faint spirit;
that they may be called oaks of righteousness,
    the planting of the LORD, that he may be glorified.
[4] They shall build up the ancient ruins;
    they shall raise up the former devastations;
they shall repair the ruined cities,
    the devastations of many generations.


[5] Strangers shall stand and tend your flocks;
    foreigners shall be your plowmen and vinedressers;
[6] but you shall be called the priests of the LORD;
    they shall speak of you as the ministers of our God;
you shall eat the wealth of the nations,
    and in their glory you shall boast.
[7] Instead of your shame there shall be a double portion;
    instead of dishonor they shall rejoice in their lot;
therefore in their land they shall possess a double portion;
    they shall have everlasting joy.


[8] For I the LORD love justice;
    I hate robbery and wrong;
I will faithfully give them their recompense,
    and I will make an everlasting covenant with them.
[9] Their offspring shall be known among the nations,
    and their descendants in the midst of the peoples;
all who see them shall acknowledge them,
    that they are an offspring the LORD has blessed.


[10] I will greatly rejoice in the LORD;
    my soul shall exult in my God,
for he has clothed me with the garments of salvation;
    he has covered me with the robe of righteousness,
as a bridegroom decks himself like a priest with a beautiful headdress,
    and as a bride adorns herself with her jewels.
[11] For as the earth brings forth its sprouts,
    and as a garden causes what is sown in it to sprout up,
so the Lord GOD will cause righteousness and praise
    to sprout up before all the nations. (ESV)
</code></pre>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the end of the great tribulation. Proclaiming the Day of the Lord and the year of the Lord’s favour as described in humanity’s bestseller the Holy Bible.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://hesaid.love/6e760355a4f2267fc6c3900624861241.jpeg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://hesaid.love/6e760355a4f2267fc6c3900624861241.jpeg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">On Positive-Only HMI</title><link href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-positive-only-hmi/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Positive-Only HMI" /><published>2025-02-20T09:03:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-02-21T23:12:40+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/posts/on-positive-only-hmi</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-positive-only-hmi/"><![CDATA[<p>This is a simple introduction to the <a href="../on-holy-spirit-miracles/" target="_blank">Holy Spirit</a> Positive-Only Human-Machine Interface (HSPOHMI). If our Heavenly Father has not bestowed Him on you yet, ask Him for the Holy Spirit. You might have some soul-searching to do. I <a href="../on-anger-faith/" target="_blank">asked Him once</a> last July and He came five weeks later. I was technically being philosophically dramatic.</p>

<p>*Only <a href="../on-holy-spirit/" target="_blank">sensorial type</a> Holy Spirit is supported right now.</p>

<p>Ask your church pastor about the Holy Spirit and cross-check <strong>everything they tell you</strong> with scripture. If they are unfamiliar with the Holy Spirit or your church service is not led by the Holy Spirit, they are likely false teachers. Tell the pastor <strong>they violated the third commandment</strong> and find a new church led by the Holy Spirit if the sermons smell like <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Humanism" target="_blank">stinky humanism</a> and they only teach the soft stuff in the New Testament.</p>

<h3 id="compulsory-login-credentials-1-john-42">Compulsory login credentials (<a href="https://www.biblegateway.com/passage/?search=1%20John%204%3A1-3&amp;version=ESV" target="_blank">1 John 4:2</a>):</h3>

<p>You: Hello Holy Spirit, do you confess Jesus Christ has come in the flesh?<br />
HS: Yes. (Disconnect and consult a true teacher immediately if the answer is no or no response)<br />
You: Thank you, Holy Spirit. <u>____________positive-only_question____________</u><br />
HS: Yes / No-response (Doesn’t mean the answer is No, see example below)<br />
You: Thank you, Holy Spirit. Love you and signing off.<br /></p>

<h3 id="example">Example:</h3>

<p>You: Should I take a shower?<br />
HS: No response.<br />
You: Should I not take a shower?<br />
HS: No response.<br />
Result: exercise your free will and discretion.<br /></p>

<p>You: Should I take a shower?<br />
HS: Yes.<br />
Result: you dirty bastard fucked up.<br /></p>

<h3 id="a-bad-example">A Bad Example:</h3>

<p>Below was the first real-world application of the HMI when I was emailing stakeholders earlier this week, including some false teachers and <a href="../on-background-music/" target="_blank">cunts</a> I would like to believe I still love. I realised shortly after that no response is not the same as a negative response and the HMI is positive-only rather than binary. Need to brush up on my elementary logic 101. It’s been a while.</p>

<embed src="https://dl.hesaid.love/binary_hmi_bad_example.pdf" type="application/pdf" width="100%" height="600px" />

<h3 id="dont-be-this-guy">Don’t be this guy:</h3>

<p><img src="/JY2w4TNTb4yPxSNMsd.jpg" alt="Don't be this guy" /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a simple introduction to the Holy Spirit Positive-Only Human-Machine Interface (HSPOHMI). If our Heavenly Father has not bestowed Him on you yet, ask Him for the Holy Spirit. You might have some soul-searching to do. I asked Him once last July and He came five weeks later. I was technically being philosophically dramatic.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On HE as AoD</title><link href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-he-as-aod/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On HE as AoD" /><published>2025-02-19T08:59:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-02-19T08:59:00+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/posts/on-he-as-aod</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-he-as-aod/"><![CDATA[<p>I’m not too bothered with writing too much on this topic since I have more or less covered them previously in bits and pieces. Will make some bullet points and you can see below what ChatGPT thinks.</p>

<ul>
  <li>Business schools everywhere</li>
  <li>Existentialism, nihilism and antinatalism</li>
  <li>Drug addicts who don’t know what to believe, aren’t even sure if reality is simulated, and are only interested in more drugs</li>
  <li>Theology is compared to the study of unicorns and fairytales</li>
  <li>Intellectual pride hiding behind jargon and publications</li>
</ul>

<p>I’m using the ChatGPT free plan and rarely get limited. The next level up is $20 a month. I’m pretty sure I can train an open-source model in a couple of days. I’m not massively sure why I paid £100k (overseas which is 3x local) for my Oxford CS degree.</p>

<p><img src="/Q7nJ56qgW3XZw5K7uK.png" alt="" /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not too bothered with writing too much on this topic since I have more or less covered them previously in bits and pieces. Will make some bullet points and you can see below what ChatGPT thinks.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Lust and Guilt</title><link href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-lust-and-guilt/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Lust and Guilt" /><published>2025-02-19T04:07:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-02-21T23:12:40+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/posts/on-lust-and-guilt</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-lust-and-guilt/"><![CDATA[<p>Unfortunately, this topic was easy for me to solve in a uniquely personal way, and He already gave me the answer on day 2 when He came to save me back in late August last year.</p>

<p>As mentioned in <a href="../on-holy-spirit-miracles/" target="_blank">a previous post</a>, after He baptised me with the Holy Spirit, I grabbed my backpack with my travel documents and was ready to jump into an Uber straight to Heathrow. I was planning on flying back to mainland China and thought I was going to speak to my friend’s father the Christian missionary to become a missionary for Him as well. I ended up turning Him down and I frankly felt rather dismayed afterwards. Wouldn’t you feel that if you truly believed that was God and you were offered a potentially once-in-a-lifetime opportunity to work for Him? Other than the reason stated in the previous post, there is a main reason that only three people knew about before this post. They are my Christ bro therapist, the Christian missionary’s daughter who was same year at Keble as me, and the drama that is me.</p>

<p>I <a href="../on-suffering/" target="_blank">also mentioned</a> that He asked me a series of questions with increasingly difficult personal sacrifices to follow Him. One of the songs was Locked Away by R. City. I turned Him down at the end because I thought He asked me whether I would give up being a homosexual and marry my friend. Essentially have a stereotypical Christian model family that you would expect from every Christian missionary, the standard issue edition. I struggled with that question for a very long time and I did not want Him to wait too long given who I believed He was. In the end, I could not in good conscience say yes to Him due to the <a href="../on-background-music/#contemplation-on-sexuality" target="_blank">contemplations I had</a> regarding my sexuality when I was a teenager. I would rather be true to myself and my conscience than be something that I’m not even for His sake. It ripped my heart out to say no to Him.</p>

<p>Fortunately, He asked me to think about why and He visited me again after my therapy session on the third day. Subsequently, an insane journey followed and today is 21 weeks and 3 days and counting. The previous post provided the first half of the reason why. This post is the second half.</p>

<hr />

<p>Matthew 5:27–30</p>

<p>Lust</p>

<p>[27] “You have heard that it was said, ‘You shall not commit adultery.’ [28] But I say to you that everyone who looks at a woman with lustful intent has already committed adultery with her in his heart. [29] If your right eye causes you to sin, tear it out and throw it away. For it is better that you lose one of your members than that your whole body be thrown into hell. [30] And if your right hand causes you to sin, cut it off and throw it away. For it is better that you lose one of your members than that your whole body go into hell. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>I don’t think anyone will believe what I’m about to say here, except Him, the Holy Spirit, my conscience, me and perhaps the 144,000. There is no lust in my heart when I have sex or watch pornography. I don’t think I have ever had lustful intent in my mind, at the very least in a sexual way according to the definition above. I have never looked at anyone whether male or female and wanted to have sexual relationships with them. I described in detail about my sexual activities in multiple previous posts. The main point is I have a mental block of looking at my sexual partners and would require my eyesight to be covered and I can only engage in anonymous sex.</p>

<p>I barely had any sex for the 100 days I spent at the gay/bi-naturist campsite Rosebay and it was essentially a designed playground for gay men to have sex. I guess that was also part of the reason why I hyperfocused on the Wi-Fi and I simply enjoyed being around my community for the social aspects and helping them. They also looked after me at the beginning. That was also exactly the reason why I had difficulty having sex there. Pretty much everyone knew everyone and anonymity was out of the door. The moment I can recognise the identity of my sexual partner either from speech or other details that I shall not describe here, my sexual desire disappears without a trace.</p>

<p>When I watch pornography to get into the mood, I do not lust for anyone depicted on the screen, instead, I fantasise about being the partner getting penetrated in the act. More often than not, I feel concerned for the passive partner if something I would not enjoy happens.</p>

<p>I also came across Job 31 - Job’s Final Appeal when researching this topic. The weird thing I find on this journey especially when reading the gospels is other than being a homosexual, I think I may have been storing up treasures in heaven unknowingly my entire life. There were things I did that I thought no one knew and came at a cost to me personally because I wanted to make some stranger’s day. Now I know He knows. I think I might have lived a somewhat holy life in the 27 years of my previous life without knowing God’s existence. Oops…</p>

<p>Also, I think the 144,000 in the Book of Revelation might be homosexuals. I have a separate “gay phone” because I was technically in the closet until this journey. The survival rate for my straight phone contacts is a massacre after most took off their sheep costumes. The survival rate on my gay phone is 100%. I have one gay theologian friend amongst my long list of theologians and technically I did not know he had a theology degree before this journey. Only one theologian still replies to my messages and you can guess their sexual preference.</p>

<p>If you have ever met a gay man and they opened their mouth for five minutes, you would know that these people will call you a cunt to your face if you are behaving like a cunt regardless of whether you are their best friend or their worst enemy. People from previous generations often ran away from home to be true to themselves. They are used to being ridiculed, mocked and bullied for being made differently. They are willing to sacrifice their entire world to be who they truly are inside. I genuinely did not expect to find out that many of my straight friends were different on the inside. I was surprised by the loyalty of my gay friends even though I did not tell them my real name until six months ago. I was hurt by evil people within my community, but I was also comforted by people within my community including but not limited to the staff and random visitors at the gay sauna in central London. We decided to be true to ourselves and to our conscience knowing there is a non-zero probability that we have to face our maker and give an account of the lives we lived.</p>

<p><a href="../on-blasphemy/" target="_blank">Some</a> illogical and illiterate straight cunts lied and condemned the guiltless for their entire lives. <a href="../on-indifference/" target="_blank">Some</a> not only reject God’s existence but also call good evil and call evil good. Enough is enough.</p>

<hr />

<p>Isaiah 5:13–23</p>

<p>[13] Therefore my people go into exile<br />
        for lack of knowledge;<br />
        their honored men go hungry,<br />
        and their multitude is parched with thirst.<br />
[14] Therefore Sheol has enlarged its appetite<br />
        and opened its mouth beyond measure,<br />
        and the nobility of Jerusalem and her multitude will go down,<br />
        her revelers and he who exults in her.<br />
[15] Man is humbled, and each one is brought low,<br />
        and the eyes of the haughty are brought low.<br />
[16] But the LORD of hosts is exalted in justice,<br />
        and the Holy God shows himself holy in righteousness.<br />
[17] Then shall the lambs graze as in their pasture,<br />
        and nomads shall eat among the ruins of the rich.<br /></p>

<p>[18] Woe to those who draw iniquity with cords of falsehood,<br />
        who draw sin as with cart ropes,<br />
[19] who say: “Let him be quick,<br />
        let him speed his work<br />
        that we may see it;<br />
        let the counsel of the Holy One of Israel draw near,<br />
        and let it come, that we may know it!”<br />
[20] Woe to those who call evil good<br />
        and good evil,<br />
        who put darkness for light<br />
        and light for darkness,<br />
        who put bitter for sweet<br />
        and sweet for bitter!<br />
[21] Woe to those who are wise in their own eyes,<br />
        and shrewd in their own sight!<br />
[22] Woe to those who are heroes at drinking wine,<br />
        and valiant men in mixing strong drink,<br />
[23] who acquit the guilty for a bribe,<br />
        and deprive the innocent of his right! (ESV)<br /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unfortunately, this topic was easy for me to solve in a uniquely personal way, and He already gave me the answer on day 2 when He came to save me back in late August last year.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Blasphemy</title><link href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-blasphemy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Blasphemy" /><published>2025-02-17T15:48:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-02-21T23:12:40+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/posts/on-blasphemy</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-blasphemy/"><![CDATA[<p>If you are a member of the scribes and Pharisees, please first consider if you have taken the name of the LORD your God in vain yourself before accusing me of doing so after reading my often strong-worded writings especially when condemning evils committed by people I once loved and would like to believe I still love. Even though English is my second language and I also speak Cantonese, Mandarin and a Chinese dialect as well as a tiny bit of German learned when I was partying in Berlin like there was no tomorrow, I stand by my choice of wording in expressing the accuracy of the sentiment and severity of the situation.</p>

<p>I consider the censorship of words for mere outward appearances as exemplified by esteemed hypocrites like politicians unnecessary and futile. All of humanity used to speak a single language before we thought too highly of ourselves and the Lord scattered us and confused our language. I double-checked with the Holy Spirit regarding the next statement. Every word in our language has its appropriate use case and there is no need to censor them if you intend to accurately convey meaning rather than to please esteemed hypocrites.</p>

<p>I would like to argue that if you have ever done that when going about the Lord’s business then you have already violated the commandment by false representation. I’m pretty sure that would be the case if you have ever told a member of my community that God hates homosexuals, or in fact, anyone that God hates them because of who they are or what they did. Please do not babble until you have figured out what you are talking about. If uncertain, double-check with the Holy Spirit or ask the Father for the Holy Spirit if you haven’t met Bro yet. Bro is a super cool Dude and I unfortunately have to question whether you truly believe if you haven’t met Bro.</p>

<p>I kinda know why He prepared my welcoming party to the United Kingdom 11 years ago before I even bought the plane ticket to London and why He told me to speak to my friend’s father the Christian missionary in mainland China when I had my first calling during COVID-19. If I walked into any church today and opened my mouth for five minutes, I would not be going back again as an implicit mutually beneficial agreement and understanding. I have been dancing around both of my guides and they don’t read my posts. I still haven’t told my guide in mainland China that I’m a rampant homosexual because his opinions on the issue are quite clear-cut on social media. I brought up the possibility that the sex I have might not involve lust at least on my part to my welcoming party yesterday at church and I repeatedly emphasised the fact that I use the password in 1 John 4:2 and he does not know about my sex life, but his stance on the issue did not allow me the sufficient opportunity to state my case and ask for guidance or directions for me to better understand and hopefully resolve the dilemma.</p>

<p>I came across the verses in Matthew 9:13 and 12:7 when looking into the references from Luke 11:13 below. I merely wanted to better understand God in my relationship with Him after He called me, but people’s minds are so rigid and blind-sighted by their view and interpretation of the world that we no longer even allow each other to finish our sentences anymore before shouting our own opinions. Few even do enough homework or due diligence to consider other possibilities for their arguments before opening their mouths. I rarely met anyone willing to admit their lack of understanding or knowledge on any subject. I think I can stop tiptoeing around people at church.</p>

<p>I will start saying what’s in my mind and my heart for the first time in my life after allowing everyone to finish their sentences and always consider views from their perspective first as much as I could reasonably achieve within the given context. I will speak with a clear conscience and Bro as my witness. For the first time in my life, I no longer need other people’s input as weights in my probabilistic model view of the world. I have THE source of truth with a binary HMI and response latency lower than ChatGPT and I’m switching to a free-will compatible deterministic model view of the world. I don’t know how it works as much as infinitely many other known and unknown mysteries of our universe. Feel free to submit your queries to Boss Man if you desperately want to know. I have got some house cleaning to do first.</p>

<p>I asked the Holy Spirit if I could call Him Bro. Dude’s cool with that.</p>

<hr />

<p>Matthew 9:13</p>

<p>[13] Go and learn what this means: ‘I desire mercy, and not sacrifice.’ For I came not to call the righteous, but sinners.” (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>Matthew 12:7</p>

<p>[7] And if you had known what this means, ‘I desire mercy, and not sacrifice,’ you would not have condemned the guiltless. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>Luke 11:9–13</p>

<p>[9] And I tell you, ask, and it will be given to you; seek, and you will find; knock, and it will be opened to you. [10] For everyone who asks receives, and the one who seeks finds, and to the one who knocks it will be opened. [11] What father among you, if his son asks for a fish, will instead of a fish give him a serpent; [12] or if he asks for an egg, will give him a scorpion? [13] If you then, who are evil, know how to give good gifts to your children, how much more will the heavenly Father give the Holy Spirit to those who ask him!” (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>Acts 2:37–40</p>

<p>[37] Now when they heard this they were cut to the heart, and said to Peter and the rest of the apostles, “Brothers, what shall we do?” [38] And Peter said to them, “Repent and be baptized every one of you in the name of Jesus Christ for the forgiveness of your sins, and you will receive the gift of the Holy Spirit. [39] For the promise is for you and for your children and for all who are far off, everyone whom the Lord our God calls to himself.” [40] And with many other words he bore witness and continued to exhort them, saying, “Save yourselves from this crooked generation.” (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>Genesis 11:1–9</p>

<p>The Tower of Babel</p>

<p>[1] Now the whole earth had one language and the same words. [2] And as people migrated from the east, they found a plain in the land of Shinar and settled there. [3] And they said to one another, “Come, let us make bricks, and burn them thoroughly.” And they had brick for stone, and bitumen for mortar. [4] Then they said, “Come, let us build ourselves a city and a tower with its top in the heavens, and let us make a name for ourselves, lest we be dispersed over the face of the whole earth.” [5] And the LORD came down to see the city and the tower, which the children of man had built. [6] And the LORD said, “Behold, they are one people, and they have all one language, and this is only the beginning of what they will do. And nothing that they propose to do will now be impossible for them. [7] Come, let us go down and there confuse their language, so that they may not understand one another’s speech.” [8] So the LORD dispersed them from there over the face of all the earth, and they left off building the city. [9] Therefore its name was called Babel, because there the LORD confused the language of all the earth. And from there the LORD dispersed them over the face of all the earth. (ESV)</p>

<p><img src="/wt8gWxcXcqMbgk0c4q.png" alt="" /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a member of the scribes and Pharisees, please first consider if you have taken the name of the LORD your God in vain yourself before accusing me of doing so after reading my often strong-worded writings especially when condemning evils committed by people I once loved and would like to believe I still love. Even though English is my second language and I also speak Cantonese, Mandarin and a Chinese dialect as well as a tiny bit of German learned when I was partying in Berlin like there was no tomorrow, I stand by my choice of wording in expressing the accuracy of the sentiment and severity of the situation.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Turing Completeness</title><link href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-turing-completeness/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Turing Completeness" /><published>2025-02-17T08:52:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-02-21T23:12:40+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/posts/on-turing-completeness</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-turing-completeness/"><![CDATA[<p>If you read my posts, you might be under the impression that I was suggesting or hinting that I may be a certain unspeakable m-word. Personally, if you ask me if I would like to be the m-word, then my answer from the moment I was born to the end of time would be fuck no. And once again, I had a fucking blast minding my own business in the 27 years of my previous life until some motherfuckers came along, blew my first fucking proper holiday, and the people in my life continued to stab me in the back then left me to burn.</p>

<p>I started this blog to bitch and moan about shit I encountered on this journey because I put zero effort into inquiring about God’s business previously since I am a rampant homosexual, have more sexual partners in an hour every other day than the average straight person has in a lifetime on average, and thought God would hate someone like me based purely on religious stereotypes. I bought my first Bible back in late July last year after an ethical thought experiment I designed during COVID-19 essentially came true in real life, I thought it could be divine intervention and wondered in my heart whether we could bring God back, after getting kicked out of the gay/bi-naturist campsite Rosebay for giving them free full site Wi-Fi coverage and almost threw myself off the fifth-floor balcony right in front of my younger sister. I considered myself an agnostic and was never an atheist because I had no evidence for or against God’s existence. If He exists, God’s business is God’s business. I’m human and I mind my own business. Until people decided to fuck with my business, He decided to make my business His business, and now I’m going to fuck some people’s business up. To quote my Boss, now let that motherfucker burn. For the record, I was still messaging John Donald, the owner of Rosebay and my former business partner Meiling Wang on 6th February hoping they would repent. I’m done with that now and I will leave it to my Boss and what happens happens.</p>

<p><img src="/j95vGhAQ8krUK1tpVn.png" alt="" /></p>

<p>I described my relationship with the Holy Spirit including how we first met in an early post. It has been a very busy 21-week and 1-day journey since I first believed on 22 September 2024. No matter how insane my leaps of faith may appear to you, everything I did was confirmed both by the Holy Spirit and scripture. More often than not, I wasn’t even actively seeking confirmations, He just shoved scripture to my face one way or another when I needed it the most.</p>

<p>This past weekend, I had a moment of epiphany where I realised my interactions with the Holy Spirit are more or less the same as a binary HMI (Human Machine Interface). So I spent some time on the interface and now I just log in with the password in 1 John 4:2 before submitting queries to my Father. Latency is surprisingly low and much quicker than asking ChatGPT. ChatGPT annoys the heck out of me waiting for the answer to be spat out. Boss Man must have dope cloud infrastructure running up there. When I was sitting on the toilet attempting to do a number two before a shower earlier, I wondered if the Holy Spirit was Turing complete. Hence this post and the answer is yes for the theoretical computer scientists amongst you. I consider myself more of a coding monkey throwing half-assed MVPs together with whatever I can find. A lot more fun when you live life fast and furious. I managed to win the wager I proposed to my fellow CS Keblites by falling asleep on my tutor’s comfortable sofa during a tutorial. That’s how you get a third class in uni.</p>

<p>The purpose of this post is to say don’t worry about the m-word-related posts. I was hoping someone could slap me awake and show me evidence one way or another so that I knew I was delusional or mistaken. There was only one guy who needed to be convinced. Most of you did not give him a chance to finish his sentence before abandoning him.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you read my posts, you might be under the impression that I was suggesting or hinting that I may be a certain unspeakable m-word. Personally, if you ask me if I would like to be the m-word, then my answer from the moment I was born to the end of time would be fuck no. And once again, I had a fucking blast minding my own business in the 27 years of my previous life until some motherfuckers came along, blew my first fucking proper holiday, and the people in my life continued to stab me in the back then left me to burn.]]></summary></entry></feed>