<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://hesaid.love/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://hesaid.love/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" /><updated>2025-03-18T13:55:51+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Aaron @ He Said Love</title><subtitle>A rampant homosexual writing about Boss Man&apos;s love and the good, bad, ugly, stupid, idiotic, crazy, and insane during my walk with Him. Dude made me feel more loved in a week than anyone, including my parents, ever managed to make me feel my entire life combined. It might not be a beautiful testimony (yet), but it&apos;s a truthful testimony. I believe since 22 September 2024. Zeal for His house consumes me.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have done everything out of &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/posts/on-love&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;love&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, and I sincerely wish my love could be more patient under normal circumstances, but unfortunately, we are &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://letter.hesaid.love&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;running out of time&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;DO NOT take my words at face value.&lt;/b&gt; Trust, but verify. He is the way, and the truth, and the life. Ask Him, not me. I lean not on my own understanding. But reason within the boundaries and understanding He gives me.  I do not seek to condemn, even though telling the truth could easily be interpreted as such.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fire in hell would be warmer than the coldness I felt in this world. How about you do your part, I do mine, Boss Man does His and let&apos;s find out on the other side what we are?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Say what I want by telling the truth, the whole truth and nothing but the truth feels as good as getting fucked in the ass by talented Germans in FickstutenMarkt for 4hrs+ non-stop whilst listening to sick Berlin techno. I intend to continue doing both.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;His name is Jesus Christ, my Lord and Saviour.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">On Faith Party</title><link href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-faith-party/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Faith Party" /><published>2025-03-18T12:48:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-18T12:48:00+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/posts/on-faith-party</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-faith-party/"><![CDATA[<p>Initially, I had the name Restore Faith Party in mind, but the domain name restore.faith costs over £500, and I could barely afford a cup of vanilla latte with coconut milk. By the grace of God, I managed to secure the domain name <a href="https://www.faithparty.org/" target="_blank">FaithParty.org</a> earlier this morning for $7.66 (£5.91), the price of a cup of vanilla latte with coconut milk at London RPI with spare change. As a <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rust_(programming_language)" target="_blank">Rust</a> developer, I’m also a gigantic <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Functional_programming" target="_blank">functional programming</a> (FP) fanboy.</p>

<p>I am working on the <a href="https://www.electoralcommission.org.uk/sites/default/files/2023-06/RP1%20GB%20updated%20May%202023.pdf" target="_blank">RP1 GB form</a> (Application to register a political party in Great Britain). Due to my poor history of managing personal finance, I would raise more than a few eyebrows if I signed up to be the treasurer. I asked a faithful new friend if he would like the honour. I wanted to put down the Lord as the party leader, but I do not have the postcode for His current address. I am also reluctant to ask for His telephone number and email address. Therefore, I disgracefully nominated myself for the interim position. Hopefully, this will be the last time I try over-employment. I almost threw myself off the balcony last year.</p>

<p>I have been working on the party emblem and have three draft designs. ChatGPT kept rebelling against my instruction to reflect the full party slogan—”Love in Action. Faith in People. Hope for the Future.”—in the design. I resorted to asking my new faithful friend again if he had any faithful artist friends who might be interested. The gig would be fully credited. The down payment is in the form of a bestseller with a full invoice paid on an unknown future date if they charge above-market premium rates.</p>

<hr />

<div style="display: flex; justify-content: space-between;">
  <img src="/emblem_v0_3.webp" alt="Emblem v0.3" style="max-width: 90%; height: auto;" />
  <img src="/emblem_v0_2.webp" alt="Emblem v0.2" style="max-width: 90%; height: auto;" />
  <img src="/emblem_v0_1.webp" alt="Emblem v0.1" style="max-width: 90%; height: auto;" />
</div>

<hr />

<p>I cheated again by asking ChatGPT to write the draft party constitution. Frankly, I could not have done it better myself. It’s slightly longer than one page, but considering the legal and formal language involved, it’s still better than <a href="https://public.conservatives.com/organisation-department/202101/Conservative%20Party%20Constitution%20%20as%20amended%20January%202021.pdf" target="_blank">Conservative’s 58</a> and <a href="https://labour.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/Rule-Book-2024.pdf" target="_blank">Labour’s 146</a>. You have to give credit where credit is due. The <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bible" target="_blank">full version</a> and more details can be found on humanity’s bestseller.</p>

<hr />

<embed src="https://dl.hesaidlove.com/Great_Commandment_of_Jesus.pdf" type="application/pdf" width="100%" height="700px" />]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Initially, I had the name Restore Faith Party in mind, but the domain name restore.faith costs over £500, and I could barely afford a cup of vanilla latte with coconut milk. By the grace of God, I managed to secure the domain name FaithParty.org earlier this morning for $7.66 (£5.91), the price of a cup of vanilla latte with coconut milk at London RPI with spare change. As a Rust developer, I’m also a gigantic functional programming (FP) fanboy.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Son of Man</title><link href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-son-of-man/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Son of Man" /><published>2025-03-17T18:24:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-18T08:45:44+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/posts/on-son-of-man</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-son-of-man/"><![CDATA[<p>I was feasting on delicious noodles I bought yesterday after selling two overkill high-end SSDs in the last hour. A scary thought entered my mind when I was devouring the noodles. Could Boss Man be talking about the same person in Luke 11:29-32?</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="luke-112932">Luke 11:29–32</h2>

<p>The Sign of Jonah</p>

<p>[29] When the crowds were increasing, he began to say, “This generation is an evil generation. It seeks for a sign, but no sign will be given to it except the sign of Jonah. [30] For as Jonah became a sign to the people of Nineveh, so will the Son of Man be to this generation. [31] The queen of the South will rise up at the judgment with the men of this generation and condemn them, for she came from the ends of the earth to hear the wisdom of Solomon, and behold, something greater than Solomon is here. [32] The men of Nineveh will rise up at the judgment with this generation and condemn it, for they repented at the preaching of Jonah, and behold, something greater than Jonah is here. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>Unless there has been a major breakthrough in <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/CRISPR_gene_editing" target="_blank">CRISPR-Cas9</a>-related technologies that I am unaware of, I believe everyone is a son or daughter of a man.</p>

<p>At the beginning of this journey, I wondered whether the Son of Man wanted to finish reading the bestseller because it gets scary when things get too magical. The bestseller is also long-ass. Could that be why no one knows that day or hour? The Son of Man is human. And it would be an understandable sentiment for a fellow human being. That could be the case if the Son of Man is amongst us without knowing he is the Son of Man.</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="matthew-243639">Matthew 24:36–39</h2>

<p>No One Knows That Day and Hour</p>

<p>[36] “But concerning that day and hour no one knows, not even the angels of heaven, nor the Son, but the Father only. [37] For as were the days of Noah, so will be the coming of the Son of Man. [38] For as in those days before the flood they were eating and drinking, marrying and giving in marriage, until the day when Noah entered the ark, [39] and they were unaware until the flood came and swept them all away, so will be the coming of the Son of Man. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>For some weird reason, the following verse keeps calling and motivating me, unlike <a href="../on-revelation-13/#antichrist-not-christian" target="_blank">the antichrists</a> pretending to be Christians who informed me the desire to save people is a sign of pride.</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="matthew-2422">Matthew 24:22</h2>

<p>[22] And if those days had not been cut short, no human being would be saved. But for the sake of the elect those days will be cut short. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>I don’t know about the Son of Man. But I intend to finish reading the bestseller, start a political party in the United Kingdom, and save some rampant homosexuals this year. Totally unrelated to the following verse, I also found <a href="../on-condemnation/" target="_blank">little faith</a> and caught a bunch of <a href="../on-revelation-13/" target="_blank">false teachers and antichrists</a>. I wonder what kind of shitshow the Son of Man will find. That day will be fun for sure.</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="luke-188">Luke 18:8</h2>

<p>[8] I tell you, he will give justice to them speedily. Nevertheless, when the Son of Man comes, will he find faith on earth?” (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>Also, are you fucking telling me no one has walked in His statues in the last 2,000 fucking years?</p>

<p>If you are <a href="../on-revelation-13/#antichrist-not-christian" target="_blank">an antichrist</a> pretending to be a Christian, feel free to let me know whether I accidentally climbed the Hall of Faith on my second week as a believer. I give zero fuck what you think if you don’t know what the Hall of Faith is.</p>

<h2 id="meme">Meme</h2>

<p><img src="/d15b2d9925fb70e0628ee8749b878326.jpeg" alt="F for failure" /></p>

<h2 id="what-do-i-know---ed-sheeran">What Do I Know? - Ed Sheeran</h2>

<p><img src="/eaz8vwgfeWp5AQCdBP.png" alt="What Do I Know? - Ed Sheeran" /></p>

<iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/2pJZ1v8HezrAoZ0Fhzby92?utm_source=generator&amp;theme=0" width="100%" height="152" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe>

<div id="rg_embed_link_2953771" class="rg_embed_link" data-song-id="2953771">Read <a href="https://genius.com/Ed-sheeran-what-do-i-know-lyrics">“What Do I Know?” by Ed Sheeran</a> on Genius</div>
<script crossorigin="" src="https://genius.com/songs/2953771/embed.js"></script>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was feasting on delicious noodles I bought yesterday after selling two overkill high-end SSDs in the last hour. A scary thought entered my mind when I was devouring the noodles. Could Boss Man be talking about the same person in Luke 11:29-32?]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Money and Fiscal Policy</title><link href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-money-and-fiscal-policy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Money and Fiscal Policy" /><published>2025-03-17T09:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-18T08:29:03+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/posts/on-money-and-fiscal-policy</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-money-and-fiscal-policy/"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to the first of a series of policy posts as I prepare to register a political party in Great Britain. I intend to apply the principles in my personal life where applicable. Someone has got to start walking in His statutes, observing His commandments, and doing them.</p>

<p>If you like to doubt, which is understandable given that we are all human and imperfect, I would like to paraphrase Boss Man by saying, “Go and learn what this means: ‘He is the Lord our <strong><em>God</em></strong>.’”</p>

<p>If you are a “believer” who “thinks” I have gone batshit crazy, then please consider whether trust and belief are <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Transitive_relation" target="_blank">transitive</a> and whether you truly believe if you consider me nuts. I would also strongly encourage you to take a revision course on the <a href="https://www.biblegateway.com/verse/en/Hebrews%2011%3A1" target="_blank">definition of faith</a> outlined in Hebrews 11. We should stop this wishy-washy nonsense, and you are either in or you are out. No more foot in both camps bullshit.</p>

<h2 id="edit">Edit</h2>

<p>After publishing the original post, I was thinking about the next major policy item - education, which would be an exceptionally tricky area for obvious reasons. Then, I had the epiphany that I already had the answer in the original post. We need to stop making <a href="../on-genesis-3-fall-man/" target="_blank">the mistake</a> we have been making since Genesis 3, the fall of man, and start putting God first rather than reason and end up with nothing but death. Seek Him first, and He will make our paths straight rather than lean on our insufficient understanding and go at it with our half-assed reasoning and comprehension.</p>

<hr />

<h3 id="proverbs-318">Proverbs 3:1–8</h3>

<p>Trust in the LORD with All Your Heart</p>

<p>[1] My son, do not forget my teaching,<br />
      but let your heart keep my commandments,<br />
 [2] for length of days and years of life<br />
      and peace they will add to you.</p>

<p>[3] Let not steadfast love and faithfulness forsake you;<br />
      bind them around your neck;<br />
      write them on the tablet of your heart.<br />
 [4] So you will find favor and good success<br />
      in the sight of God and man.</p>

<p><strong>[5] Trust in the LORD with all your heart,</strong><br />
      <strong>and do not lean on your own understanding.</strong><br />
 <strong>[6] In all your ways acknowledge him,</strong><br />
      <strong>and he will make straight your paths.</strong><br />
 [7] Be not wise in your own eyes;<br />
      fear the LORD, and turn away from evil.<br />
 [8] It will be healing to your flesh<br />
      and refreshment to your bones. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>I mentioned previously <a href="../on-holy-spirit-miracles/" target="_blank">the first call</a> we had after not speaking for 11 years with my welcoming party lasted 6.5 hours. We were arguing about semantic differences in the Bible. Boss Man told me to make the argument known to you in this post. I was 100% certain God exists, but only 95% about Jesus Christ as my Lord and Saviour in that call. My welcoming party was trying to bash me into confessing Jesus Christ as my Lord and Saviour. My issue with that? Tomato, tomahto. I could not comprehend the significance of the name Jesus since it’s written and pronounced differently in different languages. Why not stick with God when referring to God? Two days later, I read Romans 1-4 and felt the truth cutting through my bones into my soul. If you have never read Romans 1-4 before, Mr Noisy Gong kept talking about a Dude named Jesus Christ in it, which I later found out was a letter written to the Romans rather than a personal letter written to me by some dude named Roman. At that point, I was like “Okay, fine, all in Jesus Christ as my Lord and Saviour.”</p>

<p>Now, if you subscribe to a religion, which I do not, or you have yet to encounter God personally, perhaps due to learning whatever through doctrine written by some historical figures whose names are not on the No. 1 bestseller of humanity, then I would advise you to ask God with your heart to show you who He is. <strong>We won’t get anywhere unless we fix the immediate problem of people thinking you are nuts the moment you bring up the three-letter word <em>God</em>.</strong> Our inability to let each other finish our sentences and instinctive rejection of God are getting ridiculous and out of control.</p>

<p>A new friend of mine mentioned the following highlighted verse from the Book of Joel yesterday.</p>

<hr />

<h3 id="joel-22732">Joel 2:27–32</h3>

<p>[27] You shall know that I am in the midst of Israel,<br />
  and that I am the LORD your God and there is none else.<br />
 And my people shall never again be put to shame.</p>

<p>The LORD Will Pour Out His Spirit</p>

<p><strong>[28] “And it shall come to pass afterward,</strong><br />
      <strong>that I will pour out my Spirit on all flesh;</strong><br />
 <strong>your sons and your daughters shall prophesy,</strong><br />
      <strong>your old men shall dream dreams,</strong><br />
      <strong>and your young men shall see visions.</strong><br />
 [29] Even on the male and female servants<br />
      in those days I will pour out my Spirit.</p>

<p>[30] “And I will show wonders in the heavens and on the earth, blood and fire and columns of smoke. [31] The sun shall be turned to darkness, and the moon to blood, before the great and awesome day of the LORD comes. [32] And it shall come to pass that everyone who calls on the name of the LORD shall be saved. For in Mount Zion and in Jerusalem there shall be those who escape, as the LORD has said, and among the survivors shall be those whom the LORD calls. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>According to my half-assed ChatGPT research, Joel is one of the twelve minor prophets like Jonah, but Joel is not lucky enough to be included in all Abrahamic religions like Jonah. However, Isaiah and Ezekiel are both recognised in all Abrahamic religions, which I do not subscribe to. So here you go.</p>

<hr />

<h3 id="isaiah-4418">Isaiah 44:1–8</h3>

<p>Israel the LORD’s Chosen</p>

<p>[1] “But now hear, O Jacob my servant,<br />
      Israel whom I have chosen!<br />
 [2] Thus says the LORD who made you,<br />
      who formed you from the womb and will help you:<br />
 Fear not, O Jacob my servant,<br />
      Jeshurun whom I have chosen.<br />
 [3] For I will pour water on the thirsty land,<br />
      and streams on the dry ground;<br />
 <strong>I will pour my Spirit upon your offspring,</strong><br />
      and my blessing on your descendants.<br />
 [4] They shall spring up among the grass<br />
      like willows by flowing streams.<br />
 [5] This one will say, ‘I am the LORD’s,’<br />
      another will call on the name of Jacob,<br />
 and another will write on his hand, ‘The LORD’s,’<br />
      and name himself by the name of Israel.”</p>

<p>Besides Me There Is No God</p>

<p>[6] Thus says the LORD, the King of Israel<br />
      and his Redeemer, the LORD of hosts:<br />
 “I am the first and I am the last;<br />
      besides me there is no god.<br />
 [7] Who is like me? Let him proclaim it.<br />
      Let him declare and set it before me,<br />
 since I appointed an ancient people.<br />
      Let them declare what is to come, and what will happen.<br />
 [8] Fear not, nor be afraid;<br />
      have I not told you from of old and declared it?<br />
      And you are my witnesses!<br />
 Is there a God besides me?<br />
      There is no Rock; I know not any.” (ESV)</p>

<h3 id="ezekiel-392529">Ezekiel 39:25–29</h3>

<p>The LORD Will Restore Israel</p>

<p>[25] “Therefore thus says the Lord GOD: Now I will restore the fortunes of Jacob and have mercy on the whole house of Israel, and I will be jealous for my holy name. [26] They shall forget their shame and all the treachery they have practiced against me, when they dwell securely in their land with none to make them afraid, [27] when I have brought them back from the peoples and gathered them from their enemies’ lands, and through them have vindicated my holiness in the sight of many nations. [28] Then they shall know that I am the LORD their God, because I sent them into exile among the nations and then assembled them into their own land. I will leave none of them remaining among the nations anymore. <strong>[29] And I will not hide my face anymore from them, when I pour out my Spirit upon the house of Israel, declares the Lord GOD.”</strong> (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="challenge">Challenge</h2>

<p>I inquired about Him once in the first 27 years of my life, and He showed up five weeks later. Do you dare to have a go? I dare you, bitch.</p>

<p>I use the word <strong>bitch</strong> to describe anyone who is unfaithful. I was a bitch myself back when I did not have faith. I am still a bitch sometimes especially when I’m late to meet my new friend for over half an hour.</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="malachi-3615">Malachi 3:6–15</h2>

<p>Robbing God</p>

<p>[6] “For I the LORD do not change; therefore you, O children of Jacob, are not consumed. [7] From the days of your fathers you have turned aside from my statutes and have not kept them. Return to me, and I will return to you, says the LORD of hosts. But you say, ‘How shall we return?’ [8] Will man rob God? Yet you are robbing me. But you say, ‘How have we robbed you?’ In your tithes and contributions. [9] You are cursed with a curse, for you are robbing me, the whole nation of you. <strong>[10] Bring the full tithe into the storehouse, that there may be food in my house. And thereby put me to the test, says the LORD of hosts, if I will not open the windows of heaven for you and pour down for you a blessing until there is no more need.</strong> [11] I will rebuke the devourer for you, so that it will not destroy the fruits of your soil, and your vine in the field shall not fail to bear, says the LORD of hosts. [12] Then all nations will call you blessed, for you will be a land of delight, says the LORD of hosts.</p>

<p><strong>[13] “Your words have been hard against me, says the LORD. But you say, ‘How have we spoken against you?’ [14] You have said, ‘It is vain to serve God. What is the profit of our keeping his charge or of walking as in mourning before the LORD of hosts? [15] And now we call the arrogant blessed. Evildoers not only prosper but they put God to the test and they escape.’”</strong> (ESV)</p>

<h2 id="matthew-62534">Matthew 6:25–34</h2>

<p>Do Not Be Anxious</p>

<p>[25] “Therefore I tell you, do not be anxious about your life, what you will eat or what you will drink, nor about your body, what you will put on. Is not life more than food, and the body more than clothing? [26] Look at the birds of the air: they neither sow nor reap nor gather into barns, and yet your heavenly Father feeds them. Are you not of more value than they? [27] And which of you by being anxious can add a single hour to his span of life? [28] And why are you anxious about clothing? Consider the lilies of the field, how they grow: they neither toil nor spin, [29] yet I tell you, even Solomon in all his glory was not arrayed like one of these. [30] But if God so clothes the grass of the field, which today is alive and tomorrow is thrown into the oven, will he not much more clothe you, O you of little faith? [31] Therefore do not be anxious, saying, ‘What shall we eat?’ or ‘What shall we drink?’ or ‘What shall we wear?’ [32] For the Gentiles seek after all these things, and your heavenly Father knows that you need them all. <strong>[33] But seek first the kingdom of God and his righteousness, and all these things will be added to you.</strong></p>

<p><strong>[34] “Therefore do not be anxious about tomorrow, for tomorrow will be anxious for itself. Sufficient for the day is its own trouble.</strong> (ESV)</p>

<h2 id="leviticus-26113">Leviticus 26:1–13</h2>

<p>Blessings for Obedience</p>

<p>[1] “You shall not make idols for yourselves or erect an image or pillar, and you shall not set up a figured stone in your land to bow down to it, for I am the LORD your God. [2] You shall keep my Sabbaths and reverence my sanctuary: I am the LORD.</p>

<p><strong>[3] “If you walk in my statutes and observe my commandments and do them, [4] then I will give you your rains in their season, and the land shall yield its increase, and the trees of the field shall yield their fruit. [5] Your threshing shall last to the time of the grape harvest, and the grape harvest shall last to the time for sowing. And you shall eat your bread to the full and dwell in your land securely.</strong> [6] I will give peace in the land, and you shall lie down, and none shall make you afraid. And I will remove harmful beasts from the land, and the sword shall not go through your land. [7] You shall chase your enemies, and they shall fall before you by the sword. [8] Five of you shall chase a hundred, and a hundred of you shall chase ten thousand, and your enemies shall fall before you by the sword. [9] I will turn to you and make you fruitful and multiply you and will confirm my covenant with you. [10] You shall eat old store long kept, and you shall clear out the old to make way for the new. [11] I will make my dwelling among you, and my soul shall not abhor you. [12] And I will walk among you and will be your God, and you shall be my people. [13] I am the LORD your God, who brought you out of the land of Egypt, that you should not be their slaves. And I have broken the bars of your yoke and made you walk erect. (ESV)</p>

<h2 id="ezekiel-362232">Ezekiel 36:22–32</h2>

<p>I Will Put My Spirit Within You</p>

<p>[22] “Therefore say to the house of Israel, Thus says the Lord GOD: It is not for your sake, O house of Israel, that I am about to act, but for the sake of my holy name, which you have profaned among the nations to which you came. [23] And I will vindicate the holiness of my great name, which has been profaned among the nations, and which you have profaned among them. And the nations will know that I am the LORD, declares the Lord GOD, when through you I vindicate my holiness before their eyes. [24] I will take you from the nations and gather you from all the countries and bring you into your own land. <strong>[25] I will sprinkle clean water on you, and you shall be clean from all your uncleannesses, and from all your idols I will cleanse you. [26] And I will give you a new heart, and a new spirit I will put within you. And I will remove the heart of stone from your flesh and give you a heart of flesh. [27] And I will put my Spirit within you, and cause you to walk in my statutes and be careful to obey my rules.</strong> [28] You shall dwell in the land that I gave to your fathers, and you shall be my people, and I will be your God. [29] And I will deliver you from all your uncleannesses. And I will summon the grain and make it abundant and lay no famine upon you. [30] I will make the fruit of the tree and the increase of the field abundant, that you may never again suffer the disgrace of famine among the nations. [31] Then you will remember your evil ways, and your deeds that were not good, and you will loathe yourselves for your iniquities and your abominations. [32] It is not for your sake that I will act, declares the Lord GOD; let that be known to you. Be ashamed and confounded for your ways, O house of Israel. (ESV)</p>

<h2 id="deuteronomy-101222">Deuteronomy 10:12–22</h2>

<p>Circumcise Your Heart</p>

<p><strong>[12] “And now, Israel, what does the LORD your God require of you, but to fear the LORD your God, to walk in all his ways, to love him, to serve the LORD your God with all your heart and with all your soul, [13] and to keep the commandments and statutes of the LORD, which I am commanding you today for your good? [14] Behold, to the LORD your God belong heaven and the heaven of heavens, the earth with all that is in it. [15] Yet the LORD set his heart in love on your fathers and chose their offspring after them, you above all peoples, as you are this day. [16] Circumcise therefore the foreskin of your heart, and be no longer stubborn.</strong> [17] For the LORD your God is God of gods and Lord of lords, the great, the mighty, and the awesome God, who is not partial and takes no bribe. [18] He executes justice for the fatherless and the widow, and loves the sojourner, giving him food and clothing. [19] Love the sojourner, therefore, for you were sojourners in the land of Egypt. [20] You shall fear the LORD your God. You shall serve him and hold fast to him, and by his name you shall swear. [21] He is your praise. He is your God, who has done for you these great and terrifying things that your eyes have seen. [22] Your fathers went down to Egypt seventy persons, and now the LORD your God has made you as numerous as the stars of heaven. (ESV)</p>

<h2 id="proverbs-102123">Proverbs 10:21–23</h2>

<p>[21] The lips of the righteous feed many,<br />
      but fools die for lack of sense.<br />
 <strong>[22] The blessing of the LORD makes rich,</strong><br />
      <strong>and he adds no sorrow with it.</strong><br />
 [23] Doing wrong is like a joke to a fool,<br />
      but wisdom is pleasure to a man of understanding. (ESV)</p>

<h2 id="ecclesiastes-5820">Ecclesiastes 5:8–20</h2>

<p>The Vanity of Wealth and Honor</p>

<p>[8] If you see in a province the oppression of the poor and the violation of justice and righteousness, do not be amazed at the matter, for the high official is watched by a higher, and there are yet higher ones over them. [9] But this is gain for a land in every way: a king committed to cultivated fields.</p>

<p><strong>[10] He who loves money will not be satisfied with money, nor he who loves wealth with his income; this also is vanity.</strong> [11] When goods increase, they increase who eat them, and what advantage has their owner but to see them with his eyes? [12] Sweet is the sleep of a laborer, whether he eats little or much, but the full stomach of the rich will not let him sleep.</p>

<p>[13] There is a grievous evil that I have seen under the sun: riches were kept by their owner to his hurt, [14] and those riches were lost in a bad venture. And he is father of a son, but he has nothing in his hand. [15] As he came from his mother’s womb he shall go again, naked as he came, and shall take nothing for his toil that he may carry away in his hand. [16] This also is a grievous evil: just as he came, so shall he go, and what gain is there to him who toils for the wind? [17] Moreover, all his days he eats in darkness in much vexation and sickness and anger.</p>

<p>[18] Behold, what I have seen to be good and fitting is to eat and drink and find enjoyment in all the toil with which one toils under the sun the few days of his life that God has given him, for this is his lot. [19] Everyone also to whom God has given wealth and possessions and power to enjoy them, and to accept his lot and rejoice in his toil—this is the gift of God. [20] For he will not much remember the days of his life because God keeps him occupied with joy in his heart. (ESV)</p>

<h2 id="1-timothy-6610">1 Timothy 6:6–10</h2>

<p>[6] But godliness with contentment is great gain, [7] for we brought nothing into the world, and we cannot take anything out of the world. [8] But if we have food and clothing, with these we will be content. [9] But those who desire to be rich fall into temptation, into a snare, into many senseless and harmful desires that plunge people into ruin and destruction. <strong>[10] For the love of money is a root of all kinds of evils. It is through this craving that some have wandered away from the faith and pierced themselves with many pangs.</strong> (ESV)</p>

<h2 id="luke-121315">Luke 12:13–15</h2>

<p>The Parable of the Rich Fool</p>

<p>[13] Someone in the crowd said to him, “Teacher, tell my brother to divide the inheritance with me.” [14] But he said to him, “Man, who made me a judge or arbitrator over you?” <strong>[15] And he said to them, “Take care, and be on your guard against all covetousness, for one’s life does not consist in the abundance of his possessions.”</strong> (ESV)</p>

<h2 id="2-corinthians-969">2 Corinthians 9:6–9</h2>

<p>The Cheerful Giver</p>

<p>[6] The point is this: whoever sows sparingly will also reap sparingly, and whoever sows bountifully will also reap bountifully. [7] Each one must give as he has decided in his heart, not reluctantly or under compulsion, for God loves a cheerful giver. <strong>[8] And God is able to make all grace abound to you, so that having all sufficiency in all things at all times, you may abound in every good work.</strong> [9] As it is written,</p>

<p>“He has distributed freely, he has given to the poor;<br />
      his righteousness endures forever.” (ESV)</p>

<h2 id="matthew-61924">Matthew 6:19–24</h2>

<p>Lay Up Treasures in Heaven</p>

<p><strong>[19] “Do not lay up for yourselves treasures on earth, where moth and rust destroy and where thieves break in and steal, [20] but lay up for yourselves treasures in heaven, where neither moth nor rust destroys and where thieves do not break in and steal. [21] For where your treasure is, there your heart will be also.</strong></p>

<p>[22] “The eye is the lamp of the body. So, if your eye is healthy, your whole body will be full of light, [23] but if your eye is bad, your whole body will be full of darkness. If then the light in you is darkness, how great is the darkness!</p>

<p><strong>[24] “No one can serve two masters, for either he will hate the one and love the other, or he will be devoted to the one and despise the other. You cannot serve God and money.</strong> (ESV)</p>

<h2 id="philippians-41020">Philippians 4:10–20</h2>

<p>God’s Provision</p>

<p>[10] I rejoiced in the Lord greatly that now at length you have revived your concern for me. You were indeed concerned for me, but you had no opportunity. [11] Not that I am speaking of being in need, for I have learned, in whatever situation I am, to be content. <strong>[12] I know how to be brought low, and I know how to abound. In any and every circumstance, I have learned the secret of facing plenty and hunger, abundance and need. [13] I can do all things through him who strengthens me.</strong></p>

<p>[14] Yet it was kind of you to share my trouble. [15] And you Philippians yourselves know that in the beginning of the gospel, when I left Macedonia, no church entered into partnership with me in giving and receiving, except you only. [16] Even in Thessalonica you sent me help for my needs once and again. [17] Not that I seek the gift, but I seek the fruit that increases to your credit. <strong>[18] I have received full payment, and more. I am well supplied, having received from Epaphroditus the gifts you sent, a fragrant offering, a sacrifice acceptable and pleasing to God. [19] And my God will supply every need of yours according to his riches in glory in Christ Jesus. [20] To our God and Father be glory forever and ever. Amen.</strong> (ESV)</p>

<h2 id="policy-areas">Policy Areas</h2>

<embed src="https://dl.hesaid.love/Political_Manifesto_Policy_Areas.pdf" type="application/pdf" width="100%" height="600px" />

<h2 id="faith-to-fall-back-on---hunter-hayes">Faith to Fall Back On - Hunter Hayes</h2>

<iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/2mTcupWbSEH3CpOQyd9Ztx?utm_source=generator&amp;theme=0" width="100%" height="152" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe>

<div id="rg_embed_link_182389" class="rg_embed_link" data-song-id="182389">Read <a href="https://genius.com/Hunter-hayes-faith-to-fall-back-on-lyrics">“Faith to Fall Back On” by Hunter Hayes</a> on Genius</div>
<script crossorigin="" src="https://genius.com/songs/182389/embed.js"></script>

<h2 id="right-here-waiting-澀谷駅前等---felix-lam-felix-林智樂">Right Here Waiting (澀谷駅前等) - Felix Lam (Felix 林智樂)</h2>

<iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/1UyAVLliY9kByk6reuuzDa?utm_source=generator&amp;theme=0" width="100%" height="152" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe>

<h3 id="lyrics">Lyrics</h3>

<p>任路人避一陣雨<br />
雨過後再未重遇<br />
我卻死心塌地 呆站在原處<br />
只有青春有甚麼可以輸</p>

<p>雨季走了突來暴雪<br />
雪再飄過換寒暑<br />
兩腳即使顫動 情緒卻鎖住<br />
一片忠心這是我的短處</p>

<p>耐性的比賽 像隻忠犬的愛<br />
長流細水編織典故方可以跨世代<br />
善良的車站 盡其一生替戀人乘載<br />
風雪我都依然觀賞尾班車開</p>

<p>被雪花淹蓋 蒙著兩眼看將來<br />
人潮暗湧一心找你充滿絕望和期待<br />
自殘式忍耐 歷遍春花秋葉從沒有悔改<br />
當你的芳蹤也石沉大海</p>

<p>背唱片店自言自語<br />
語氣輕似唸情書<br />
信有一千歲命 時間太充裕<br />
所有光陰押下我的賭注</p>

<p>耐性的比賽 像隻忠犬的愛<br />
長流細水編織典故方可以跨世代<br />
善良的車站 盡其一生替戀人乘載<br />
相信有生之年總可妄想天開</p>

<p>被雪花淹蓋 蒙著兩眼看將來<br />
人潮暗湧一心找你充滿絕望和期待<br />
自殘式忍耐 歷遍春花秋葉從沒有悔改<br />
會有歷史記載 令後代動容的愛</p>

<p>耐性的比賽 直到風光不再<br />
原來澀谷東急總店消失我都會在<br />
做遊客地標 讓每一位因為我等到所愛<br />
所以我等不來亦視為很應該</p>

<p>像潦倒乞丐 垂垂老矣也痴呆<br />
繁榮會死比不起我這故事更令別人無奈<br />
任誰勸喻移不開一千個萬年爭取一夕愛</p>

<p>自鳴年紀輕斗膽與愛競賽<br />
萬年後今天待旁觀者感慨<br />
Writer(s): Chak Yat Sang<br />
Lyrics powered by <a href="https://www.musixmatch.com/lyrics/Felix-%E6%9E%97%E6%99%BA%E6%A8%82/%E6%BE%80%E8%B0%B7%E9%A7%85%E5%89%8D%E7%AD%89" target="_blank">musixmatch</a></p>

<h2 id="meme">Meme</h2>

<p><img src="/6e6oxuhH0eDqjNkH.jpg" alt="Martin Luther translating the Bible" /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first of a series of policy posts as I prepare to register a political party in Great Britain. I intend to apply the principles in my personal life where applicable. Someone has got to start walking in His statutes, observing His commandments, and doing them.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Cost-benefit Analysis</title><link href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-cost-benefit-analysis/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Cost-benefit Analysis" /><published>2025-03-16T21:45:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-18T08:45:44+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/posts/on-cost-benefit-analysis</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-cost-benefit-analysis/"><![CDATA[<p>I attended an event yesterday called <em>Tea With Your MP</em>. I downed several cups of coffee, which are considered luxury goods for me nowadays. It has been weeks since I had my favourite vanilla latte with coconut milk.</p>

<p>I spent two and a half hours teaching secondary school students at my table how to cheat their A-Level exams by building up muscle memory using past papers and mark schemes. I also shared my concerns about Artificial Intelligence on both the economic impact and national security. My local representative in parliament has done his homework on the subject, and he used the example of the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Great_horse_manure_crisis_of_1894" target="_blank">Great Horse Manure Crisis of 1894</a> in London to reassure me that there was no need to panic. I responded bitterly with the throw-the-dice and see who was right in the end analogy. I was not brave enough to pull out the I-have-confirmation-from-the-Holy-Spirit card since my local MP took his Oath on a <a href="#jps-vs-kjv">JPS Bible</a>.</p>

<p>If this was the old me, I would have called it a day and told myself not to worry too much since I most likely got it wrong. And I should leave the matter to people who know what they are doing. I also asked if there was a chance to volunteer for events since I enjoyed being a bad influence and teaching secondary students how to cheat, as well as bitching and moaning about the Home Office caseworkers with other local constituents who are also first-generation immigrants.</p>

<p>I felt somewhat deflated after the event and wondered whether I had indeed gone batshit crazy given my recent pattern of behaviour and how understandably it could be interpreted as such by anyone who does not bother with the context. I asked the Lord for guidance on my walk back home.</p>

<p>Earlier this morning, I got rather annoyed again when I was in the shower doing unspeakable things. The following cost-benefit analysis appeared in my head.</p>

<p>If I got it wrong, what is the worst-case scenario? I become a laughing stock and maybe get my 30 seconds of fame by <a href="../on-legislature/" target="_blank">shouting God and love</a> at the world. Boss Man would take up residence in a handful of minds for 30 seconds. I am already <a href="../on-sexual-theology/" target="_blank">90% there</a> on being a laughing stock.</p>

<p>If I got it right, then I keep my clear conscience before God when <a href="https://letter.hesaid.love/" target="_blank">shit hits the fan</a>, and I get to say <a href="../on-money-and-fiscal-policy/#challenge" target="_blank">bitch</a>, I told you so.</p>

<p>The annoying part? I realised He set me up by giving me the <a href="../on-gethsemane/" target="_blank">thought experiment</a> to test pastors and theologians. And I already made my choice when I pulled that <a href="../reasoning-behind-preaching-mainland-china-jonah-style/" target="_blank">stunt</a> in mainland China last October.</p>

<p>I do not know what Jonah’s vow was, but I know what my vow was.</p>

<p>I need to <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Politically_exposed_person" target="_blank">expose myself</a> a bit more.</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="jonah-2">Jonah 2</h2>

<p>Jonah’s Prayer</p>

<p>[1] Then Jonah prayed to the LORD his God from the belly of the fish, [2] saying,</p>

<p>“I called out to the LORD, out of my distress,<br />
      and he answered me;<br />
 out of the belly of Sheol I cried,<br />
      and you heard my voice.<br />
 [3] For you cast me into the deep,<br />
      into the heart of the seas,<br />
      and the flood surrounded me;<br />
 all your breakers and your waves<br />
      passed over me.<br />
 [4] Then I said, ‘I am driven away<br />
      from your sight;<br />
 yet I shall again look<br />
      upon your holy temple.’<br />
 [5] The waters closed in over me to take my life;<br />
      the deep surrounded me;<br />
 weeds were wrapped about my head.<br />
 [6] To the roots of the mountains I went down,<br />
      to the land whose bars closed upon me forever.<br />
 Yet you brought up my life from the pit,<br />
      O LORD my God.<br />
 [7] When my life was fainting away,<br />
      I remembered the LORD,<br />
 and my prayer came to you,<br />
      into your holy temple.<br />
 [8] Those who pay regard to vain idols<br />
      forsake their hope of steadfast love.<br />
 <b>[9] But I with the voice of thanksgiving<br />
      will sacrifice to you;<br />
 what I have vowed I will pay.<br />
      Salvation belongs to the LORD!”</b><br /></p>

<p>[10] And the LORD spoke to the fish, and it vomited Jonah out upon the dry land. (ESV)</p>

<h2 id="isaiah-6417">Isaiah 64:1–7</h2>

<p>[1] Oh that you would rend the heavens and come down,<br />
      that the mountains might quake at your presence—<br />
 [2] as when fire kindles brushwood<br />
      and the fire causes water to boil—<br />
 to make your name known to your adversaries,<br />
      and that the nations might tremble at your presence!<br />
 [3] When you did awesome things that we did not look for,<br />
      you came down, the mountains quaked at your presence.<br />
 [4] From of old no one has heard<br />
      or perceived by the ear,<br />
 no eye has seen a God besides you,<br />
      who acts for those who wait for him.<br />
 [5] You meet him who joyfully works righteousness,<br />
      those who remember you in your ways.<br />
 Behold, you were angry, and we sinned;<br />
      in our sins we have been a long time, and shall we be saved?<br />
 [6] We have all become like one who is unclean,<br />
      and all our righteous deeds are like a polluted garment.<br />
 We all fade like a leaf,<br />
      and our iniquities, like the wind, take us away.<br />
 [7] There is no one who calls upon your name,<br />
      who rouses himself to take hold of you;<br />
 for you have hidden your face from us,<br />
      and have made us melt in the hand of our iniquities. (ESV)<br /></p>

<h2 id="jps-vs-kjv">JPS vs KJV</h2>

<embed src="https://dl.hesaid.love/JPS_vs_KJV_Comparison.pdf" type="application/pdf" width="100%" height="600px" />]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I attended an event yesterday called Tea With Your MP. I downed several cups of coffee, which are considered luxury goods for me nowadays. It has been weeks since I had my favourite vanilla latte with coconut milk.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Pizza</title><link href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-pizza/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Pizza" /><published>2025-03-14T12:21:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-14T13:16:32+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/posts/on-pizza</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-pizza/"><![CDATA[<p>If you attended the 2018 Keble Ball and you had pizza, then you are more than welcome, and please try not to fuck things up if you are running for office or plan to run in the future.</p>

<p>If you did not attend the 2018 Keble Ball, then I just want to apologise for feeding potentially up to 1,500 pretentious Oxford grads when they were young, stupid and drunk during a summer night back in 2018. I was punished severely the following morning and got a hangover for the first time in my life. I was also craving badly for fish.</p>

<p><img src="/Punished_Him_Severely.webp" alt="Punished him severely" /></p>

<p><img src="/dGvjctCppu7SfuXSfc.jpg" alt="Let's pray" /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you attended the 2018 Keble Ball and you had pizza, then you are more than welcome, and please try not to fuck things up if you are running for office or plan to run in the future.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On WhatsApp</title><link href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-whatsapp/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On WhatsApp" /><published>2025-03-13T13:40:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-14T13:21:49+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/posts/on-whatsapp</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-whatsapp/"><![CDATA[<p>I made a new friend recently—a fellow computer scientist/software engineer who suspiciously knows too much philosophy and was lurking around a WhatsApp group chat. The dude is super weird, does not have a phone and uses an Oyster card. I cannot be late for more than 20-30min of our agreed meeting time. And there is no backing out at the last minute.</p>

<p>Frankly, I might enjoy that way of life. I already got quite into self-hosting. Things stopped working one by one as I went broke. Friends first, then iCloud and 1Password, and now WhatsApp. The only reason why I still haven’t sold my iPhone is because of the various chat applications, including but not limited to WhatsApp and WeChat. I did not expect to share the Martin Luther meme in my treasured meme collection one day, but life stopped making sense last October. I stopped worrying about tomorrow and just took it day by day without any expectations.</p>

<p>After a recent realisation, I think true friends would make more than an effort to arrive on time. I have got an iPhone 15 Pro to sell.</p>

<p>The only issue is the dude went to a <a href="../reasoning-behind-going-rome-fig-tree/" target="_blank">catholic</a> school.</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="john-151217">John 15:12–17</h2>

<p>[12] “This is my commandment, that you love one another as I have loved you. [13] Greater love has no one than this, that someone lay down his life for his friends. [14] You are my friends if you do what I command you. [15] No longer do I call you servants, for the servant does not know what his master is doing; but I have called you friends, for all that I have heard from my Father I have made known to you. [16] You did not choose me, but I chose you and appointed you that you should go and bear fruit and that your fruit should abide, so that whatever you ask the Father in my name, he may give it to you. [17] These things I command you, so that you will love one another. (ESV)</p>

<h2 id="matthew-62534">Matthew 6:25–34</h2>

<p>Do Not Be Anxious</p>

<p>[25] “Therefore I tell you, do not be anxious about your life, what you will eat or what you will drink, nor about your body, what you will put on. Is not life more than food, and the body more than clothing? [26] Look at the birds of the air: they neither sow nor reap nor gather into barns, and yet your heavenly Father feeds them. Are you not of more value than they? [27] And which of you by being anxious can add a single hour to his span of life? [28] And why are you anxious about clothing? Consider the lilies of the field, how they grow: they neither toil nor spin, [29] yet I tell you, even Solomon in all his glory was not arrayed like one of these. [30] But if God so clothes the grass of the field, which today is alive and tomorrow is thrown into the oven, will he not much more clothe you, O you of little faith? [31] Therefore do not be anxious, saying, ‘What shall we eat?’ or ‘What shall we drink?’ or ‘What shall we wear?’ [32] For the Gentiles seek after all these things, and your heavenly Father knows that you need them all. [33] But seek first the kingdom of God and his righteousness, and all these things will be added to you.</p>

<p>[34] “Therefore do not be anxious about tomorrow, for tomorrow will be anxious for itself. Sufficient for the day is its own trouble. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p><img src="/6p04RpxvPVzQvemVnd.jpg" alt="Pope Zuckerberg" /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I made a new friend recently—a fellow computer scientist/software engineer who suspiciously knows too much philosophy and was lurking around a WhatsApp group chat. The dude is super weird, does not have a phone and uses an Oyster card. I cannot be late for more than 20-30min of our agreed meeting time. And there is no backing out at the last minute.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Fuck-up</title><link href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-fuck-up/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Fuck-up" /><published>2025-03-12T07:04:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-12T07:04:00+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/posts/on-fuck-up</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-fuck-up/"><![CDATA[<p>He sent a rampant homosexual.</p>

<p><img src="/Roll_Safe_meme.jpg" alt="Think about it" /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[He sent a rampant homosexual.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Humanity’s Bestseller</title><link href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-humanity-s-bestseller/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Humanity’s Bestseller" /><published>2025-03-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-17T14:47:51+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/posts/on-humanity-s-bestseller</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-humanity-s-bestseller/"><![CDATA[<p>It dawned on me yesterday that as many as 7 out of 10 “Christians” I have met on this 24-week and 3-day faith journey act as they have barely read humanity’s bestseller. I know I cheated a lot using Artificial Intelligence over the last 171 days, and my eccentricity is evident to anyone who knows me personally. I made the <a href="../../cuntslied/" target="_blank">open invitation</a> because He had much to say in the long-ass bestseller. But if the “Christians” I know spent half as much effort into learning about Him than procuring more <a href="../on-drug-money-addiction/" target="_blank">drugs</a>, we would be living in a not-so-shitty world right now. We <a href="../on-indifference/" target="_blank">blame each other</a> for this shitty world and spend zero effort in contributing our share to make things better.</p>

<p>I topped up $12 in my OpenAI account when launching the project <a href="https://biblesays.love/" target="_blank">Bible Says Love</a> three months ago. I even built a simple mechanism to prevent abuse. I worry unnecessarily too much.</p>

<p>All of the stereotypes I had about Christianity turned out to be wrong once I started reading the bestseller. It is the closest thing to <a href="../reasoning-behind-going-rome-fig-tree/" target="_blank">magic</a> I had ever come across in the 28 years of my life. I am not proud to make the following statement. I’m merely stating a fact. And they seem useless now that I have the <em>Teacher</em> and the <em>Textbook</em> to learn from. I studied four undergraduate degrees in the last decade, specialising in mathematics, physics, computer science, philosophy and modern ballet. Not a single book or research paper I read made me feel the truth cutting through my bones into my soul.</p>

<p>And no, Christianity is not a religion. Why would you call the truth a religion?</p>

<p>I will slap you with the bestseller if you inform me the truth is subjective in person.</p>

<hr />

<p><img src="/tZC3qndFY6msRF4j7k.jpg" alt="PLS HELP" /></p>

<p><img src="/MGqdpJ1E334Ej90Tn4.jpg" alt="I will slap you" /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[It dawned on me yesterday that as many as 7 out of 10 “Christians” I have met on this 24-week and 3-day faith journey act as they have barely read humanity’s bestseller. I know I cheated a lot using Artificial Intelligence over the last 171 days, and my eccentricity is evident to anyone who knows me personally. I made the open invitation because He had much to say in the long-ass bestseller. But if the “Christians” I know spent half as much effort into learning about Him than procuring more drugs, we would be living in a not-so-shitty world right now. We blame each other for this shitty world and spend zero effort in contributing our share to make things better.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Legislature</title><link href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-legislature/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Legislature" /><published>2025-03-11T14:50:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-17T15:51:06+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/posts/on-legislature</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-legislature/"><![CDATA[<p>In my typical fashion, I tried spamming the UK Parliament earlier today after scraping the email addresses of 642 MPs. I also have a list of legislatures from 190+ countries that may or may not have been loaded into a Redis sorted set on an AWS EC2 instance for web scraping. The UK Parliament email server blocked my first attempt at sending the following email to 100 MPs. Then I realised my message might not be that important, and the MPs I was emailing could have a life to save today. Reading my email might not be the most constructive use of their valuable time. If my message is indeed that important, then surely one email should be more than enough. I called it a day after writing to a handful of Lords, who say Jesus Christ and Artificial Intelligence the most, according to TheyWorkForYou.com.</p>

<p>I will spend the rest of today reflecting on my hypocritical lack of faith in the United Kingdom’s legislature.</p>

<p>I’m not being sarcastic this time.</p>

<p>Edit: Representatives from <a href="https://github.com/zyang01/email-scraping/blob/main/gov/legislatures.csv" target="_blank">legislatures in 190+ countries</a> will be receiving the updated email. I spent nearly a decade trying to predict financial market price movement in the next second, and I declared bankruptcy five months ago. Do you know how annoying it was to stumble across random passages in a bestseller written nearly 2,000 years ago and find out I had been accidentally fulfilling prophecies? 🤦🤷🙄</p>

<p>13 March 2025 Update: Sprinkled <a href="https://dl.hesaid.love/campaignRecipients_2500541_3432911_0211dad95f5c60db3590c02dbc60e821.csv" target="_blank">1,335 representatives</a> from legislatures. The number is accidentally <a href="https://www.gotquestions.org/tribulation-1260-1290-1335-days.html" target="_blank">very Daniel</a>. Startling <a href="https://dl.hesaid.love/campaignRecipients_2501789_3432911_c150a2903025aa06d6289a42b5ee0096.csv" target="_blank">3,225 government officials</a>, including Bibi Netanyahu. Shared with <a href="https://dl.hesaid.love/campaignRecipients_2502635_3432911_2e6dce838b3cec25c230de30dc4b753d.csv" target="_blank">777 recipients</a> from 70+ international LGBTQIA+ organisations, including the <a href="https://www.lgbtchristians.eu/" target="_blank">European Forum of LGBTI+ Christian Groups</a>. The theology, philosophy, computer science, economics faculties and drug laboratories (a.k.a. business schools) of abominations of desolation around the world next.</p>

<p>14 March 2025 Update: Considering the <a href="https://rosebay.uk/schedule-of-events/" target="_blank">Rosebay 2025 season</a> is about to start on Easter weekend next month, it is vital to raise awareness of <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Narcissistic_personality_disorder" target="_blank">Narcissistic Personality Disorder (NPD)</a> to prevent another young gay man from taking <a href="../on-background-music/#shortcut" target="_blank">the shortcut</a> I almost took last year to meet our maker. The abominations of desolation around the globe will have to wait. Commencing the sprinkling of <a href="https://dl.hesaid.love/world_media_outlets.csv" target="_blank">80,000+ worldwide media outlets</a>. I also have a water baptism to attend on Easter weekend. 🤞</p>

<p>15 March 2025 Update: Included <a href="https://dl.hesaid.love/psychology.csv" target="_blank">3,643 experts</a> in the field of psychology from the <a href="https://www.apa.org/" target="_blank">American Psychological Association (APA)</a> in the United States, the <a href="https://www.bps.org.uk/" target="_blank">British Psychological Society (BPS)</a> and the <a href="https://www.hcpc-uk.org/" target="_blank">Health and Care Professions Council (HCPC)</a> in the United Kingdom, the <a href="https://cpa.ca/" target="_blank">Canadian Psychological Association (CPA)</a> in Canada, the <a href="https://psychology.org.au/" target="_blank">Australian Psychological Society (APS)</a> and the <a href="https://www.ahpra.gov.au/" target="_blank">Australian Health Practitioner Regulation Agency (AHPRA)</a> in Australia, and the <a href="https://www.efpa.eu/" target="_blank">European Federation of Psychologists’ Associations (EFPA)</a> in the European Union. I couldn’t quite wait anymore for my New Millennium holiday, and my email infrastructure seems stable enough to handle the load, sexual innuendo somewhat unintended. Loaded <a href="https://dl.hesaid.love/edu.csv" target="_blank">8,515 esteemed modest scholars</a> from our best and finest abominations of desolation around the globe. And <a href="https://dl.hesaid.love/christian_orgs.txt" target="_blank">2,568 contacts</a> from <a href="https://dl.hesaid.love/Suspected_Christian_Organizations.pdf" target="_blank">31 suspected “Christian” organisations</a>.</p>

<p>17 March 2025 Update: Added contact emails of <a href="https://dl.hesaid.love/uk_charity_emails.txt" target="_blank">138,447 charities</a> and <a href="https://dl.hesaid.love/uk_mp_emails.txt" target="_blank">642 MPs</a> in the United Kingdom.</p>

<p>I will keep <a href="#shouting-love">shouting love</a> at the world till the day He comes back or I die, whichever comes first.</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="isaiah-494">Isaiah 49:4</h2>

<p>[4] But I said, “I have labored in vain;<br />
      I have spent my strength for nothing and vanity;<br />
 yet surely my right is with the LORD,<br />
      and my recompense with my God.” (ESV)</p>

<h2 id="ezekiel-2230">Ezekiel 22:30</h2>

<p>[30] And I sought for a man among them who should build up the wall and stand in the breach before me for the land, that I should not destroy it, but I found none. (ESV)</p>

<h2 id="isaiah-58612">Isaiah 58:6–12</h2>

<p>[6] “Is not this the fast that I choose:<br />
      to loose the bonds of wickedness,<br />
      to undo the straps of the yoke,<br />
 to let the oppressed go free,<br />
      and to break every yoke?<br />
 [7] Is it not to share your bread with the hungry<br />
      and bring the homeless poor into your house;<br />
 when you see the naked, to cover him,<br />
      and not to hide yourself from your own flesh?<br />
 [8] Then shall your light break forth like the dawn,<br />
      and your healing shall spring up speedily;<br />
 your righteousness shall go before you;<br />
      the glory of the LORD shall be your rear guard.<br />
 [9] Then you shall call, and the LORD will answer;<br />
      you shall cry, and he will say, ‘Here I am.’<br />
 If you take away the yoke from your midst,<br />
      the pointing of the finger, and speaking wickedness,<br />
 [10] if you pour yourself out for the hungry<br />
      and satisfy the desire of the afflicted,<br />
 then shall your light rise in the darkness<br />
      and your gloom be as the noonday.<br />
 [11] And the LORD will guide you continually<br />
      and satisfy your desire in scorched places<br />
      and make your bones strong;<br />
 and you shall be like a watered garden,<br />
      like a spring of water,<br />
      whose waters do not fail.<br />
 [12] And your ancient ruins shall be rebuilt;<br />
      you shall raise up the foundations of many generations;<br />
 you shall be called the repairer of the breach,<br />
      the restorer of streets to dwell in. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="on-love-artificial-intelligence-andnarcissistic-personality-disorder">On Love, Artificial Intelligence and Narcissistic Personality Disorder</h2>

<p>Dear Member of the Legislature,</p>

<p>I hope this email finds you well.</p>

<p>Read this email in your preferred language:<br />
🔗 <a href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-legislature/" target="_blank">Click here to translate</a><br />
🌐 ipfs://bafybeicisy3p7wnvrmattzb7cnqi43bdlmrqgg466e5myovc2u3k3yzdcm</p>

<p>🌎 <a href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-legislature/" target="_blank">Select Your Language</a> 📩<br />
✅ 🇬🇧 English: Click the link to translate this email into your language.<br />
✅ 🇪🇸 Español (Spanish): Haga clic en el enlace para traducir este correo a su idioma.<br />
✅ 🇫🇷 Français (French): Cliquez sur le lien pour traduire cet e-mail dans votre langue.<br />
✅ 🇷🇺 Русский (Russian): Нажмите на ссылку, чтобы перевести это письмо на ваш язык.<br />
✅ 🇨🇳 中文 (Chinese - Simplified): 点击链接，将此电子邮件翻译成您的语言。<br />
✅ 🇦🇪 العربية (Arabic): انقر على الرابط لترجمة هذا البريد الإلكتروني إلى لغتك.<br />
✅ 🇮🇳 हिन्दी (Hindi): अपनी भाषा में अनुवाद करने के लिए लिंक पर क्लिक करें।<br />
✅ 🇵🇹 Português (Portuguese): Clique no link para traduzir este e-mail para o seu idioma.<br />
✅ 🇧🇩 বাংলা (Bengali): আপনার ভাষায় অনুবাদ করতে লিঙ্কে ক্লিক করুন।<br />
✅ 🇯🇵 日本語 (Japanese): リンクをクリックして、このメールをあなたの言語に翻訳してください。<br />
✅ 🇩🇪 Deutsch (German): Klicken Sie auf den Link, um diese E-Mail in Ihre Sprache zu übersetzen.<br />
✅ 🇵🇰 اردو (Urdu): اپنی زبان میں ترجمہ کرنے کے لیے لنک پر کلک کریں۔<br />
✅ 🇮🇳 ਪੰਜਾਬੀ (Punjabi): ਆਪਣੇ ਭਾਸ਼ਾ ਵਿੱਚ ਅਨੁਵਾਦ ਕਰਨ ਲਈ ਲਿੰਕ ‘ਤੇ ਕਲਿੱਕ ਕਰੋ।<br />
✅ 🇮🇳 తెలుగు (Telugu): మీ భాషలోకి అనువదించడానికి లింక్‌పై క్లిక్ చేయండి.<br />
✅ 🇮🇳 मराठी (Marathi): आपल्या भाषेत भाषांतरित करण्यासाठी लिंकवर क्लिक करा.<br />
✅ 🇮🇳🇱🇰 தமிழ் (Tamil): உங்கள் மொழிக்கு மொழிபெயர்க்க இணைப்பை கிளிக் செய்யவும்.<br />
✅ 🇹🇷 Türkçe (Turkish): E-postayı dilinize çevirmek için bağlantıya tıklayın.<br />
✅ 🇻🇳 Tiếng Việt (Vietnamese): Nhấp vào liên kết để dịch email này sang ngôn ngữ của bạn.<br />
✅ 🇰🇷 한국어 (Korean): 이 이메일을 귀하의 언어로 번역하려면 링크를 클릭하세요.<br />
✅ 🇮🇹 Italiano (Italian): Fai clic sul link per tradurre questa email nella tua lingua.<br />
✅ 🇮🇷 فارسی (Persian - Farsi): برای ترجمه این ایمیل به زبان خود روی لینک کلیک کنید.<br />
✅ 🇹🇭 ไทย (Thai): คลิกลิงก์เพื่อแปลอีเมลนี้เป็นภาษาของคุณ<br />
✅ 🇰🇪🇹🇿 Kiswahili (Swahili): Bofya kiungo ili kutafsiri barua pepe hii kwa lugha yako.</p>

<p>My name is Aaron. I’m a 28-year-old rampant homosexual currently residing in Barnet, London. In the last decade, I have studied four undergraduate degrees in the United Kingdom, including mathematics, physics, computer science, philosophy, and modern ballet. Less than 12 months ago, I worked remotely as a software engineer and consultant with a mid-six-figure pretax income. I single-handedly financially supported two adult younger siblings to study in London, paying overseas student fees.</p>

<p>I tried to take my first holiday in April last year at a gay/bi-naturist campsite in Peterborough. I ended up getting kicked out of the campsite three months later after giving them free full-site Wi-Fi coverage, declaring bankruptcy, and nearly throwing myself out of the fifth-floor balcony in my London home right in front of my younger sister.</p>

<p>I ordered a humanity’s bestseller on Amazon shortly after getting kicked out of the gay/bi-naturist campsite. Over the last 170 days, I travelled to Hong Kong, Shenzhen, Shanghai, Beijing, Macau, California, New York, Rome, Istanbul, Moscow, Tel Aviv and Jerusalem. I have also been sprinkling and potentially startling the nations via multiple Spotify Ads and email campaigns to warn the world of the socioeconomic tsunami brought about by Artificial Intelligence that we have never seen before in human history, which I believe will cause significant unemployment rates and global suffering for the bottom 90%. I consulted computer scientists from King’s College London and Imperial College London concerning my argument. Everyone was more pessimistic than I was.</p>

<p>Aside from the economic impact, my latest realisation over this past weekend involves national security. To briefly summarise my argument, anyone with the technical know-how to train a large language model can, in theory, construct dirty miniature devices by training their custom LLM or perhaps using one of the increasingly powerful open-source models on <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Aaron_Swartz" target="_blank">Aaron Swartz’s hard drives</a>.</p>

<p>You can find more details on my blog HeSaidLove.com. I faithfully and truthfully documented my 170-day journey through 270+ posts. You will also find the draft manifesto for a new political party I intend to launch shortly in the United Kingdom.</p>

<p><span id="shouting-love">I believe I’m supposed to bring you the following message.</span></p>

<p>Love is the greatest sacrifice one is willing to make. Just ask any father what they are willing to sacrifice for their child.</p>

<p>For Love and Devotion,<br />
Aaron Yang<br />
HeSaidLove.com<br />
11 March 2025<br />
Barnet, London</p>

<hr />

<p><img src="/6h93kexuawxz.jpg" alt="Remember Lot's wife" /></p>

<h2 id="the-flood---take-that">The Flood - Take That</h2>

<iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/2a3U3GTCvrcma7wetBtOpi?utm_source=generator&amp;theme=0" width="100%" height="152" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe>

<div id="rg_embed_link_2307790" class="rg_embed_link" data-song-id="2307790">Read <a href="https://genius.com/Take-that-the-flood-lyrics">“The Flood” by Take That</a> on Genius</div>
<script crossorigin="" src="https://genius.com/songs/2307790/embed.js"></script>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my typical fashion, I tried spamming the UK Parliament earlier today after scraping the email addresses of 642 MPs. I also have a list of legislatures from 190+ countries that may or may not have been loaded into a Redis sorted set on an AWS EC2 instance for web scraping. The UK Parliament email server blocked my first attempt at sending the following email to 100 MPs. Then I realised my message might not be that important, and the MPs I was emailing could have a life to save today. Reading my email might not be the most constructive use of their valuable time. If my message is indeed that important, then surely one email should be more than enough. I called it a day after writing to a handful of Lords, who say Jesus Christ and Artificial Intelligence the most, according to TheyWorkForYou.com.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Fucked</title><link href="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-fucked/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Fucked" /><published>2025-03-10T07:13:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-17T14:39:22+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaid.love/posts/on-fucked</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaid.love/posts/on-fucked/"><![CDATA[<blockquote>
  <p>If you are a <strong><em>stupid fucking idiot</em></strong> like <a href="../on-indifference/" target="_blank">this one</a>, or the word <strong><em>dictator</em></strong> is one of the words that shows up when I google your name, then <strong><em>this post is not for you</em></strong>.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>I participated in a three-day event this past Friday to Sunday called <strong>Encounter</strong> with the Pentecostal church my welcoming party goes to. To repeat myself, some of the pastors and theologians I met in this 24-week and 1-day journey will call the mental health institutions nearby and tell them to bring a bus if they saw our worship.</p>

<p>On the train back to London yesterday morning, the scale of how truly fucked we are, dawned on me. You can watch my director’s cut New Millenium present to the world for a quick revision on the definition of fucked. I don’t have confirmation from the Holy Spirit on this, but it is logically simple enough for anyone with a semi-functioning reasoning faculty to understand it.</p>

<p>I hope the work I have shown in the 270+ posts written on this 169-day journey is sufficient to demonstrate the power of Artificial Intelligence. I have received no help from anyone except a handful of friends who financially supported me up to this point to the best of their abilities. I am forever grateful for their support, even if they had only bought me one coffee, and they are in the top 10% of taxpayers in the United Kingdom. If you remain sceptical that you will <a href="https://letter.hesaid.love/" target="_blank">lose your job within two years</a> due to Artificial Intelligence, then more proof will come as I embark on a new and exciting journey. That was confirmed by the Holy Spirit this morning, shortly before I started this post.</p>

<p>I will end this post by leaving you with the following thoughts. Anyone with the technical know-how to train a large language model, including idiots and people with the word dictator on the first page of Google search results using their name, can, in theory, construct stinkily dirty miniature devices by training their custom LLM or perhaps using one of the increasingly powerful open-source models on <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Aaron_Swartz" target="_blank">Aaron Swartz’s hard drives</a>. They would need access to the key ingredients in my former colleague’s <a href="../on-acute-chemical-toxicity-uranium/" target="_blank">recipe</a>. I hope she did not end up eating that cake.</p>

<p>If you are reading this post and from law enforcement, you can call King’s College London and confirm that I dropped out of my Physics and Philosophy undergraduate degree after only one term. My student number is 1580407. I tried building a device that required a power source more than a 9v battery last year. I ended up getting kicked out of a gay/bi-naturist campsite, declaring bankruptcy, and nearly throwing myself out of the fifth-floor balcony of my London home right in front of my younger sister. Feel free to email me if you struggle to find my home address for a welfare visit using your intelligence capabilities. Alternatively, you will soon be able to locate the address on a registration application to the Electoral Commission. I’m also on the electoral register.</p>

<p>The <a href="../on-sheep-and-goats/" target="_blank">ethical thought experiment</a> I designed during COVID-19 is still coming true. I’m going to bring Him back. Divine intervention has only just begun.</p>

<p>For the 27 years of my previous life, I had always considered myself an agnostic, and I was never once an atheist. I had no evidence for or against God’s existence, and even if He exists, God’s business is God’s business. I’m human, and I mind my own business. Then some people, including my former business partner, decided to fuck with my business, He decided to make my business His business, and now it’s time to fuck some people’s business up.</p>

<p>After much delay and trouble, the date on my certificate of naturalisation as a British citizen is 30 November 2024.</p>

<p>To help fund the crusade, you can <a href="https://donate.hesaid.love" target="_blank">donate</a> a cup of coffee (vanilla latte with coconut milk) at London RPI or via the GoFundMe below. By donating, you consent to the publication of your email address. There is nothing you can hide from Him. I have a couple more items to list on eBay to raise the £150 non-refundable registration fee.</p>

<hr />

<div class="gfm-embed" data-url="https://www.gofundme.com/f/start-a-new-political-party-in-the-united-kingdom/widget/large?sharesheet=manage hero&amp;attribution_id=sl:9ef3cae9-33a0-40ca-b886-f80577ae1dce"></div>
<script defer="" src="https://www.gofundme.com/static/js/embed.js"></script>

<hr />

<h2 id="romans-13810">Romans 13:8–10</h2>

<p>Fulfilling the Law Through Love</p>

<p>[8] Owe no one anything, except to love each other, for the one who loves another has fulfilled the law. [9] For the commandments, “You shall not commit adultery, You shall not murder, You shall not steal, You shall not covet,” and any other commandment, are summed up in this word: “You shall love your neighbor as yourself.” [10] Love does no wrong to a neighbor; therefore love is the fulfilling of the law. (ESV)</p>

<h2 id="luke-112932">Luke 11:29–32</h2>

<p>The Sign of Jonah</p>

<p>[29] When the crowds were increasing, he began to say, “This generation is an evil generation. It seeks for a sign, but no sign will be given to it except the sign of Jonah. [30] For as Jonah became a sign to the people of Nineveh, so will the Son of Man be to this generation. [31] The queen of the South will rise up at the judgment with the men of this generation and condemn them, for she came from the ends of the earth to hear the wisdom of Solomon, and behold, something greater than Solomon is here. [32] The men of Nineveh will rise up at the judgment with this generation and condemn it, for they repented at the preaching of Jonah, and behold, something greater than Jonah is here. (ESV)</p>

<h2 id="isaiah-4219">Isaiah 42:1–9</h2>

<p>The LORD’s Chosen Servant</p>

<p>[1] Behold my servant, whom I uphold,<br />
  my chosen, in whom my soul delights;<br />
 I have put my Spirit upon him;<br />
  he will bring forth justice to the nations.<br />
 [2] He will not cry aloud or lift up his voice,<br />
  or make it heard in the street;<br />
 [3] a bruised reed he will not break,<br />
  and a faintly burning wick he will not quench;<br />
  he will faithfully bring forth justice.<br />
 [4] He will not grow faint or be discouraged<br />
  till he has established justice in the earth;<br />
  and the coastlands wait for his law.<br /></p>

<p>[5] Thus says God, the LORD,<br />
  who created the heavens and stretched them out,<br />
  who spread out the earth and what comes from it,<br />
 who gives breath to the people on it<br />
  and spirit to those who walk in it:<br />
 [6] “I am the LORD; I have called you in righteousness;<br />
  I will take you by the hand and keep you;<br />
 I will give you as a covenant for the people,<br />
  a light for the nations,<br />
 [7]  to open the eyes that are blind,<br />
 to bring out the prisoners from the dungeon,<br />
  from the prison those who sit in darkness.<br />
 [8] I am the LORD; that is my name;<br />
  my glory I give to no other,<br />
  nor my praise to carved idols.<br />
 [9] Behold, the former things have come to pass,<br />
  and new things I now declare;<br />
 before they spring forth<br />
  I tell you of them.” (ESV)<br /></p>

<h2 id="romans-3920">Romans 3:9–20</h2>

<p>No One Is Righteous</p>

<p>[9] What then? Are we Jews any better off? No, not at all. For we have already charged that all, both Jews and Greeks, are under sin, [10] as it is written:</p>

<p>“None is righteous, no, not one;<br />
 [11]  no one understands;<br />
  no one seeks for God.<br />
 [12] All have turned aside; together they have become worthless;<br />
  no one does good,<br />
  not even one.”<br />
 [13] “Their throat is an open grave;<br />
  they use their tongues to deceive.”<br />
 “The venom of asps is under their lips.”<br />
 [14]  “Their mouth is full of curses and bitterness.”<br />
 [15] “Their feet are swift to shed blood;<br />
 [16]  in their paths are ruin and misery,<br />
 [17] and the way of peace they have not known.”<br />
 [18]  “There is no fear of God before their eyes.”<br /></p>

<p>[19] Now we know that whatever the law says it speaks to those who are under the law, so that every mouth may be stopped, and the whole world may be held accountable to God. [20] For by works of the law no human being will be justified in his sight, since through the law comes knowledge of sin. (ESV)</p>

<h2 id="ezekiel-222331">Ezekiel 22:23–31</h2>

<p>[23] And the word of the LORD came to me: [24] “Son of man, say to her, You are a land that is not cleansed or rained upon in the day of indignation. [25] The conspiracy of her prophets in her midst is like a roaring lion tearing the prey; they have devoured human lives; they have taken treasure and precious things; they have made many widows in her midst. [26] Her priests have done violence to my law and have profaned my holy things. They have made no distinction between the holy and the common, neither have they taught the difference between the unclean and the clean, and they have disregarded my Sabbaths, so that I am profaned among them. [27] Her princes in her midst are like wolves tearing the prey, shedding blood, destroying lives to get dishonest gain. [28] And her prophets have smeared whitewash for them, seeing false visions and divining lies for them, saying, ‘Thus says the Lord GOD,’ when the LORD has not spoken. [29] The people of the land have practiced extortion and committed robbery. They have oppressed the poor and needy, and have extorted from the sojourner without justice. [30] And I sought for a man among them who should build up the wall and stand in the breach before me for the land, that I should not destroy it, but I found none. [31] Therefore I have poured out my indignation upon them. I have consumed them with the fire of my wrath. I have returned their way upon their heads, declares the Lord GOD.” (ESV)</p>

<h2 id="isaiah-591421">Isaiah 59:14–21</h2>

<p>Judgment and Redemption</p>

<p>[14] Justice is turned back,<br />
  and righteousness stands far away;<br />
 for truth has stumbled in the public squares,<br />
  and uprightness cannot enter.<br />
 [15] Truth is lacking,<br />
  and he who departs from evil makes himself a prey.<br /></p>

<p>The LORD saw it, and it displeased him<br />
  that there was no justice.<br />
 [16] He saw that there was no man,<br />
  and wondered that there was no one to intercede;<br />
 then his own arm brought him salvation,<br />
  and his righteousness upheld him.<br />
 [17] He put on righteousness as a breastplate,<br />
  and a helmet of salvation on his head;<br />
 he put on garments of vengeance for clothing,<br />
  and wrapped himself in zeal as a cloak.<br />
 [18] According to their deeds, so will he repay,<br />
  wrath to his adversaries, repayment to his enemies;<br />
  to the coastlands he will render repayment.<br />
 [19] So they shall fear the name of the LORD from the west,<br />
  and his glory from the rising of the sun;<br />
 for he will come like a rushing stream,<br />
  which the wind of the LORD drives.<br /></p>

<p>[20] “And a Redeemer will come to Zion,<br />
  to those in Jacob who turn from transgression,” declares the LORD.<br /></p>

<p>[21] “And as for me, this is my covenant with them,” says the LORD: “My Spirit that is upon you, and my words that I have put in your mouth, shall not depart out of your mouth, or out of the mouth of your offspring, or out of the mouth of your children’s offspring,” says the LORD, “from this time forth and forevermore.” (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="representation-of-the-people-act-1983"><a href="https://www.legislation.gov.uk/ukpga/1983/2" target="_blank">Representation of the People Act 1983</a></h2>

<pre><code class="language-none">1 Parliamentary electors.

(1) A person is entitled to vote as an elector at a parliamentary election in any constituency if on the date of the poll he—

    (a)is registered in the register of parliamentary electors for that constituency;

    (b)is not subject to any legal incapacity to vote (age apart);

    (c)is either a Commonwealth citizen or a citizen of the Republic of Ireland; and

    (d)is of voting age (that is, 18 years or over).

(2) A person is not entitled to vote as an elector—

    (a)more than once in the same constituency at any parliamentary election; or

    (b)in more than one constituency at a general election.
</code></pre>

<hr />

<p><img src="/6m63PvSF0ZPfCceH0j.png" alt="Wild enough for you?" /></p>

<p><img src="/XTXwwcCRzJze73wDTK.jpg" alt="Relationship between Pentecostals and Baptists summed up in two pictures" /></p>

<h2 id="coming-home-diddy--dirty-money-song">Coming Home (Diddy – Dirty Money song)</h2>

<div id="rg_embed_link_2338" class="rg_embed_link" data-song-id="2338">Read <a href="https://genius.com/Diddy-dirty-money-coming-home-lyrics">“Coming Home” by Diddy – Dirty Money</a> on Genius</div>
<script crossorigin="" src="https://genius.com/songs/2338/embed.js"></script>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a stupid fucking idiot like this one, or the word dictator is one of the words that shows up when I google your name, then this post is not for you.]]></summary></entry></feed>