<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://hesaidlove.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://hesaidlove.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" /><updated>2025-04-27T16:44:18+01:00</updated><id>https://hesaidlove.com/feed.xml</id><title type="html">He Said Love</title><subtitle>A rampant homosexual, an adult webcam streamer, a meme theologian, a not-so-modest philosopher, a practical computer scientist, a clumsy dancer, and most importantly, a Christ bro.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A burning love that wished for death because that would have been mercy.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">On Matthew 25 and Forgiveness</title><link href="https://hesaidlove.com/posts/on-matthew-25-and-forgiveness/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Matthew 25 and Forgiveness" /><published>2025-04-27T09:13:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-04-27T16:21:21+01:00</updated><id>https://hesaidlove.com/posts/on-matthew-25-and-forgiveness</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaidlove.com/posts/on-matthew-25-and-forgiveness/"><![CDATA[<p>To the theologians and philosophers who received my email and got here, feel free to let me know if I can help with the resurrection of theology and philosophy. I will be focusing on bringing my community, who were condemned but guiltless, back to Him.</p>

<hr />

<p>Revelation 14:1–5</p>

<p>The Lamb and the 144,000</p>

<p>[1] Then I looked, and behold, on Mount Zion stood the Lamb, and with him 144,000 who had his name and his Father’s name written on their foreheads. [2] And I heard a voice from heaven like the roar of many waters and like the sound of loud thunder. The voice I heard was like the sound of harpists playing on their harps, [3] and they were singing a new song before the throne and before the four living creatures and before the elders. No one could learn that song except the 144,000 who had been redeemed from the earth. [4] It is these who have not defiled themselves with women, for they are virgins. It is these who follow the Lamb wherever he goes. These have been redeemed from mankind as firstfruits for God and the Lamb, [5] and in their mouth no lie was found, for they are blameless. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<embed src="https://dl.hesaidlove.com/Re_Matthew_25_and_Forgiveness.pdf" type="application/pdf" width="100%" height="700px" />]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[To the theologians and philosophers who received my email and got here, feel free to let me know if I can help with the resurrection of theology and philosophy. I will be focusing on bringing my community, who were condemned but guiltless, back to Him.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On My Suffering</title><link href="https://hesaidlove.com/posts/on-my-suffering/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On My Suffering" /><published>2025-04-17T19:06:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-04-17T19:14:16+01:00</updated><id>https://hesaidlove.com/posts/on-my-suffering</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaidlove.com/posts/on-my-suffering/"><![CDATA[<p>There is only so much I, a mere mortal human being, can do. Thank you.</p>

<p><a href="https://aparableoflove.com">https://aparableoflove.com</a></p>

<p><a href="https://thesuffering.one">https://thesuffering.one</a></p>

<embed src="https://dl.hesaidlove.com/News.pdf" type="application/pdf" width="100%" height="700px" />]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is only so much I, a mere mortal human being, can do. Thank you.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Nothingness</title><link href="https://hesaidlove.com/posts/on-nothingness/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Nothingness" /><published>2025-04-15T12:34:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-04-18T12:39:50+01:00</updated><id>https://hesaidlove.com/posts/on-nothingness</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaidlove.com/posts/on-nothingness/"><![CDATA[<p>Jesus Christ, what a Glorious and Holy Name; what a King of Kings!</p>

<p>And I have not finished three out of the four gospels. I quickly flipped through Matthew once on my way to Moscow.</p>

<p>The truth does set you free. It is not just any truth. It is THE TRUTH written on humanity’s bestseller, the Holy Bible, which contains both the Old Testament and the New Testament. If you have never opened one before, my guess is you would be quite annoyed when you open one for the first time. But I can testify and say that it contains 1,000,000,000% good stuff, the best stuff. I would suggest starting with the four gospels, Matthew, Luke, Mark and John. And then just let Him guide you and wing it, which is how I think one should live life anyway. Let Boss Man show you a surprise beyond your wildest imagination around every corner, and just enjoy the ride and thank Him when you get a chance to catch a breadth. I’m going back to start over again.</p>

<p>And He does answer prayers. I called for the first time in my life back in July last year. And Dude showed up five weeks later to save me. I asked Him to allow me to save some rampant homosexuals before I even read the Book of Jonah. It took less than 30 weeks. I need to learn to be patient. The good stuff takes time and the Maestro’s work is just absolutely sick, majestic and renders one speechless.</p>

<p>Anyway, I have got a water baptism to attend this weekend. That is a wrap for <a href="https://gonnabelit.com/" target="_blank">GonnaBeLit: He Said Love</a>. The follow-up series is in production, and updates will be posted on <a href="https://suffering.one" target="_blank">Suffering One</a>.</p>

<p>Halle-fucking-lujah! And enjoy.</p>

<p>P.S. I tried taking the shortcut using ProtonMail. Got bounced straight away by their email server due to 100x recipients. I’m gonna stop taking shortcuts. Yes, Boss; okay, Boss; Your Wish is my Command, Boss. Lesson learned.</p>

<hr />

<p>Matthew 7:12–14</p>

<p>The Golden Rule</p>

<p>[12] “So whatever you wish that others would do to you, do also to them, for this is the Law and the Prophets.</p>

<p>[13] “Enter by the narrow gate. For the gate is wide and the way is easy that leads to destruction, and those who enter by it are many. [14] For the gate is narrow and the way is hard that leads to life, and those who find it are few. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>Edit: Hopefully, this is the final edit of GonnaBeLit. This is for the blind, for the deaf and for the illiterate to proclaim liberty to the captives, and the opening of the prison to those who are bound. Boss Man said it long ago. And it was written long ago. You either believe He is the way and the truth and the life or you don’t. If you believe Him, then you would agree that Moses is the accuser, the ancient serpent who led the whole world astray. You can never justify killing with love, which in its true form would always make you fearlessly sacrifice for others, even if that means giving up your own life. Enjoy, and I will see you at sunrise.</p>

<hr />

<p>Zechariah 3:1</p>

<p>A Vision of Joshua the High Priest</p>

<p>[1] Then he showed me Joshua the high priest standing before the angel of the LORD, and Satan standing at his right hand to accuse him. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>John 5:45</p>

<p>[45] Do not think that I will accuse you to the Father. There is one who accuses you: Moses, on whom you have set your hope. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>Revelation 12:10</p>

<p>[10] And I heard a loud voice in heaven, saying, “Now the salvation and the power and the kingdom of our God and the authority of his Christ have come, for the accuser of our brothers has been thrown down, who accuses them day and night before our God. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<embed src="https://dl.hesaidlove.com/on_nothingness.pdf" type="application/pdf" width="100%" height="700px" />]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jesus Christ, what a Glorious and Holy Name; what a King of Kings!]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Publishing</title><link href="https://hesaidlove.com/posts/on-publishing/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Publishing" /><published>2025-03-31T12:21:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-03-31T13:02:52+01:00</updated><id>https://hesaidlove.com/posts/on-publishing</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaidlove.com/posts/on-publishing/"><![CDATA[<p>The only thing I knew about the publishing industry 24 hours ago was they printed books.</p>

<p>I pulled another all-nighter again last night. I hope I can stop that soon.</p>

<p>The order of events I remember after staring at a handful of pages for 24 hours is roughly the following.</p>

<hr />

<p>Frances Haugen</p>

<p>Jane Friedman</p>

<p>Sinister Malefactor of Panglossian Expectations</p>

<p>An annoyingly bitter, sarcastic and relatable welcoming letter</p>

<p>Someone had some issues with getting emails delivered</p>

<p>Beautiful poetry on Sartre’s gastrointestinal problems</p>

<p>Some news about Lit Mag</p>

<p>Something about having pockets</p>

<p>Something about post road</p>

<p>A whole lot on AI and various other matters in between</p>

<hr />

<p>If you did not follow, you don’t and won’t need to know. If you followed, you would know without me telling you.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The only thing I knew about the publishing industry 24 hours ago was they printed books.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On 100 Trillion</title><link href="https://hesaidlove.com/posts/on-100-trillion/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On 100 Trillion" /><published>2025-03-31T01:25:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-03-31T03:33:05+01:00</updated><id>https://hesaidlove.com/posts/on-100-trillion</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaidlove.com/posts/on-100-trillion/"><![CDATA[<p>I slacked off again 27 weeks into my internship and spent part of yesterday investigating a suspected rehearsal in October 2021, possibly for the grand premier of an epic show. I believe the show is premiering in three months.</p>

<p>The buzzwords are AIT, 10 million^2 and <a href="https://www.gambleaware.org/media/xwflz4jd/ga_relative-risk-infographic_final.pdf" target="_blank">GambleAware</a>.</p>

<p>Gonna be dark.</p>

<p>The Stripe logo is purple.</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="under-the-lights---cassio-monroe">Under The Lights - Cassio Monroe</h2>

<iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/6k8pcAdClw6a2dlK23itYO?utm_source=generator&amp;theme=0" width="100%" height="152" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I slacked off again 27 weeks into my internship and spent part of yesterday investigating a suspected rehearsal in October 2021, possibly for the grand premier of an epic show. I believe the show is premiering in three months.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Crypto</title><link href="https://hesaidlove.com/posts/on-crypto/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Crypto" /><published>2025-03-29T05:26:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-29T05:26:00+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaidlove.com/posts/on-crypto</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaidlove.com/posts/on-crypto/"><![CDATA[<p>I had quite a day yesterday and pulled another all-nighter.</p>

<hr />

<embed src="https://dl.hesaidlove.com/Cover_Letter_to_Solflare.pdf" type="application/pdf" width="100%" height="700px" />

<hr />

<embed src="https://dl.hesaidlove.com/CV.pdf" type="application/pdf" width="100%" height="700px" />

<hr />

<p>I tried to cheat again, but Mr Noisy Gong’s style differs quite a lot from mine.</p>

<p>Enjoy, and God bless.</p>

<hr />

<embed src="https://dl.hesaidlove.com/gpt-4o_cover_letter.pdf" type="application/pdf" width="100%" height="600px" />]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I had quite a day yesterday and pulled another all-nighter.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Dignity</title><link href="https://hesaidlove.com/posts/on-dignity/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Dignity" /><published>2025-03-26T17:26:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-28T16:36:02+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaidlove.com/posts/on-dignity</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaidlove.com/posts/on-dignity/"><![CDATA[<p>What would you be willing to sacrifice to save someone you love?</p>

<p>I tried laying down my life in mainland China last October. By the grace of God, it did not work out unexpectedly.</p>

<p>How much is the salvation of a soul worth to you?</p>

<p>It is priceless for me. And my dignity is nothing compared to the salvation of a soul, especially for my community.</p>

<p>I had a blast earlier today doing another stream on Stripchat. It was my best stream because the crowd was kind and loved to chat. It turns out I love bringing the good news of salvation to my fellow rampant homosexuals and helping them to know who God is.</p>

<p>As one observant viewer elegantly put it, things got deeper than the fuck machine at the end.</p>

<p>I totally did not expect to be a sex worker one day, but oh well. I will start handing out my servant business cards at Horse Fair and FickstutenMarkt. It’s been a while since the drone crash.</p>

<p>I will not embed the director’s cut of the stream highlight here. It is way too explosive and NSFW. You can find it on my Stripchat profile for free and IPFS if you want to.</p>

<p>ipfs://bafybeigxxzyamhbz66w7xu7bufonadl4v7nespkroa2ezl7aai53we5cgy</p>

<p>Enjoy.</p>

<hr />

<p>Edit (28 March 2025)</p>

<p>I was hoping to do another stream earlier today. However, I totally did not expect it would take me an entire day to produce a Not-Really-SFW director’s cut for general consumption.</p>

<p>I got really annoyed at ChatGPT again. Anyway, I will not be paying OpenAI a single dollar anymore. I found a list of goodies that I can play with. I’m already self-hosting Open WebUI. I would have gone entirely open-source if it wasn’t for the $12 I paid OpenAI last year for the project Bible Says Love. I don’t think the sky is the limit this time.</p>

<p>It will be fun.</p>

<embed src="https://dl.hesaidlove.com/ubuntu_video_image_overlay.pdf" type="application/pdf" width="100%" height="600px" />

<hr />

<h2 id="isaiah-26">Isaiah 26</h2>

<p>You Keep Him in Perfect Peace</p>

<p>[1] In that day this song will be sung in the land of Judah:</p>

<p>“We have a strong city;<br />
      he sets up salvation<br />
      as walls and bulwarks.<br />
 [2] Open the gates,<br />
      that the righteous nation that keeps faith may enter in.<br />
 [3] You keep him in perfect peace<br />
      whose mind is stayed on you,<br />
      because he trusts in you.<br />
 [4] Trust in the LORD forever,<br />
      for the LORD GOD is an everlasting rock.<br />
 [5] For he has humbled<br />
      the inhabitants of the height,<br />
      the lofty city.<br />
 He lays it low, lays it low to the ground,<br />
      casts it to the dust.<br />
 [6] The foot tramples it,<br />
      the feet of the poor,<br />
      the steps of the needy.”</p>

<p>[7] The path of the righteous is level;<br />
      you make level the way of the righteous.<br />
 [8] In the path of your judgments,<br />
      O LORD, we wait for you;<br />
 your name and remembrance<br />
      are the desire of our soul.<br />
 [9] My soul yearns for you in the night;<br />
      my spirit within me earnestly seeks you.<br />
 For when your judgments are in the earth,<br />
      the inhabitants of the world learn righteousness.<br />
 [10] If favor is shown to the wicked,<br />
      he does not learn righteousness;<br />
 in the land of uprightness he deals corruptly<br />
      and does not see the majesty of the LORD.<br />
 [11] O LORD, your hand is lifted up,<br />
      but they do not see it.<br />
 Let them see your zeal for your people, and be ashamed.<br />
      Let the fire for your adversaries consume them.<br />
 [12] O LORD, you will ordain peace for us,<br />
      for you have indeed done for us all our works.<br />
 [13] O LORD our God,<br />
      other lords besides you have ruled over us,<br />
      but your name alone we bring to remembrance.<br />
 [14] They are dead, they will not live;<br />
      they are shades, they will not arise;<br />
 to that end you have visited them with destruction<br />
      and wiped out all remembrance of them.<br />
 [15] But you have increased the nation, O LORD,<br />
      you have increased the nation; you are glorified;<br />
      you have enlarged all the borders of the land.</p>

<p>[16] O LORD, in distress they sought you;<br />
      they poured out a whispered prayer<br />
      when your discipline was upon them.<br />
 [17] Like a pregnant woman<br />
      who writhes and cries out in her pangs<br />
      when she is near to giving birth,<br />
 so were we because of you, O LORD;<br />
 [18]  we were pregnant, we writhed,<br />
      but we have given birth to wind.<br />
 We have accomplished no deliverance in the earth,<br />
      and the inhabitants of the world have not fallen.<br />
 [19] Your dead shall live; their bodies shall rise.<br />
      You who dwell in the dust, awake and sing for joy!<br />
 For your dew is a dew of light,<br />
      and the earth will give birth to the dead.</p>

<p>[20] Come, my people, enter your chambers,<br />
      and shut your doors behind you;<br />
 hide yourselves for a little while<br />
      until the fury has passed by.<br />
 [21] For behold, the LORD is coming out from his place<br />
      to punish the inhabitants of the earth for their iniquity,<br />
 and the earth will disclose the blood shed on it,<br />
      and will no more cover its slain. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="theres-nothing-holdin-me-back---shawn-mendes">There’s Nothing Holdin’ Me Back - Shawn Mendes</h2>

<p>Interesting. I added this song to my Spotify Liked Songs playlist on 26 August 2024, the second day of His three-day visit and the day He baptised me with the Holy Spirit. I misheard the line “we stumbled in the dark” as “we assemble in the dark”.</p>

<hr />

<p><img src="/MAHn8HWXbWdHWmewUpZ2.png" alt="Spotify Liked Songs" /></p>

<hr />

<p>I got a lot of things wrong on this 26-week and 3-day faith journey. I thought there might be a day that I would burn capitalism down, but as my Christian missionary guide in mainland China put it, capitalism is already well done now and about to get burnt.</p>

<p>I worry unnecessarily way too much. It gets annoying to care. I guess that is why most people don’t.</p>

<hr />

<iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/7JJmb5XwzOO8jgpou264Ml?utm_source=generator&amp;theme=0" width="100%" height="152" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe>

<div id="rg_embed_link_3051803" class="rg_embed_link" data-song-id="3051803">Read <a href="https://genius.com/Shawn-mendes-theres-nothing-holdin-me-back-lyrics">“There's Nothing Holdin' Me Back” by Shawn Mendes</a> on Genius</div>
<script crossorigin="" src="https://genius.com/songs/3051803/embed.js"></script>

<h2 id="peanut-butter-jelly---galantis">Peanut Butter Jelly - Galantis</h2>

<iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/2WlEuHXJjUJeMGUdK3f6Ny?utm_source=generator&amp;theme=0" width="100%" height="152" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe>

<div id="rg_embed_link_974109" class="rg_embed_link" data-song-id="974109">Read <a href="https://genius.com/Galantis-peanut-butter-jelly-lyrics">“Peanut Butter Jelly” by Galantis</a> on Genius</div>
<script crossorigin="" src="https://genius.com/songs/974109/embed.js"></script>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[What would you be willing to sacrifice to save someone you love?]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Idolatry</title><link href="https://hesaidlove.com/posts/on-idolatry/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Idolatry" /><published>2025-03-25T09:27:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-27T03:08:09+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaidlove.com/posts/on-idolatry</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaidlove.com/posts/on-idolatry/"><![CDATA[<p>I discussed with an antichrist pretending to be a Christian this morning. How do I know they are an antichrist? Because they speak as though they have never read one of the gospels, and nearly every opinion they express goes against Boss Man’s teachings.</p>

<p>I watched a sermon on the abomination of desolation on YouTube a while back. The preacher mentioned that Boss Man hates idolatry the most, and the severity of His hatred against idolatry is like no other in the Old Testament.</p>

<p>Shortly before writing this post, it dawned on me what it truly means to worship false idols. I realized there is a form of idolatry that many people, including most Christians, antichrists included, might not even recognize. But before I unpack all that, let’s revisit what Boss Man said about the commandments.</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="matthew-223440">Matthew 22:34–40</h2>

<p>The Great Commandment</p>

<p>[34] But when the Pharisees heard that he had silenced the Sadducees, they gathered together. [35] And one of them, a lawyer, asked him a question to test him. [36] “Teacher, which is the great commandment in the Law?” <strong><em>[37] And he said to him, “You shall love the Lord your God with all your heart and with all your soul and with all your mind. [38] This is the great and first commandment. [39] And a second is like it: You shall love your neighbor as yourself. [40] On these two commandments depend all the Law and the Prophets.”</em></strong> (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>Did you notice the verb in both commandments is the same? Boss Man said to <strong><em>love</em></strong>. I suspect unbelievers and possibly most Christians, especially the antichrists, do not know what the first commandment means. You need to know who God is and what He is like before you can understand the first commandment. John the Apostle answered that in 1 John.</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="1-john-4712">1 John 4:7–12</h2>

<p>God Is Love</p>

<p><strong><em>[7] Beloved, let us love one another, for love is from God, and whoever loves has been born of God and knows God. [8] Anyone who does not love does not know God, because God is love.</em></strong> [9] In this the love of God was made manifest among us, that God sent his only Son into the world, so that we might live through him. [10] In this is love, not that we have loved God but that he loved us and sent his Son to be the propitiation for our sins. [11] Beloved, if God so loved us, we also ought to love one another. [12] No one has ever seen God; if we love one another, God abides in us and his love is perfected in us. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>Assuming you did not fail your logical reasoning or reading comprehension in school, you should be able to logically deduce the following statement using the concept of <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Equivalence_relation" target="_blank">equivalence relations</a>. You shall <strong>love <em>love</em></strong> with all your heart and with all your soul and with all your mind.</p>

<p>If you have followed the logical reasoning up to this point, it is natural to wonder, “What is love?” If you are the lucky target of my clickbait campaigns, you would know the equation of love I derived at age 16.</p>

<p><strong>Love is the greatest sacrifice one is willing to make. Just ask any father what they are willing to sacrifice for their child.</strong></p>

<p>The definition is confirmed by Boss Man’s actions 2,000 years ago before He went on a 2,000-year paid leave due to a severe workplace injury, as well as His words.</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="john-151217">John 15:12–17</h2>

<p>[12] “This is my commandment, that you love one another as I have loved you. <strong><em>[13] Greater love has no one than this, that someone lay down his life for his friends.</em></strong> [14] You are my friends if you do what I command you. [15] No longer do I call you servants, for the servant does not know what his master is doing; but I have called you friends, for all that I have heard from my Father I have made known to you. [16] You did not choose me, but I chose you and appointed you that you should go and bear fruit and that your fruit should abide, so that whatever you ask the Father in my name, he may give it to you. [17] These things I command you, so that you will love one another. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>Through the <a href="../on-genesis-3-fall-man/" target="_blank">lesson of Genesis 3</a>, we learned the importance of the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Order_of_operations" target="_blank">order of precedence</a>. We can apply the same principle here and deduce the following statement. You are worshipping a false idol called <strong>the law</strong> if you believe God hates rampant homosexuals like me. <strong>You are effectively putting the law above God by putting the law above love.</strong></p>

<hr />

<h2 id="1-corinthians-13">1 Corinthians 13</h2>

<p>The Way of Love</p>

<p>[1] If I speak in the tongues of men and of angels, but have not love, I am a noisy gong or a clanging cymbal. [2] And if I have prophetic powers, and understand all mysteries and all knowledge, and if I have all faith, so as to remove mountains, but have not love, I am nothing. [3] If I give away all I have, and if I deliver up my body to be burned, but have not love, I gain nothing.</p>

<p>[4] Love is patient and kind; love does not envy or boast; it is not arrogant [5] or rude. It does not insist on its own way; it is not irritable or resentful; [6] it does not rejoice at wrongdoing, but rejoices with the truth. [7] Love bears all things, believes all things, hopes all things, endures all things.</p>

<p>[8] Love never ends. As for prophecies, they will pass away; as for tongues, they will cease; as for knowledge, it will pass away. [9] For we know in part and we prophesy in part, [10] but when the perfect comes, the partial will pass away. [11] When I was a child, I spoke like a child, I thought like a child, I reasoned like a child. When I became a man, I gave up childish ways. [12] For now we see in a mirror dimly, but then face to face. Now I know in part; then I shall know fully, even as I have been fully known.</p>

<p><strong><em>[13] So now faith, hope, and love abide, these three; but the greatest of these is love.</em></strong> (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<p>Through this 26-week and 2-day faith journey, I learned the world does not know God and love. If you subscribe to the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Darwinism" target="_blank">religion of Darwinism</a>, you would not know God and love because you do not know what it means to sacrifice. All you would know is natural selection and survival of the fittest. Your existence and suffering are inherently meaningless due to <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Existentialism" target="_blank">existentialism</a>, <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nihilism" target="_blank">nihilism</a> and <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Antinatalism" target="_blank">antinatalism</a>. There is nothing but death waiting for you at the end of the road. Congratulations, I guess.</p>

<p>I came across this <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uD4izuDMUQA" target="_blank">video on YouTube</a> called <em>TIMELAPSE OF THE FUTURE: A Journey to the End of Time (4K)</em> during COVID-19. I was obsessed with <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Quantum_mechanics" target="_blank">quantum mechanics</a> and the mysteries of our physical universe. It’s an amazing production, but unfortunately, it’s also a load of bull excrement. Now that I know the truth. Enjoy.</p>

<hr />

<p>
  <video class="embed-video file" controls="">
    
    

    
    
    

    

    
      
      
      
      <source src="https://dl.hesaidlove.com/A_Journey_to_the_End_of_Time.webm" type="video/webm" />
    

    Your browser does not support the video tag. Here is a
    <a href="https://dl.hesaidlove.com/A_Journey_to_the_End_of_Time.webm">link to the video file</a> instead.
  </video>
  
</p>

<hr />

<embed src="https://dl.hesaidlove.com/What_God_Hates.pdf" type="application/pdf" width="100%" height="600px" />

<hr />

<h2 id="memes">Memes</h2>

<p><img src="/23b77f88ffc37781d362c68e8fb444a0.jpeg" alt="God: Did I stutter?!" /></p>

<p><img src="/599ccf5c3b42e6259e003d6682a1cb42.png" alt="Me explaining the deep mysteries of God" /></p>

<p><img src="/625e87e562806d2e10e2d1e239fddc7a.jpeg" alt="Christians on the internet" /></p>

<hr />

<h2 id="a-thousand-years---christina-perri">A Thousand Years - Christina Perri</h2>

<iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/6z5Yh7kOKeLjqIsNdokIpU?utm_source=generator&amp;theme=0" width="100%" height="152" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe>

<div id="rg_embed_link_98919" class="rg_embed_link" data-song-id="98919">Read <a href="https://genius.com/Christina-perri-a-thousand-years-lyrics">“A Thousand Years” by Christina Perri</a> on Genius</div>
<script crossorigin="" src="https://genius.com/songs/98919/embed.js"></script>

<h2 id="price-tag---jessie-j-bob">Price Tag - Jessie J, B.o.B</h2>

<iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/2fTsFCKRFQ5M0igJgabnLA?utm_source=generator&amp;theme=0" width="100%" height="152" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe>

<div id="rg_embed_link_6125" class="rg_embed_link" data-song-id="6125">Read <a href="https://genius.com/Jessie-j-price-tag-lyrics">“Price Tag” by Jessie J</a> on Genius</div>
<script crossorigin="" src="https://genius.com/songs/6125/embed.js"></script>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I discussed with an antichrist pretending to be a Christian this morning. How do I know they are an antichrist? Because they speak as though they have never read one of the gospels, and nearly every opinion they express goes against Boss Man’s teachings.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Irony</title><link href="https://hesaidlove.com/posts/on-irony/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Irony" /><published>2025-03-25T00:33:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-26T15:26:15+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaidlove.com/posts/on-irony</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaidlove.com/posts/on-irony/"><![CDATA[<p>I am a rampant homosexual who got fucked in the ass by hundreds, if not thousands, of men. I had 20+ men dump their loads inside me on one evening alone early last year.</p>

<p>If you have read the Book of Hebrews chapter 11, I might have accidentally condemned the world on my second week as a believer. And I am advising you what it means to be faithful.</p>

<p>Does God have a sense of humour? I think He is the King of Irony.</p>

<p>It does not look great. Does it?</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="hebrews-11">Hebrews 11</h2>

<p>By Faith</p>

<p>[1] Now faith is the assurance of things hoped for, the conviction of things not seen. [2] For by it the people of old received their commendation. [3] By faith we understand that the universe was created by the word of God, so that what is seen was not made out of things that are visible.</p>

<p>[4] By faith Abel offered to God a more acceptable sacrifice than Cain, through which he was commended as righteous, God commending him by accepting his gifts. And through his faith, though he died, he still speaks. [5] By faith Enoch was taken up so that he should not see death, and he was not found, because God had taken him. Now before he was taken he was commended as having pleased God. [6] And without faith it is impossible to please him, for whoever would draw near to God must believe that he exists and that he rewards those who seek him. <strong><em>[7] By faith Noah, being warned by God concerning events as yet unseen, in reverent fear constructed an ark for the saving of his household. By this he condemned the world and became an heir of the righteousness that comes by faith.</em></strong></p>

<p>[8] By faith Abraham obeyed when he was called to go out to a place that he was to receive as an inheritance. And he went out, not knowing where he was going. [9] By faith he went to live in the land of promise, as in a foreign land, living in tents with Isaac and Jacob, heirs with him of the same promise. [10] For he was looking forward to the city that has foundations, whose designer and builder is God. [11] By faith Sarah herself received power to conceive, even when she was past the age, since she considered him faithful who had promised. [12] Therefore from one man, and him as good as dead, were born descendants as many as the stars of heaven and as many as the innumerable grains of sand by the seashore.</p>

<p>[13] These all died in faith, not having received the things promised, but having seen them and greeted them from afar, and having acknowledged that they were strangers and exiles on the earth. [14] For people who speak thus make it clear that they are seeking a homeland. [15] If they had been thinking of that land from which they had gone out, they would have had opportunity to return. [16] But as it is, they desire a better country, that is, a heavenly one. Therefore God is not ashamed to be called their God, for he has prepared for them a city.</p>

<p>[17] By faith Abraham, when he was tested, offered up Isaac, and he who had received the promises was in the act of offering up his only son, [18] of whom it was said, “Through Isaac shall your offspring be named.” [19] He considered that God was able even to raise him from the dead, from which, figuratively speaking, he did receive him back. [20] By faith Isaac invoked future blessings on Jacob and Esau. [21] By faith Jacob, when dying, blessed each of the sons of Joseph, bowing in worship over the head of his staff. [22] By faith Joseph, at the end of his life, made mention of the exodus of the Israelites and gave directions concerning his bones.</p>

<p>[23] By faith Moses, when he was born, was hidden for three months by his parents, because they saw that the child was beautiful, and they were not afraid of the king’s edict. [24] By faith Moses, when he was grown up, refused to be called the son of Pharaoh’s daughter, [25] choosing rather to be mistreated with the people of God than to enjoy the fleeting pleasures of sin. [26] He considered the reproach of Christ greater wealth than the treasures of Egypt, for he was looking to the reward. [27] By faith he left Egypt, not being afraid of the anger of the king, for he endured as seeing him who is invisible. [28] By faith he kept the Passover and sprinkled the blood, so that the Destroyer of the firstborn might not touch them.</p>

<p>[29] By faith the people crossed the Red Sea as on dry land, but the Egyptians, when they attempted to do the same, were drowned. [30] By faith the walls of Jericho fell down after they had been encircled for seven days. [31] By faith Rahab the prostitute did not perish with those who were disobedient, because she had given a friendly welcome to the spies.</p>

<p>[32] And what more shall I say? For time would fail me to tell of Gideon, Barak, Samson, Jephthah, of David and Samuel and the prophets—[33] who through faith conquered kingdoms, enforced justice, obtained promises, stopped the mouths of lions, [34] quenched the power of fire, escaped the edge of the sword, were made strong out of weakness, became mighty in war, put foreign armies to flight. [35] Women received back their dead by resurrection. Some were tortured, refusing to accept release, so that they might rise again to a better life. [36] Others suffered mocking and flogging, and even chains and imprisonment. [37] They were stoned, they were sawn in two, they were killed with the sword. They went about in skins of sheep and goats, destitute, afflicted, mistreated—[38] of whom the world was not worthy—wandering about in deserts and mountains, and in dens and caves of the earth.</p>

<p>[39] And all these, though commended through their faith, did not receive what was promised, [40] since God had provided something better for us, that apart from us they should not be made perfect. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="issues---julia-michaels">Issues - Julia Michaels</h2>

<iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/7vu0JkJh0ldukEYbTVcqd0?utm_source=generator&amp;theme=0" width="100%" height="152" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe>

<div id="rg_embed_link_2942605" class="rg_embed_link" data-song-id="2942605">Read <a href="https://genius.com/Julia-michaels-issues-lyrics">“Issues” by Julia Michaels</a> on Genius</div>
<script crossorigin="" src="https://genius.com/songs/2942605/embed.js"></script>

<hr />

<h2 id="meme">Meme</h2>

<p><img src="/s98TtTvYEtYc0jFG4d.jpg" alt="Where are the turtles?!" /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am a rampant homosexual who got fucked in the ass by hundreds, if not thousands, of men. I had 20+ men dump their loads inside me on one evening alone early last year.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Good and Evil</title><link href="https://hesaidlove.com/posts/on-good-and-evil/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Good and Evil" /><published>2025-03-24T15:07:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-28T13:34:27+00:00</updated><id>https://hesaidlove.com/posts/on-good-and-evil</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hesaidlove.com/posts/on-good-and-evil/"><![CDATA[<p><a href="../on-background-music/#definition-of-good" target="_blank">Here</a> is a quick reminder of the definition of good from my early teenage years. The TL;DR is to wet my pants rather than cross the road at a red light.</p>

<p>I published <a href="https://uncensoredmodels.com" target="_blank">the post</a> on uncensored models this past weekend after learning that one could get an uncensored large language model up and running with a handful of commands in minutes, subject to the download speed of their internet connection. Technically, anyone can start making devices that resemble the word boobs.</p>

<p>In case you have not read my posts—which I would not expect you to have—I spent the last decade studying four undergraduate degrees in mathematics, physics, computer science, philosophy, and modern ballet. I also cooked solid-state rocket fuels when I was in high school. Frankly, I should be on a list somewhere if I am not already.</p>

<p>I got kicked out of a gay/bi-naturist campsite last July, and due to the unfaithfulness of a former business partner, I had to move all of my camping equipment back to my London flat. As of the moment of writing, I have six 3D printers in my flat, including a Bambu X1-Carbon with AMS, which I’m forbidden from selling due to bankruptcy proceedings. I also have enough camping equipment, which allowed me to survive outdoors for three months without stepping foot outside of the campsite, and an abundance of electrical equipment that enabled me to run a solo IT department for a campsite with a max capacity of 200+ guests and give them full Wi-Fi coverage for free.</p>

<p>If this is anyone else, I think some people should start writing to their MP and be very worried by now. If Boss Man didn’t show up last August to save me, I would have thrown myself off the fifth-floor balcony in my flat more than a dozen times. But, being the delusional nutjob that I am, I instead chose to put up some nipples, spam people with clickbait campaigns, <a href="../on-forgiveness/" target="_blank">keep emailing</a> some people and hope they would repent and turn from their evil ways. And my rent is six months overdue.</p>

<p>You tell me if I know how to spell good and evil.</p>

<p>I am always an ass man and never a boobs guy anyway.</p>

<hr />

<p><img src="/1qfxtsMv5P4QuGayyF.jpg" alt="4 of 6 3D printers" /></p>

<hr />

<h2 id="1-peter-3822">1 Peter 3:8–22</h2>

<p>Suffering for Righteousness’ Sake</p>

<p>[8] Finally, all of you, have unity of mind, sympathy, brotherly love, a tender heart, and a humble mind. <strong><em>[9] Do not repay evil for evil or reviling for reviling, but on the contrary, bless, for to this you were called, that you may obtain a blessing.</em></strong> [10] For</p>

<p>“Whoever desires to love life<br />
      and see good days,<br />
 let him keep his tongue from evil<br />
      and his lips from speaking deceit;<br />
 [11] let him turn away from evil and do good;<br />
      let him seek peace and pursue it.<br />
 [12] For the eyes of the Lord are on the righteous,<br />
      and his ears are open to their prayer.<br />
 But the face of the Lord is against those who do evil.”</p>

<p>[13] Now who is there to harm you if you are zealous for what is good? [14] But even if you should suffer for righteousness’ sake, you will be blessed. Have no fear of them, nor be troubled, [15] but in your hearts honor Christ the Lord as holy, always being prepared to make a defense to anyone who asks you for a reason for the hope that is in you; yet do it with gentleness and respect, [16] having a good conscience, so that, when you are slandered, those who revile your good behavior in Christ may be put to shame. [17] For it is better to suffer for doing good, if that should be God’s will, than for doing evil.</p>

<p>[18] For Christ also suffered once for sins, the righteous for the unrighteous, that he might bring us to God, being put to death in the flesh but made alive in the spirit, [19] in which he went and proclaimed to the spirits in prison, [20] because they formerly did not obey, when God’s patience waited in the days of Noah, while the ark was being prepared, in which a few, that is, eight persons, were brought safely through water. [21] Baptism, which corresponds to this, now saves you, not as a removal of dirt from the body but as an appeal to God for a good conscience, through the resurrection of Jesus Christ, [22] who has gone into heaven and is at the right hand of God, with angels, authorities, and powers having been subjected to him. (ESV)</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="just-give-me-a-reason---pnk">Just Give Me a Reason - P!nk</h2>

<iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/1mKXFLRA179hdOWQBwUk9e?utm_source=generator&amp;theme=0" width="100%" height="152" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe>

<div id="rg_embed_link_108589" class="rg_embed_link" data-song-id="108589">Read <a href="https://genius.com/P-nk-just-give-me-a-reason-lyrics">“Just Give Me a Reason” by P!nk</a> on Genius</div>
<script crossorigin="" src="https://genius.com/songs/108589/embed.js"></script>

<h2 id="true-colors-ft-maya-avedis---xo-cupid">True Colors (ft. Maya Avedis) - XO Cupid</h2>

<iframe style="border-radius:12px" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/4AMY0oGSt7vZwgxDnHCJBr?utm_source=generator&amp;theme=0" width="100%" height="152" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe>

<div id="rg_embed_link_3988413" class="rg_embed_link" data-song-id="3988413">Read <a href="https://genius.com/Xo-cupid-true-colors-lyrics">“True Colors” by XO Cupid</a> on Genius</div>
<script crossorigin="" src="https://genius.com/songs/3988413/embed.js"></script>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is a quick reminder of the definition of good from my early teenage years. The TL;DR is to wet my pants rather than cross the road at a red light.]]></summary></entry></feed>